{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -93 + (((-42 % (89 - -73)) + (52 - (-91 * -92))) + -76)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 0, "answer": -8369}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (44 // -49) % (((15 - 51) * -28) + -98)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1, "answer": 909}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-60 * -44) + (-73 + -76)) + (-75 + -8)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2, "answer": 2408}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((87 - (38 - -68)) - (-79 + 42)) + (61 + 59)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 3, "answer": 138}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-88 - 70) + (98 * (-79 - -40))) - (-2 - -28)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 4, "answer": -4006}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-5 - (-46 + 72)) % ((56 + 63) + -56)) % 37", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 5, "answer": 32}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (19 * -2) - ((76 + (97 + 99)) + (-41 - (-19 * 3)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 6, "answer": -326}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -45 - (((68 // (2 + 65)) - (-63 + -32)) + -64)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 7, "answer": -77}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-7 - -43) + -64) * (-76 % 94)) // -87", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 8, "answer": 5}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (75 // 9) + ((-1 // (53 - 20)) + 36)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 9, "answer": 43}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (75 + ((75 + (97 + 65)) - -12)) - (-24 * 12)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 10, "answer": 612}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (85 + ((30 + -72) - 61)) + (64 * 30)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 11, "answer": 1902}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-4 % 96) * ((54 * -17) * ((-71 + -7) * (-38 + -85)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 12, "answer": -810270864}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-78 + (((95 * 37) + 97) - -67)) // -67", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 13, "answer": -54}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-32 + (-45 - 39)) + 94) - ((83 + (3 + 72)) * 67)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 14, "answer": -10608}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-36 // -42) - -83) + -13) - (51 * (51 * -43))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 15, "answer": 111913}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 82 + (-41 - (-91 - ((32 * -39) - -28)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 16, "answer": -1088}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (39 - (86 + (-37 + 22))) + ((-75 + -75) // (-9 - 9))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 17, "answer": -24}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((73 * (-84 - 4)) + 87) + ((-36 + -50) + -51)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 18, "answer": -6474}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (9 - (-28 * (-36 // -80))) // ((-87 // 67) + (-76 * 93))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 19, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (25 - 24) + (3 + (-57 // (17 + -26)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 20, "answer": 10}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-51 // ((-85 - 49) * 89)) + 39) - -84) - 92", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 21, "answer": 31}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -87 - ((((-85 + (-52 + -82)) - 53) // -82) + 73)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 22, "answer": -163}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (46 % (49 - (59 * -79))) + (69 % 50)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 23, "answer": 65}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((72 - 84) + -19) + (-32 + 2)) + (72 - (18 - -19))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 24, "answer": -26}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 18 - (-81 + ((30 // (-66 + -10)) + -82))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 25, "answer": 182}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((13 % 40) + 81) + ((71 * 42) * -23)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 26, "answer": -68492}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -65 // ((-72 - (-30 * -27)) + ((84 - (-47 - 76)) - 63))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 27, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-76 + 63) + (-29 + -88)) - -99) + (98 * -66)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 28, "answer": -6499}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (90 + (42 - 81)) // (((-71 + (77 - -61)) * 40) - -90)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 29, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-67 + -89) // ((-89 - -8) + -46)) + (71 // -73)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 30, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-39 * (-54 - 6)) - -93) - -54) + (6 + 72)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 31, "answer": 2565}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-59 // 80) * (-2 - (21 - (-48 - (-10 // -21))))) // -41", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 32, "answer": -2}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 69 + ((-15 // -28) + (98 - (-10 * 65)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 33, "answer": 817}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-70 // -33) - -54) + 49) + ((-72 + 53) + (-11 - 87))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 34, "answer": -12}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-1 * (-34 - -88)) - 82) + ((34 + 38) * 76)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 35, "answer": 5336}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((11 + -82) - (((70 * -68) - 85) // -23)) + (71 - 5)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 36, "answer": -215}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-50 - 8) + 71) + -2) // (58 - (4 % 41))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 37, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((11 - 49) * 56) - ((14 - 14) - 73)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 38, "answer": -2055}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((69 * (-27 + 32)) + 70) + 63) - 59", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 39, "answer": 419}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 93 // ((-42 + -49) + (-93 - (-37 % (17 // 7))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 40, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((27 - 3) // (-62 % (93 % 98))) // (9 - (-54 + 79))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 41, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (43 - (-68 + (-65 + 19))) + (((57 // 85) * 30) - 10)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 42, "answer": 147}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (91 + ((-33 - 93) % -36)) * (((61 - -38) // -29) * 13)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 43, "answer": -3796}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-30 - (-18 * 39)) * (-64 * (-40 + -1))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 44, "answer": 1763328}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-83 // 7) * (((7 // -84) - (8 - 0)) - (96 * 48))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 45, "answer": 55404}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-9 - ((8 * 38) // 92)) - (25 + (-30 - 12))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 46, "answer": 5}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 0 + (((20 + -67) - 60) - (1 + (-78 - 65)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 47, "answer": 35}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-53 + -87) * (((-45 * 17) - -16) - (95 + -2))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 48, "answer": 117880}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((21 + -95) + (-10 - -42)) - (67 - (94 + -92))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 49, "answer": -107}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (60 - -60) + (-67 - ((45 * -44) % 20))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 50, "answer": 53}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((56 * 56) + 92) // (-58 % ((49 - -93) + (48 + 74)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 51, "answer": 15}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-80 - (-73 * 79)) + 98) - ((45 + -89) + -11)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 52, "answer": 5840}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((30 * 66) - -12) + -96) - ((-72 % 11) - (63 * 18))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 53, "answer": 3025}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-54 - 88) + ((((12 + 88) - 52) + (-17 * -37)) + -77)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 54, "answer": 458}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (93 * ((-13 + -92) // 27)) - ((25 - -45) + -9)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 55, "answer": -433}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((43 - -97) + 33) - (-78 - (85 - (26 - 43)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 56, "answer": 353}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-95 + -76) - -24) - -43) // (78 - -37)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 57, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((((9 - 91) + 41) - (-9 + 80)) + 17) - -30", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 58, "answer": -65}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-69 - (-19 // -69)) - ((-50 - (90 - 24)) - -29)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 59, "answer": 18}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-50 - (-41 // -7)) // (-22 % -96)) + (-29 + (-86 + 42))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 60, "answer": -71}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-73 + -96) + (((23 + 13) * -12) + -52)) // -86", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 61, "answer": 7}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-83 + ((-81 + 48) * 62)) - (-61 * (45 + -22))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 62, "answer": -726}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (43 // 96) + ((99 * 34) + (16 * 14))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 63, "answer": 3590}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((57 * 90) % (96 * -46)) - 61) * (-32 - 70)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 64, "answer": 383826}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-55 - 42) * (-59 - (5 // (77 // 53)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 65, "answer": 6208}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-40 + (81 * -27)) + (((76 // -40) - -32) * 61)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 66, "answer": -397}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-70 // 40) + (66 // (-31 + (-81 - -84)))) % (-21 + 53)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 67, "answer": 27}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((((20 % 77) - -22) - (-30 - 29)) + (13 + -79)) * 54", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 68, "answer": 1890}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-93 * -76) * -41) * 73) - (96 + 73)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 69, "answer": -21154693}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (96 // (21 - ((-53 + 50) - 12))) + (-76 - 21)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 70, "answer": -95}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((72 + -73) - (-15 * 6)) * ((70 + 3) + 95)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 71, "answer": 14952}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 17 - (-19 % (((98 + 4) * 32) + (69 + (6 * -86))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 72, "answer": -2781}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((95 - -86) * -47) % (41 % -66)) * -26", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 73, "answer": 182}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-92 * (82 + (-20 - 42))) - (42 - 5)) // -76", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 74, "answer": 24}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 19 + (66 - (28 + ((7 + 24) - 21)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 75, "answer": 47}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-1 + (54 + 31)) - 92) - (-82 * -29)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 76, "answer": -2386}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-27 % 86) - -23) % (((15 + 38) // 24) + -11)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 77, "answer": -8}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-51 + 79) + (47 % -1)) // -40) % (-88 - -18)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 78, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((70 + 67) - -61) % 27) - (-67 * ((13 - -74) - 35))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 79, "answer": 3493}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 85 % ((68 - -60) + (21 + ((60 - 78) // 2)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 80, "answer": 85}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -15 - (((((39 // -90) - (-39 - 62)) + 76) + -26) - -41)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 81, "answer": -206}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 12 * (95 * (14 + ((-92 - -88) % ((-37 * 36) - 6))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 82, "answer": 11400}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-55 + -79) * (((28 // 50) * -63) % -40)) - (64 - -34)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 83, "answer": -98}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (20 // (74 // 40)) * (-81 - ((51 + -23) + 64))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 84, "answer": -3460}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-49 % -1) + 24) % (-39 - (47 - -8))) // 48", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 85, "answer": -2}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((69 - (-29 // -97)) + (56 + (-26 - 99))) // -41", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 86, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((63 % (59 * -35)) % ((-91 // 49) - (88 + -66))) + -76", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 87, "answer": -86}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-48 % -66) - 39) - ((-57 + -34) - (-24 * 92))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 88, "answer": -2204}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 20 // (-63 - ((43 + -6) * (2 - (-32 * 38))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 89, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((50 - -2) // (-72 - 73)) + (21 - -93)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 90, "answer": 113}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((66 * (63 + 19)) * (67 - 5)) + (-64 + (-90 + -22))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 91, "answer": 335368}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -75 - ((0 - 17) // ((51 - 91) - (7 - 68)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 92, "answer": -74}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-91 - 77) * -5) - -44) // (14 - -39)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 93, "answer": 16}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 76 - (((2 % -29) + -51) + (17 - (70 // -45)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 94, "answer": 135}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-87 - ((-67 % 45) + (-82 - 96))) + 42) + (51 + -44)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 95, "answer": 117}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (53 + (-29 + -62)) + (39 - (-55 + -71))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 96, "answer": 127}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-66 + (-8 + ((-95 - -55) * ((-67 // 90) - 8)))) + 35", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 97, "answer": 321}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 22 + (((16 + 29) + (58 + -88)) + 87)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 98, "answer": 124}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-84 - 23) + 3) - (76 - -72)) * ((-81 * -79) + -17)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 99, "answer": -1608264}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-67 - -29) * ((((17 + 30) // 55) + (-74 // 80)) + -70)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 100, "answer": 2698}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((16 * -41) - ((17 + 3) + 7)) - 87) - (-19 - 10)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 101, "answer": -741}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((76 - 22) * -82) * (-78 + (11 + -75))) // 91", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 102, "answer": 6909}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (43 - (51 - 44)) + ((6 - (71 + 93)) + (85 - -86))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 103, "answer": 49}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((48 - 30) + -45) + (69 + 24)) + (-72 + -10)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 104, "answer": -16}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (96 - (47 // -42)) - (((56 * (-92 * -53)) - -30) + 80)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 105, "answer": -273068}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-53 - -63) * 45) - (((-63 - 90) + 63) + -92)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 106, "answer": 632}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((8 - 17) % ((-5 - -20) - 85)) - -16", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 107, "answer": 7}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-86 + (-59 + (73 + (-30 + 14)))) + ((56 + 14) + 7)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 108, "answer": -11}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-11 + 11) % (-27 - (((-88 // -43) + 2) - 54))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 109, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -47 * ((97 - (96 + -34)) // (-16 % -69))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 110, "answer": 141}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-66 + -2) + 37) * 81) - (29 // 44)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 111, "answer": -2511}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((2 + (12 - -95)) - ((-19 * 48) + (47 + 4))) - 82", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 112, "answer": 888}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((4 + -94) - (-56 + 59)) - ((-77 + 12) + (-37 - 12))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 113, "answer": 21}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((2 + (91 - -13)) - -43) + ((-80 + 31) % (36 + 31))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 114, "answer": 167}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-39 * -73) + -62) - ((-55 * 55) * -60)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 115, "answer": -178715}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -54 + ((((75 - 45) - (61 - -19)) * (13 // -82)) % 21)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 116, "answer": -46}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-9 * 30) // -81) * ((16 + -90) + -85)) - -5", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 117, "answer": -472}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 66 + (58 + (((16 // 47) * (-17 + 55)) + 22))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 118, "answer": 146}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (16 * -73) * ((30 - (-89 - -36)) - ((35 - 34) // 57))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 119, "answer": -96944}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((0 - 5) - 99) * ((62 - 66) + -14)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 120, "answer": 1872}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (43 + (-27 - -35)) - (-14 - (50 // 70))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 121, "answer": 65}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-66 // 53) - 82) - (-20 // (65 + -15))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 122, "answer": -83}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (66 - (((-95 - -7) + -20) * -53)) - -45", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 123, "answer": -5613}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-42 + (-60 * (-24 // -74))) * (70 + (97 + 59))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 124, "answer": -9492}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-58 * (78 - (85 + 13))) // -88) - 6", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 125, "answer": -20}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((57 * -27) - (((37 + -38) // -20) + 21)) * -50", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 126, "answer": 78000}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((((-2 + 29) * (-58 + -48)) * 55) - -64) * -35", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 127, "answer": 5507110}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((83 - 33) - (-27 + -78)) // (-30 + 16)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 128, "answer": -12}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-76 - -43) - (((7 - -86) % (29 - -4)) - (-1 + -79))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 129, "answer": -140}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-18 - -74) * ((-64 // (-26 + 21)) - (95 // 81))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 130, "answer": 616}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-79 * (-34 // -44)) + -61) - ((99 - -26) - -39)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 131, "answer": -225}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -87 % ((64 * 60) + ((-71 // 28) - (62 // 32)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 132, "answer": 3749}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-25 // 10) - (58 - ((47 // (-52 + 71)) - (35 // -7)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 133, "answer": -54}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (0 + ((63 + 0) * (-35 - 92))) - -95", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 134, "answer": -7906}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -11 * ((98 - 49) - (((-88 - -9) // 40) - -13))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 135, "answer": -418}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (79 - 23) - ((-83 + 84) - ((-24 - -48) + (-48 + -89)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 136, "answer": -58}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-35 // -90) - 93) - ((-26 - (-87 - 68)) + -15)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 137, "answer": -207}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -5 % (((-1 + -13) + (28 % 78)) + (-5 - 33))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 138, "answer": -5}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 87 // ((11 + (40 - (-17 - -73))) + (-16 * 70))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 139, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-57 + 77) + 14) + ((-89 + 87) - (58 - 12))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 140, "answer": -14}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-80 - (((-92 * -63) - (-91 - -67)) - -82)) - -39", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 141, "answer": -5943}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((46 + -91) + 55) - ((-5 // -4) + ((47 % -64) - 36))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 142, "answer": 62}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-36 - -70) + (89 + -52)) + ((44 * -69) - -32)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 143, "answer": -2933}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((57 * ((-48 + -68) + -65)) + (16 + -55)) * 83", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 144, "answer": -859548}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 75 * (((41 + 39) - -25) + ((83 + 82) + 80))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 145, "answer": 26250}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (31 // -42) // (-48 + ((27 * -93) + ((20 - 42) * -66)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 146, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -83 - (((35 + 6) + 97) - ((-67 + -18) + (16 + 20)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 147, "answer": -270}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((42 * (97 // -66)) + (29 - -85)) + (33 - (-22 - -57))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 148, "answer": 28}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-11 - (-79 - -35)) + (63 - (-67 - 61))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 149, "answer": 224}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (29 // ((52 * (-56 % 69)) + 60)) // (45 - -89)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 150, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -88 - ((97 - (59 * 64)) + (28 + 61))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 151, "answer": 3502}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-37 - 76) + 4) + (((77 + -84) // -59) - (7 % 24))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 152, "answer": -116}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (56 + -63) + (((3 + -66) // 95) - (32 + 44))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 153, "answer": -84}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (20 - (-31 - 16)) + (-63 + (-87 * -25))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 154, "answer": 2179}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-59 // ((-51 + 96) // -59)) - 28) - (28 - -21)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 155, "answer": -18}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -76 + ((((-44 + 50) // -9) - -87) - (-27 - 27))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 156, "answer": 64}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((((-72 + 11) + (-32 * 87)) + (96 - 4)) - -6) + -88", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 157, "answer": -2835}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 46 - (((42 - -26) - (-1 + (96 * 41))) - -28)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 158, "answer": 3885}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-67 + (1 + ((43 // -6) * 94))) + -63) + (55 - 31)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 159, "answer": -857}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-88 * (-64 - ((33 - 17) - -61))) + (-16 + 57)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 160, "answer": 12449}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (58 * 90) * (((82 - 45) * -23) + (-95 - -5))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 161, "answer": -4912020}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (7 - ((53 * (-32 * 68)) - (85 + -86))) + 50", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 162, "answer": 115384}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-62 // 75) - ((47 + 80) + (-51 - (13 % -19)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 163, "answer": -83}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (77 // -47) // ((((81 * -64) * 33) - -46) * 44)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 164, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((((-55 + 18) - 37) + -12) // (74 % 98)) + 85", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 165, "answer": 83}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-36 * -28) // 43) // ((-23 + 98) - -26)) * (77 + 81)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 166, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((44 + 85) // -29) // ((47 % 74) - (2 // -11))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 167, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-26 + (-11 // 14)) - ((-45 * -48) + 38)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 168, "answer": -2225}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-72 + (-37 + -87)) * (64 + -40)) * (-74 - 6)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 169, "answer": 376320}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((75 - (-98 + (5 + 68))) + (23 * 67)) - -48", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 170, "answer": 1689}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((97 // -77) - 67) + ((37 + (-55 + 7)) // -54)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 171, "answer": -69}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((92 // -25) // (-97 - -23)) % (-14 * -27)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 172, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((30 - ((-50 - -71) * -15)) - -58) - 88) // 18", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 173, "answer": 17}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-96 * (-24 % 46)) + ((57 - 64) + ((32 - -16) * -77))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 174, "answer": -5815}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-52 + ((-17 - -36) + (-33 + (-39 + 15)))) + 93", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 175, "answer": 3}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-33 % 68) - -7) % ((-84 * (20 - -21)) + -59)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 176, "answer": -3461}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((64 + (-5 * 58)) // (-43 - -65)) % 23) - -60", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 177, "answer": 72}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((((94 - 38) + 71) + (96 % -36)) // 75) - 94", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 178, "answer": -93}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (35 + ((((45 - -71) - -84) + 41) + (47 + 38))) * -61", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 179, "answer": -22021}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((75 - -47) + 84) // ((31 % 15) // -85)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 180, "answer": -206}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (17 % 45) + (44 * ((86 + -94) * (-34 - -99)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 181, "answer": -22863}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-88 * 9) + ((39 + (-82 + 21)) - (-26 - (-53 - 97)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 182, "answer": -938}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((15 // -3) + (-79 + 75)) % (68 // -10)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 183, "answer": -2}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (36 // -67) + ((-99 - (-23 * 19)) - 73)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 184, "answer": 264}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((((-36 - 18) - -11) + -60) * -29) + (86 + (-91 - 70))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 185, "answer": 2912}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-38 - (-82 // (53 + (15 * 54)))) - (-37 - 90)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 186, "answer": 90}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((39 * -44) * (-64 - 29)) + (-40 - 88)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 187, "answer": 159460}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-22 // -63) * 70) - ((-23 - -29) // (-11 * (35 * -18)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 188, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-23 * -3) // (94 + 38)) + ((-42 // -23) * (19 + -85))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 189, "answer": -66}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((0 - -37) + (-47 * -15)) + ((16 * (-76 * 38)) - 86)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 190, "answer": -45552}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -31 + (((-81 - (95 + 51)) % 86) - 72)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 191, "answer": -72}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-46 - -14) % ((-45 * (90 - -69)) - ((79 + 55) * 81))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 192, "answer": -32}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (42 // ((-2 - 20) - 37)) // (-21 + -33)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 193, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((85 * 21) + (-47 + -5)) * -19) - (-88 + 45)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 194, "answer": -32884}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-33 - 42) % ((28 % 41) + (-34 * 96))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 195, "answer": -75}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((88 * -9) + (-64 + 85)) - (-52 + 39)) * 65", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 196, "answer": -49270}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-80 % ((96 - (6 * -64)) + 62)) - -40", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 197, "answer": 502}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-44 - 30) + ((-84 + 59) * (69 * 25))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 198, "answer": -43199}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 37 % ((-95 - ((-95 + 29) * 79)) + 73)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 199, "answer": 37}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-75 + 35) - ((-50 - 59) - ((-31 // 2) - -79))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 200, "answer": 132}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((79 + -42) - (76 % -79)) + (-76 + (-2 // -3))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 201, "answer": -36}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (64 - (80 - (-78 + 28))) + ((45 // -75) % (-41 - -45))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 202, "answer": -63}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-80 // 76) * (40 * 45)) // 69) + (-54 - (-95 * -46))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 203, "answer": -4477}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-80 + -23) + ((46 // 74) + (((94 - 90) * -64) - 77))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 204, "answer": -436}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 29 + (((-74 - (-40 * -80)) + ((99 + -16) - -92)) - 63)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 205, "answer": -3133}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-8 * 42) - (11 + -52)) - ((98 + 59) + -24)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 206, "answer": -428}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -78 // ((-2 - (90 - 0)) * (-7 + -72))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 207, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -21 + (((-73 * -66) - (-52 + 11)) + 15)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 208, "answer": 4853}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-93 - (-9 + (53 % 54))) - -16) + ((-25 * 6) - 0)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 209, "answer": -271}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((76 + -2) - (-64 + (-22 - -31))) + 27", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 210, "answer": 156}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -57 * (((-23 + 24) + (-7 - -35)) - -36)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 211, "answer": -3705}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((18 + (-65 * -22)) + -98) - (-14 + 59)) + (-15 * 13)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 212, "answer": 1110}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-23 + (55 // 78)) - -48) * ((-54 * 2) // -18)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 213, "answer": 150}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-16 - (-28 * 1)) * -6) // (45 + -48)) - 52", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 214, "answer": -28}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (87 * 19) + ((-25 - 78) + (5 * ((63 - -22) - -38)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 215, "answer": 2165}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-3 + -81) % ((50 + 3) + (40 // -90))) - -7", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 216, "answer": 27}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-72 - (69 - ((66 + 57) * -88))) * (93 - -15)) + 11", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 217, "answer": -1184209}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -74 * ((31 % (15 % -4)) + (19 - 98))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 218, "answer": 5846}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-93 + 24) - (-24 + (-78 + -70))) * (-10 * (-12 // 17))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 219, "answer": 1030}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-75 - 13) - (-18 - -82)) % -23) + -88", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 220, "answer": -102}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -94 // ((74 - (90 // -37)) // ((42 * (-15 - 44)) - 10))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 221, "answer": 94}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (62 - -52) - ((2 + -92) + (16 // (0 - -98)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 222, "answer": 204}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-28 - 93) + (48 + (38 // (-6 * ((18 * -70) + -32))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 223, "answer": -73}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((((57 % 1) + 51) // -70) // ((18 - 59) + -55)) - 73", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 224, "answer": -73}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((73 - (-19 - -69)) % (-21 - (-53 + (78 - -63)))) + 31", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 225, "answer": -55}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((48 + (9 - -52)) * 25) + (43 % (-52 - -19))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 226, "answer": 2702}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-8 - (25 - (-50 + (44 + 30)))) - (5 * 76)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 227, "answer": -389}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-57 + -78) - 45) * -92) + (-25 + (-29 + -42))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 228, "answer": 16464}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (18 - (41 * 31)) // (47 - (-31 * ((95 - 85) // 13)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 229, "answer": -27}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-73 + 89) + ((-91 + 16) // ((-77 + 13) - (99 + -39)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 230, "answer": 16}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((58 + -64) - -47) + (-84 // 46)) - -10", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 231, "answer": 49}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-17 + (-25 + 47)) - ((-65 % (-84 % -29)) % (80 + -66))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 232, "answer": 4}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-36 // 95) * (((-63 - 48) - 62) - -31)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 233, "answer": 142}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-80 + 63) + (4 + 32)) % (((17 * 25) + -16) * 49)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 234, "answer": 19}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 88 + ((((37 + 2) * -44) - 10) // -45)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 235, "answer": 126}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-13 * 41) // 48) - (45 - ((75 % 96) * -87))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 236, "answer": -6582}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 61 * ((-68 + (13 - (-99 // 10))) // -48)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 237, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-59 * -29) - (68 + (((-4 + 71) - 67) - (-86 - 2)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 238, "answer": 1555}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (10 + (81 % -75)) - (-45 * ((-66 % 52) // (33 - 75)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 239, "answer": -104}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -97 * ((9 // (23 * -81)) * (-1 + (88 - -73)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 240, "answer": 15520}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-64 * -2) * 99) + (65 * (-82 - 36))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 241, "answer": 5002}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 57 - (((-10 - 85) - (61 - (6 + (-44 + -77)))) * -74)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 242, "answer": -19997}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 51 + (((-19 - -64) - (-29 + 66)) + -78)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 243, "answer": -19}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((69 * (-47 - 33)) - (92 - 1)) - -24", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 244, "answer": -5587}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -38 - (((-38 // 28) - (36 - -96)) - ((-66 + 0) - 46))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 245, "answer": -16}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (96 - (98 - -81)) * (51 * (-96 * (-44 - -89)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 246, "answer": 18286560}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((9 % 80) + 3) + -78) - (-28 + -78)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 247, "answer": 40}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 31 - ((38 // -16) // ((-20 + 79) + (87 // -38)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 248, "answer": 32}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (12 + -70) + ((-20 - 71) + (-69 + -96))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 249, "answer": -314}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-58 * 28) - (((-4 - -67) + 92) + ((98 - -92) * -14))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 250, "answer": 881}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-32 + (28 + 17)) * (((28 * 46) + -57) - -5)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 251, "answer": 16068}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (47 - (-41 + 90)) - (-88 % (-37 + -88))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 252, "answer": 86}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-54 * -90) - 42) - (((-17 + -36) - 7) % 85)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 253, "answer": 4793}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (47 // (-69 * 29)) - ((-54 + (33 + -88)) - 3)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 254, "answer": 111}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-16 // -77) - (-97 // -5)) * (-25 + 45)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 255, "answer": -380}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-5 + 52) * ((88 * 40) - 95)) + -37) - -61", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 256, "answer": 160999}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-40 + ((-14 - -99) - 95)) // (89 * 87)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 257, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -47 - (((26 + -84) - (83 + (-76 + -88))) - -40)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 258, "answer": -110}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((92 + -78) - 49) - -75) * ((64 % (-80 - 52)) + 46)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 259, "answer": -880}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-39 - (-33 - -19)) * 1) % (-18 * 16)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 260, "answer": -25}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-48 + -65) + (-60 + (-57 - ((-19 + 5) * -69)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 261, "answer": -1196}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (16 // (19 + -32)) + (-76 - (76 + ((-44 + -16) + -62)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 262, "answer": -32}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (2 - 32) - (74 + ((-55 + -92) * 4))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 263, "answer": 484}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((19 // -73) + (-68 - (-84 - -43))) * (-49 + 3)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 264, "answer": 1288}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (50 - ((-94 - (-49 % 66)) * (-67 - -76))) + -15", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 265, "answer": 1034}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 19 + (-56 * (((28 - -92) % -2) + 75))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 266, "answer": -4181}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-45 - -52) - (((-61 + -91) - 58) - (66 * -24))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 267, "answer": -1367}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-77 * -28) // -1) + -64) % ((65 - 35) + -36)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 268, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-2 - (((40 // 25) - -11) // 45)) + (0 - -30)) * -53", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 269, "answer": -1484}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-92 * (-85 + 21)) + ((-59 * -74) * -36)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 270, "answer": -151288}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (37 + 89) + (96 - ((-9 + -55) // (-39 + (89 - 79))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 271, "answer": 220}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (81 - (((45 - -51) - 27) - 39)) - (-55 // 26)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 272, "answer": 54}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -85 + ((-94 % 35) // ((-15 // 58) + -48))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 273, "answer": -86}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-17 - (-94 * -62)) * (99 // (35 // -6))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 274, "answer": 99365}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-13 * -22) + -17) + (-59 - (64 + 25))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 275, "answer": 121}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (82 - (-42 * 71)) // ((-21 % 88) + ((-54 - 87) * -99))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 276, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-53 - (57 // -43)) - 64) * 45) - (28 - (-15 + 91))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 277, "answer": -5127}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-18 + -57) + ((82 + (15 - -97)) + -32)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 278, "answer": 87}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-10 % -34) + (85 - (-87 % (13 - 88)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 279, "answer": 87}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (27 - -3) - (((23 - 48) + 67) + (-58 - 16))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 280, "answer": 62}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -24 - (-18 * ((-81 - -12) + (-3 + -58)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 281, "answer": -2364}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 41 + (-13 + ((((11 % (56 + 12)) + -59) * -86) % -74))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 282, "answer": 12}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (5 + 79) - (((-39 + -75) + -87) + (47 * 41))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 283, "answer": -1642}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-7 % -99) - ((-24 + ((-75 * -93) - -47)) - -56)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 284, "answer": -7061}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (22 + (-21 - 2)) - (((-76 // 65) + (-52 - -5)) - -2)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 285, "answer": 46}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-88 * -32) - (((-42 * -31) + (-61 * 93)) - 79)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 286, "answer": 7266}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -78 + ((((42 + -84) + 0) - ((47 * -39) + 22)) + -23)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 287, "answer": 1668}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((29 % (-69 + 94)) * 15) - (-57 % -45)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 288, "answer": 72}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (9 + -79) + (((61 - -62) - 53) // -33)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 289, "answer": -73}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-77 - ((((-29 - 34) + 18) + -96) * 80)) - 60", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 290, "answer": 11143}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((7 * (-62 - (-72 - 45))) // -74) + ((6 % -32) * -1)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 291, "answer": 20}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-55 * -29) - 4) + -63) - (((2 // -15) + 77) // -39)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 292, "answer": 1530}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-94 - -13) // (-20 - -28)) - (79 - 76)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 293, "answer": -14}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-23 + 91) - ((-31 - 87) * (55 + 66))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 294, "answer": 14346}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-45 * 5) + (((-85 + 32) + -59) * -83)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 295, "answer": 9071}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((35 % (-55 + (-48 + -85))) * -36) - -91) + 17", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 296, "answer": 5616}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-29 * (19 - 30)) + ((75 - -92) + -38)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 297, "answer": 448}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((22 + 51) - 42) * -10) + ((-33 + 92) + 77)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 298, "answer": -174}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-1 + (-58 % 47)) - (-43 - (74 * -47))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 299, "answer": -3400}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((97 + (22 + -66)) - 66) - (54 * -97)) - -42", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 300, "answer": 5267}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-3 + -10) % 18) + (-44 * 20)) - (74 % 34)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 301, "answer": -881}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-98 * (44 - 66)) * 53) // (((76 - -72) + 24) - -83)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 302, "answer": 448}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-33 + 68) - 83) // (((-61 - 33) - 96) - -38)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 303, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((((85 + -93) + 68) + 28) // -24) - -33", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 304, "answer": 29}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((50 + 82) // (-12 * 86)) + (76 // (72 // -8))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 305, "answer": -10}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (69 - (-24 * -75)) + ((90 * ((75 // -14) * 68)) - -77)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 306, "answer": -38374}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (91 % (8 - -15)) + ((50 // -24) + 19)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 307, "answer": 38}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (63 * (21 * (29 + -69))) - (36 + -23)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 308, "answer": -52933}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -61 + ((-12 // 5) - (((-19 * 84) - -53) - -79))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 309, "answer": 1400}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-19 * (-98 - 16)) + ((95 // 99) * (48 - 96))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 310, "answer": 2166}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-66 + ((4 - 10) + 23)) % (-98 * -90)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 311, "answer": 8771}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-96 + -17) - (((74 - -98) - (-42 + (-20 * -66))) * -73)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 312, "answer": -80851}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-83 - (-23 + -25)) - (87 * 34)) * (12 + 76)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 313, "answer": -263384}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((93 + -51) * -57) - ((-41 + -42) % 87)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 314, "answer": -2398}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (51 + 30) % (-68 // ((-3 + 64) + -34))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 315, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (53 // (70 * (68 - (-87 - 77)))) - (7 - (-2 - -68))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 316, "answer": 59}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-47 * 78) + 76) - (-22 + ((70 - 34) * (60 - 56)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 317, "answer": -3712}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-73 - 31) - ((-27 - (-72 - ((56 - -48) + -32))) - 34)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 318, "answer": -187}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-58 * -89) * 41) - ((77 + 24) * -15)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 319, "answer": 213157}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -96 * (-71 * (((-76 + 31) + -80) - 86))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 320, "answer": -1438176}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -34 + (((-24 * -32) + ((-74 - -55) + (-25 - -7))) - 74)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 321, "answer": 623}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-75 - (-97 + -64)) * 70) - (-15 // (13 % 60))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 322, "answer": 6022}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-4 - ((-70 - (3 - 17)) + (-1 * 77))) // 23", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 323, "answer": 5}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-66 - 79) - ((-59 - (7 - 52)) + 24)) - 46", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 324, "answer": -201}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (57 * ((57 + -92) + 76)) // ((24 - (-71 + 6)) + 13)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 325, "answer": 22}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -33 * ((81 - (72 + -13)) // (24 + -11))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 326, "answer": -33}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((43 + (-97 - (30 - 21))) * (-57 + -80)) - (-17 - -38)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 327, "answer": 8610}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (30 * (41 * 65)) * ((-39 + -79) + (14 - 47))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 328, "answer": -12072450}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 28 + (((28 - 91) + (-73 % 4)) + (-90 + 43))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 329, "answer": -79}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -76 * (((68 // (-12 + -6)) + (-42 + 17)) - (44 * 97))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 330, "answer": 326572}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((((-70 + -75) - 95) + 69) + -43) - (-12 + (63 // -25))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 331, "answer": -199}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-88 - (27 - -64)) + (-72 // -34)) - (-51 % (1 - -44))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 332, "answer": -216}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-72 // 94) % ((63 + (98 - (18 + 69))) * 51)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 333, "answer": 3773}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-98 + 36) - (42 % ((((78 - 49) + -55) - 88) - -67))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 334, "answer": -57}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((8 - 56) + 78) + 96) + (-29 + 2)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 335, "answer": 99}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-64 // 6) - 55) * (((83 - 89) + 42) // 62)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 336, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (60 + 83) - ((73 * -66) + (29 - 39))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 337, "answer": 4971}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((95 + (44 - 23)) * ((9 % -96) // 34)) - (-93 - -2)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 338, "answer": -257}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 72 * (-48 - ((-26 - 75) + (-62 - -84)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 339, "answer": 2232}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((93 + (-8 - 16)) + (58 + (91 + (-39 * 31)))) + 79", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 340, "answer": -912}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-2 // (((42 * -86) + (91 - -35)) // -48)) // 59", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 341, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (94 + 51) + ((-24 - 15) + (75 * (-52 % -55)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 342, "answer": -3794}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-3 - (10 - ((-66 - -58) // 50))) * ((-15 + 20) - 82)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 343, "answer": 1078}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -60 - ((99 * (26 - 47)) + (-81 % 82))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 344, "answer": 2018}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((34 + -82) - (7 - (-76 * -10))) - (-45 * 70)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 345, "answer": 3855}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-44 // 93) - 59) + (((-70 + 72) * -11) * 15)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 346, "answer": -390}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((75 // -17) % ((-1 // -34) + 39)) + 86", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 347, "answer": 120}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 33 - (((-88 + -24) + 67) + (-17 - (-75 // -57)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 348, "answer": 96}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (61 * (-46 // (76 + (-73 - -47)))) - ((92 - 76) % -60)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 349, "answer": -17}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-77 % -81) * -86) - -54) // (43 + -81)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 350, "answer": -176}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((5 - 0) * ((((-19 + -95) + 0) - 73) - -69)) // 37", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 351, "answer": -16}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (94 // ((80 * (-8 + 29)) + -72)) * -25", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 352, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-27 * (-2 - 2)) - (22 - (37 * (-65 - (40 + -24))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 353, "answer": -2911}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (74 - 87) + ((42 - (-68 * -89)) * (47 * (38 + 41)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 354, "answer": -22315143}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (92 + (-45 + 6)) * (-58 - (-43 - 58))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 355, "answer": 2279}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-53 - 72) % (93 - (((-25 - 72) - -82) // -35))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 356, "answer": 61}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-15 - -8) * (72 + (-74 * (59 + -82)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 357, "answer": -12418}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-15 + 58) + 69) // ((45 // 46) + -6)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 358, "answer": -19}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-98 * ((-43 + 83) - 90)) + ((-7 - -65) + 74)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 359, "answer": 5032}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((15 + -8) + 99) * (((-55 - 66) // 56) * (-28 // -64))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 360, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (88 - 61) - (87 + (-95 - ((49 // (97 + 52)) * -45)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 361, "answer": 35}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-6 - 1) // -42) - (-65 - 19)) % 29", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 362, "answer": 26}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 2 // ((70 - (58 + 76)) + (94 // (15 * (-54 + 45))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 363, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-8 + -89) + (95 * ((-83 // -32) * -5))) * (-89 % 72)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 364, "answer": -57585}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((17 + -88) * -89) // (-73 + 81)) + 34", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 365, "answer": 823}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-3 * 68) - -3) - ((33 + -35) + (-42 + 33))) + 4", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 366, "answer": -186}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((55 - -98) + 29) // (13 + (-41 * (32 + 65)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 367, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-52 // -59) + ((70 - (7 * -15)) + (24 // 73))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 368, "answer": 175}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (52 + (66 * (-94 + -37))) // (-67 % (-65 - 62))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 369, "answer": 128}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 47 // ((-57 - -33) + ((54 + 45) + (85 - (-78 * -44))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 370, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-43 * 6) // (50 * 97)) - -53) - (-57 - 86)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 371, "answer": 195}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-41 + -3) - -1) - ((-95 * -48) - ((56 - -75) // -54))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 372, "answer": -4606}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (37 + ((-76 - (69 - -66)) * 55)) + (99 - 74)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 373, "answer": -11543}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-88 - 79) - 36) - 10) - (24 * ((51 % 90) - 95))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 374, "answer": 843}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (9 - (-34 + ((-78 - -27) + 54))) + ((-51 - -98) + 82)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 375, "answer": 169}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (48 - ((34 - (-3 + (77 % (5 + -7)))) + -72)) + -60", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 376, "answer": 22}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((((45 + -6) - 57) + (75 + 2)) + 94) + -47", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 377, "answer": 106}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-5 * ((-21 + 48) - -11)) - 99) + (89 - -64)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 378, "answer": -136}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 92 - ((80 // -58) - (-45 + (((41 - 58) + 79) - 76)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 379, "answer": 35}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -58 - (((-76 - (21 // 54)) * 12) + (-83 + (-43 % -5)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 380, "answer": 940}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (86 * ((58 - 68) // (83 - 53))) - -85", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 381, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-48 + 69) % (-50 * -91)) + (58 * -56)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 382, "answer": -3227}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -7 + ((-59 - -77) * (((72 + 2) + 4) - (33 + -96)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 383, "answer": 2531}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-76 - (((-29 - -42) - 56) + (17 - 4))) + (-33 * -55)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 384, "answer": 1769}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (44 * (29 // ((-70 + 32) - -34))) - (78 * 14)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 385, "answer": -1444}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((94 - ((75 - 18) + 51)) // -92) // (-70 - -33)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 386, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((74 + (-19 * 6)) // -9) - (80 + -32)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 387, "answer": -44}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (3 + (-80 + 42)) - (22 + (-9 - -44))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 388, "answer": -92}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (92 + (28 - 89)) - ((89 + -38) * ((-41 - -48) - -36))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 389, "answer": -2162}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-72 * (-79 // 74)) * (((96 * (24 - -4)) + 59) + -19)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 390, "answer": 392832}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((96 - 31) * -28) // (-43 * 93)) - (-86 // 35)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 391, "answer": 3}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((29 - (1 + 76)) - 99) * (18 * (79 - 33))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 392, "answer": -121716}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-96 + (-2 - 49)) - (-16 // ((-52 - 41) + -32))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 393, "answer": -147}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-6 + -52) + 28) - ((8 - 80) - 93)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 394, "answer": 135}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((16 + -53) - 47) - (48 - (-74 * (-39 + 43)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 395, "answer": -428}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-62 - (22 % (-54 + 8))) - ((62 * 33) + 37)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 396, "answer": -2121}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-35 + 44) - 46) - (2 + (77 + (-84 - (-34 % 22))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 397, "answer": -22}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 16 + ((((-7 + 44) + 43) + ((-94 * 6) - -68)) // -10)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 398, "answer": 57}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-27 % -9) - ((99 + 89) // 15)) + (-2 % (19 * 62))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 399, "answer": 1164}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (8 % 62) - (((-79 - -58) - -12) - -41)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 400, "answer": -24}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((55 + 66) - 2) - ((-7 - 92) // (6 * -57))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 401, "answer": 119}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -67 - ((91 + 80) + (-46 + (2 + -73)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 402, "answer": -121}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 22 - (-93 - ((-73 + -32) - (-78 % 68)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 403, "answer": -48}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-36 - (14 + 61)) % (-66 - (-92 - (70 - -8)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 404, "answer": 97}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((41 // 14) - (79 - 39)) - (52 + (62 - 92))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 405, "answer": -60}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((((24 + 39) - -41) - -77) + 14) * ((6 % -33) // -60)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 406, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -99 * (((-26 - 21) * (77 + (94 // 23))) + -23)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 407, "answer": 379170}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-98 + 41) // (-51 // 6)) - (2 + -36)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 408, "answer": 40}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-32 % -79) // (61 - -38)) - (-27 - 67)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 409, "answer": 93}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-82 + -53) + -65) - (-71 * 64)) - ((-30 - 80) - 60)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 410, "answer": 4514}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-95 // -61) - (37 * (-52 * (-27 - (-67 % 84))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 411, "answer": -84655}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-40 - (-61 // (27 + (-12 + (-20 % 28))))) // -4", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 412, "answer": 9}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-15 - (93 - (-85 // ((-81 // 40) + 21)))) - -53", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 413, "answer": -60}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-68 // 97) + 83) * (-1 * (-36 - 89))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 414, "answer": 10250}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (89 * 98) * (34 - (22 + (75 + -20)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 415, "answer": -375046}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (91 + 41) * (-35 % ((-49 + -7) + (71 % -44)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 416, "answer": -4620}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-16 * -96) // (-29 * (2 + (-97 + -89)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 417, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((((-4 + (-36 * -59)) * 28) - (76 * 59)) * -13) // 95", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 418, "answer": -7510}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -84 + ((80 + (-67 - 25)) - (-18 - ((88 - -50) + -94)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 419, "answer": -34}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-35 - -89) * (81 + 13)) - (((-51 % 46) + -52) % 40)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 420, "answer": 5047}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((54 + 42) + -58) + (36 * (16 * (-32 - 39)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 421, "answer": -40858}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (99 + ((-95 + 59) - -6)) * (-17 + (69 + 38))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 422, "answer": 6210}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (97 // 42) + ((-17 - 5) - ((-75 // 34) + 69))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 423, "answer": -86}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -66 - ((-48 - -72) - ((-74 % -91) - 47))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 424, "answer": -211}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((((-87 + -6) // -43) - 56) - (-96 - (68 - 26))) + -79", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 425, "answer": 5}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-7 * (((58 * -31) * (88 + -81)) * -22)) - -80", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 426, "answer": -1938164}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-74 + ((37 + (-51 - -50)) * 35)) - 69", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 427, "answer": 1117}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((92 + -72) + ((80 + 71) - 10)) * -73", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 428, "answer": -11753}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (30 + -13) + ((37 - (-9 + -19)) + 41)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 429, "answer": 123}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((86 * -17) + 56) * (45 + (-3 + (-7 // 16)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 430, "answer": -57646}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (86 - (-27 + (33 + -65))) + ((-23 + -43) // -45)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 431, "answer": 146}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 98 % ((-75 // (18 * -8)) - (-64 // (-6 - 50)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 432, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-23 + -76) - (((88 * -80) - 86) - -16)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 433, "answer": 7011}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (77 * 80) % (53 - (((88 + 48) + -2) * -79))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 434, "answer": 6160}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((7 * -69) % 98) + (92 + (63 * 62))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 435, "answer": 4005}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -21 - ((-18 - ((-16 - (-60 * -87)) + 73)) % 88)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 436, "answer": -62}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-43 - (-25 - 1)) + -62) + (-13 - (22 - 47))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 437, "answer": -67}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 41 - (((3 * 29) * (99 - 79)) - (96 + (24 // 44)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 438, "answer": -1603}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((44 // 58) * (-37 + -81)) + (99 - 11)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 439, "answer": 88}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-71 + (((-6 + -10) - -51) * -17)) - -11) - 53", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 440, "answer": -708}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 98 + ((-10 + (60 * -62)) + ((-40 // -48) - (-60 + 94)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 441, "answer": -3666}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-71 - (-37 - ((-96 - -12) + (-21 // (21 + -94))))) + -15", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 442, "answer": -133}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((40 + 34) - ((60 - 87) - -63)) - 78", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 443, "answer": -40}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-3 - (-34 % (-84 - ((79 - 59) + -30)))) + (20 * 68)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 444, "answer": 1391}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 0 + (((-95 * -25) * 67) % (-40 - -2))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 445, "answer": -19}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-19 + (((-52 * (29 + 18)) * 44) + 83)) + (-89 + -36)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 446, "answer": -107597}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((1 * 91) - -59) - (-11 + (((61 - -22) - -39) + 29))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 447, "answer": 10}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 61 * (((43 % -28) // -42) * (-12 // (69 + -64)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 448, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((7 - (47 - -60)) + 10) + (55 + -15)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 449, "answer": -50}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((68 + -64) - (-64 * (77 - 81))) % (11 + 98)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 450, "answer": 75}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-82 // 43) - (-52 % (-62 * 87))) % -92", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 451, "answer": -42}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((14 + 91) + (-61 - -51)) - (-66 + (-93 + 96))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 452, "answer": 158}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((53 - (-40 * 76)) * (-8 + -79)) * ((29 - 55) - 21)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 453, "answer": 12647277}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((0 - (22 + -64)) - (-50 + (-91 // 5))) * (-30 // 6)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 454, "answer": -555}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-83 + -54) - ((77 + -16) - (-36 + 10))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 455, "answer": -224}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 56 * ((((57 + 91) % 47) - 53) - (34 + -72))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 456, "answer": -448}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-37 * ((43 + 0) + 33)) - (-51 - (13 - 2))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 457, "answer": -2750}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((9 + -24) + 57) // (77 + (19 + (-76 - 85)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 458, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -53 % (((6 % -17) + ((-54 * 17) // 52)) + (17 % -76))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 459, "answer": -53}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (84 * (-76 % -70)) - (((-78 % 35) - 82) + -1)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 460, "answer": -448}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((41 - -2) % (97 - (-14 + 45))) * (-58 + -62)) // -54", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 461, "answer": 95}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 8 - (((-26 // 61) % -53) + (-66 * (-99 % (-96 - 18))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 462, "answer": -6525}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((56 + (-39 * -44)) - 51) - ((5 - 14) + -79)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 463, "answer": 1809}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-37 + (((-87 * -52) - -62) + -85)) + ((-62 - -91) // 71)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 464, "answer": 4464}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((((-87 - -72) + 7) // (-58 + 73)) + (57 * 70)) - 78", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 465, "answer": 3911}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((92 + 49) + ((-76 - 97) - -23)) // ((-2 + -82) - 95)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 466, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-25 - ((-68 % 78) * (-15 + 35))) * (35 - -46)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 467, "answer": -18225}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-72 // 47) - ((24 * (((56 % -18) - -33) - 35)) + 48)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 468, "answer": 382}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (58 - (34 - 87)) - (((57 + -40) // (-50 + -99)) + -69)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 469, "answer": 181}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((89 + (58 + 7)) + 6) // (-14 + -10)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 470, "answer": -7}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((64 + -48) - (((-82 % -21) - -23) - 30)) - 41) * -17", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 471, "answer": -17}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 76 // (((22 - -90) * 66) - (24 - -60))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 472, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((6 + 91) - -85) + 34) + ((43 + 38) + (-46 // 48))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 473, "answer": 296}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-61 + -28) // -92) + (((47 - 56) - 0) // (53 * -70))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 474, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-30 * (-77 * 28)) // (-4 + (-22 - -44))) - 35", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 475, "answer": 3558}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-4 + -90) + ((14 - 30) * (24 + (-51 + -12)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 476, "answer": 530}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((((97 - -74) - 33) % (-47 + 86)) + -90) + 18", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 477, "answer": -51}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-98 * ((76 + 53) + (-14 + 20))) % -88) + -73", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 478, "answer": -103}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((48 * (64 - -46)) + ((-50 // -26) - -29)) + 37) * -18", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 479, "answer": -96246}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-30 * ((-29 * -70) // (60 - (-47 + 39)))) % -10", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 480, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((81 * -27) - 47) * ((-81 - -20) - ((-87 - -66) + -92))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 481, "answer": -116168}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-72 + ((-77 - ((-54 + 81) * 53)) % 52)) + 62", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 482, "answer": -10}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((((-14 - -49) + 83) * 95) + (94 * 96)) - (46 - -66)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 483, "answer": 20122}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (17 * ((21 - -40) // -42)) * (58 * -33)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 484, "answer": 65076}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (80 * ((17 - 25) // -92)) + (22 // (-10 * 23))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 485, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (97 * -10) // ((4 + 83) % (-16 - (-22 - 37)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 486, "answer": -970}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((59 * -37) * 41) - -59) - ((-83 % -12) - -46)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 487, "answer": -89479}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((40 + 78) * (-55 * 70)) - 72) + (90 // (-70 + 52))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 488, "answer": -454377}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((14 * -54) - (4 % -82)) - ((76 * (-16 + 27)) * 66)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 489, "answer": -55854}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -76 * ((49 % 94) + (94 // (70 * (16 - (0 + 58)))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 490, "answer": -3648}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-47 + ((46 - 74) - -22)) + ((-77 // 50) + (57 + 31))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 491, "answer": 33}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-84 // -5) - (-99 - (((-27 * -92) * -39) + 11))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 492, "answer": -96750}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((((4 * -2) // 12) + 40) * -45) + (22 - (-51 + 43))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 493, "answer": -1725}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-26 + 72) - -67) - (-97 * (66 - (-63 - 85)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 494, "answer": 20871}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-78 + (65 * (17 + 79))) * (60 - -53)) + 17", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 495, "answer": 696323}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-9 + -42) - -52) % 9) + ((48 * (88 - -39)) - 83)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 496, "answer": 6014}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-91 - -90) * 46) % ((((49 + 24) + 77) + -79) - -63)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 497, "answer": 88}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((((34 + 57) - -77) % (21 + 62)) + 90) * (76 - 63)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 498, "answer": 1196}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-12 - (21 * 17)) - (47 - 88)) + (8 + -9)) - -24", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 499, "answer": -305}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (78 + 53) + (((62 + 22) - 49) - (47 % -86))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 500, "answer": 205}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-26 % (-78 + -67)) - (-28 - ((58 + -28) - (-34 + -96)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 501, "answer": 162}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 55 - ((69 + 15) * ((-33 % (25 + -53)) * (-12 + -78)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 502, "answer": -37745}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((93 + 6) // ((70 + 13) - 86)) % 64", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 503, "answer": 31}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-86 + 65) // ((-86 + -57) * (3 % 22))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 504, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-2 - (22 + -32)) * -62) + ((-26 * 15) - -2)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 505, "answer": -884}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-75 + (11 - 57)) + (((-31 - -74) % -34) // (19 - 98))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 506, "answer": -121}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((34 * -13) - ((-19 + (73 % -97)) + -82)) * (6 + -74)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 507, "answer": 21556}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 76 - (((86 // -27) + (-50 - -91)) + (59 * (-85 - 53)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 508, "answer": 8181}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((82 - -69) + (55 + (-3 * (-71 + (-35 - -24))))) // 20", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 509, "answer": 22}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 64 + (((78 * 71) + (-34 + -58)) + (-29 + (-2 + 0)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 510, "answer": 5479}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -33 % ((13 * (26 - -48)) + ((66 - 26) * -72))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 511, "answer": -33}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((58 * (14 * (-73 // -91))) // -81) - -81", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 512, "answer": 81}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((28 + -61) - 68) - (-90 * (-31 * -61))) - (1 + 48)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 513, "answer": 170040}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((4 // 87) - (39 - -42)) + -99) - -1", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 514, "answer": -179}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((46 * ((75 // -22) - 3)) + (62 - (-6 - 37))) * -12", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 515, "answer": 2604}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-54 - 42) - (-1 - 70)) + (-23 // 79)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 516, "answer": -26}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 62 - (((62 * 13) + 89) + (-64 + (-50 - -93)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 517, "answer": -812}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((0 + -83) + ((37 - 16) // -95)) - (-13 - (-13 * 85))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 518, "answer": -1176}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-45 + ((90 + 49) + -40)) + (-90 + 89)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 519, "answer": 53}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((21 // (-37 - 80)) * 67) + (-96 * -55)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 520, "answer": 5213}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -21 - (17 - (((-72 + -70) - ((-83 + -48) + 10)) - -13))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 521, "answer": -46}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((76 * 48) + (-17 * -45)) % (52 // -55)) - (-83 + -69)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 522, "answer": 152}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-56 - 79) - ((13 // (49 // -89)) - (-74 + 62))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 523, "answer": -134}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-95 // ((-98 - -98) + -54)) * (81 // ((78 * 98) // 22))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 524, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-63 - 64) + (((-38 - -55) + 57) * (53 + (84 * 28)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 525, "answer": 177843}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 61 + (((-98 + 43) + -39) - (-69 * (59 * (95 + 39))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 526, "answer": 545481}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (98 + 61) + ((-86 + -50) - (-61 + ((-54 + -59) // 72)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 527, "answer": 86}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 66 + (((12 + -35) - -14) + (-88 - -73))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 528, "answer": 42}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 38 - ((-92 - 25) - (-81 - (85 % ((8 + -49) + 92))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 529, "answer": 40}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-71 - (-41 - -74)) - ((-48 * -3) - (-81 + (50 * 25)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 530, "answer": 921}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-44 - ((0 // -4) - -65)) - (85 + -50)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 531, "answer": -144}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-14 + -67) - -91) // (-28 - (-71 + ((8 + -56) * 95)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 532, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (55 + -59) + ((-77 - 6) * ((52 - 22) + 19))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 533, "answer": -4071}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 87 + (((-36 - (12 - 49)) - -43) + (47 * -98))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 534, "answer": -4475}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -89 - (((9 - (23 * 79)) // -74) // (27 * -38))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 535, "answer": -88}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (78 + (((-66 - -8) * -24) - -38)) // 66", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 536, "answer": 22}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 23 * ((81 - (47 // 92)) - (17 + 19))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 537, "answer": 1035}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-5 + ((61 // -81) + -1)) - (36 // -91)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 538, "answer": -6}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((76 - -79) + (89 % -85)) - ((-71 - -1) + -6)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 539, "answer": 150}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-6 - ((66 * 44) % (44 - 82))) + (-64 + -14)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 540, "answer": -62}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (67 - ((93 - 91) + (-17 - -9))) - -31", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 541, "answer": 104}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-83 * -4) * (16 - 25)) + (21 + 82)) - (16 - 59)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 542, "answer": -2842}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-51 + ((-79 * ((-26 + -80) * -72)) - -57)) * -29", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 543, "answer": 17484738}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-61 - -47) - ((-24 * (75 * 39)) * -66)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 544, "answer": -4633214}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((89 + 66) * -94) + ((-83 - -94) + (34 * 66))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 545, "answer": -12315}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((25 // 52) * 71) // 79) - ((-22 * 46) - -66)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 546, "answer": 946}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-41 // 24) * (((-62 - -9) - -27) - (-57 + 59))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 547, "answer": 56}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-55 + (-58 + -39)) + (-89 + -18)) + 48", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 548, "answer": -211}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-52 - -47) - (71 // -18)) + (-62 + -4)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 549, "answer": -67}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-68 * -93) - ((97 - -62) * 18)) + (-60 * -98)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 550, "answer": 9342}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-25 * 94) + 47) - (45 // 87)) + ((77 + -71) + 88)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 551, "answer": -2209}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -64 * ((-21 + (3 - (15 + (-76 * -16)))) - -85)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 552, "answer": 74496}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((97 * -28) * (-94 + (38 + (74 * 72)))) - (32 - 1)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 553, "answer": -14318783}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((71 + -7) + (-62 + 84)) + (-5 // -1)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 554, "answer": 91}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -27 // (((15 - 44) + -77) // (87 + (90 * 7)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 555, "answer": 27}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (87 // (87 + 7)) + (51 // ((52 + 94) - -3))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 556, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 5 * (((43 + 19) % 82) * (-48 + -52))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 557, "answer": -31000}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-22 // 50) % -22) + ((-42 + -93) - (-60 + -32))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 558, "answer": -44}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((68 * ((-54 + 26) - 77)) + (-92 - -69)) - 96", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 559, "answer": -7259}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (54 * ((45 + 12) + -33)) + ((-4 - 32) * 88)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 560, "answer": -1872}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -33 - ((-62 // -18) - (((-8 - (-86 - -30)) - -7) // 8))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 561, "answer": -30}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-25 * (36 % 64)) - (32 + (97 - (96 * (54 - 93))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 562, "answer": -4773}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-30 // 76) // 79) - (-75 - 37)) + 49", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 563, "answer": 160}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-64 % 33) - (((6 % -12) - -58) * (-44 * -60))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 564, "answer": -137278}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (44 + 58) + ((7 - ((-70 - -66) * (23 * -10))) // -20)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 565, "answer": 147}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (14 * (-55 - 82)) - ((91 - (-43 * -67)) + (77 + -41))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 566, "answer": 836}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-66 - -79) // (((-80 * (99 + 24)) - 94) * 11)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 567, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-91 + 69) * ((21 * (-35 + -88)) - -83)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 568, "answer": 55000}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (94 - (-68 - ((51 * (-52 // 72)) % -10))) - -92", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 569, "answer": 253}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (49 + -10) - ((29 - 87) // (30 + 46))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 570, "answer": 40}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 49 - (36 + (84 + (-27 - (94 - 38))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 571, "answer": 12}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -45 - (((13 + 73) // (-53 - -9)) // -2)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 572, "answer": -46}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (5 + -71) + ((20 // (34 // -65)) * (96 + -7))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 573, "answer": -1846}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-78 % (27 * -70)) - (((54 + 89) - (76 // 14)) % -42)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 574, "answer": -48}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-51 // -82) - (74 + -5)) // (-96 * ((2 + 13) % 34))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 575, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-69 + ((3 // 78) + (90 - (-83 + -6)))) - (-13 + -48)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 576, "answer": 171}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-40 + ((-28 + 96) + 83)) * ((-8 + 22) % 71)) % 55", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 577, "answer": 14}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((97 - 17) + -72) * -68) + ((28 + -40) + 61)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 578, "answer": -495}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -74 + (-82 * ((-54 + -2) - (-60 + -22)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 579, "answer": -2206}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (95 - (70 + ((-48 + -24) * 70))) + ((30 // -33) + 39)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 580, "answer": 5103}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (96 * (11 - (-1 + (-19 - -3)))) - (18 + -90)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 581, "answer": 2760}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (81 - -57) - ((-65 + -20) + (25 - 96))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 582, "answer": 294}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((((44 + -59) - 30) + -85) * 1) + -32", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 583, "answer": -162}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((((-17 - -84) - -92) * 52) - -88) * (-6 * -10)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 584, "answer": 501360}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (96 // (((-75 // 10) + -11) - -8)) - ((-85 % 70) // -37)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 585, "answer": -7}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (52 + -78) - ((-21 * (-13 - -56)) - -94)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 586, "answer": 783}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (18 - (46 // 32)) * (((79 // 21) + (-18 - -3)) - 47)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 587, "answer": -1003}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (26 + (77 + 73)) - (-13 - ((-57 % 58) + -23))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 588, "answer": 167}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (28 + (38 - (-26 - -32))) - (-23 - (-42 - 60))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 589, "answer": -19}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 84 * ((52 + ((-82 + 46) + (10 - -46))) + (-80 + 67))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 590, "answer": 4956}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-48 + 7) // 3) - (60 % 32)) - (72 + 96)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 591, "answer": -210}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (61 * 81) + (((-45 - 70) // ((64 + 37) - 58)) * 97)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 592, "answer": 4650}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (34 // (-6 + ((-38 * -61) + 92))) + (12 + 6)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 593, "answer": 18}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 63 + ((-31 + -26) * ((-34 * (4 // -38)) - -70))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 594, "answer": -5865}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-37 - -20) // ((44 - 12) - (66 + -90))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 595, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-65 + -92) // ((69 + 41) + (65 + -89))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 596, "answer": -2}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-85 * (-19 - (-83 - 5))) - ((2 + 86) - (-39 - -71))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 597, "answer": -5921}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((34 * (((-76 % -39) * 54) - -68)) + 98) + (-15 + 50)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 598, "answer": -65487}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((9 - (-63 - -72)) - -55) + (-29 - ((-34 // 51) - -85))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 599, "answer": -58}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-18 - (22 + 75)) // (-28 - -62)) + (22 + 84)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 600, "answer": 102}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (66 + (90 - 70)) - (77 + (-35 * (-20 + 64)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 601, "answer": 1549}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (37 + (14 + 0)) + (1 * ((-76 - 94) - (-23 * -46)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 602, "answer": -1177}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-91 * -29) + -79) * 26) // (89 - 6)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 603, "answer": 801}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-58 + ((-9 - 8) + 55)) - (17 * 78)) * -92", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 604, "answer": 123832}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (65 + -65) * (3 % (61 + (-19 - 48)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 605, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -59 + ((53 // 76) * ((16 + 23) - 89))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 606, "answer": -59}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (76 % (7 // -5)) + (1 + (47 * -42))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 607, "answer": -1973}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 43 - ((19 % -49) * ((-87 + 3) * 59))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 608, "answer": -148637}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-77 + (-56 % 46)) + (-96 - 84)) + (98 - 17)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 609, "answer": -140}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-42 // ((-66 + 11) - -47)) + ((-27 + (8 // -53)) + 5)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 610, "answer": -18}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -25 - ((59 + (-36 - -5)) - (-78 % -97))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 611, "answer": -131}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (78 + 2) - ((82 - 9) * ((-75 - 43) * -84))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 612, "answer": -723496}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (21 * (56 // 72)) + (-98 + (30 * 59))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 613, "answer": 1672}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-66 + 44) - -89) // ((-33 - (29 - 27)) // -13)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 614, "answer": 33}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-18 // 82) + ((-33 + (-19 * (-67 + 28))) + -28)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 615, "answer": 679}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-32 - 57) - 95) + (((-57 * -19) + 89) - (96 * -61))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 616, "answer": 6844}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-51 - (-86 + (-53 - -90))) + (-33 - -58)) + 81) - 20", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 617, "answer": 84}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 27 * (14 // (((27 // -71) - 85) - (-68 * -10)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 618, "answer": -27}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-53 - -56) + (((50 - -98) // 35) - 97)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 619, "answer": -90}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-80 + -36) + (((-15 * (-27 * 75)) + 75) - (1 - -4))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 620, "answer": 30329}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -17 - ((-79 % 18) + (((53 + 69) - (-15 + -88)) * 68))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 621, "answer": -15328}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-45 - -87) + (-17 + -85)) * ((41 + (-76 - 3)) // -34)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 622, "answer": -60}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-77 % -94) - (-58 - ((-27 + 66) % 93))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 623, "answer": 20}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-23 + 26) + ((((-8 + 71) * -75) - -5) - (26 + 15))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 624, "answer": -4758}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-76 - 94) * (-5 - 58)) - (12 - (-76 * -89))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 625, "answer": 17462}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((66 - 76) * 83) - ((35 + 62) - (-25 + (12 + -79)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 626, "answer": -1019}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-67 + (-36 // 34)) - ((46 - -87) * (-88 * 32))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 627, "answer": 374459}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((19 - 70) // (-9 + -34)) + 50) // -79", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 628, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -70 - (((-53 + ((-78 * 7) - 81)) - (-19 - 51)) + 86)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 629, "answer": 454}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((((-52 % -45) - -52) * -79) - (73 + -72)) + 12", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 630, "answer": -3544}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -98 - ((-96 - (68 // (18 - 78))) - ((-22 + 59) - 58))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 631, "answer": -25}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-67 // -65) - (-51 * -71)) + (79 - -51)) + -93", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 632, "answer": -3583}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((67 - (12 - 61)) * 38) + (-77 - -22)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 633, "answer": 4353}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (9 - -94) - (-57 + (90 * ((21 + -94) + 16)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 634, "answer": 5290}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-24 + 46) % ((-14 + (-73 - (7 // 27))) * (-90 - 25))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 635, "answer": 22}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((83 + -84) // 36) // -95) - ((42 // -83) - -31)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 636, "answer": -30}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((27 - 60) - (15 * 79)) * ((-58 * -26) * (21 - -11))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 637, "answer": -58775808}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (51 + 76) - (((-24 * 86) - 83) - (7 // 73))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 638, "answer": 2274}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((60 // -46) + -27) - (71 - (-66 // -55))) - (-59 + 56)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 639, "answer": -96}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 7 % (((-46 + 43) + (-95 + -8)) % (-8 + 74))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 640, "answer": 7}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-83 - -13) * ((59 * -41) * (44 - -42))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 641, "answer": 14562380}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((97 % -88) - 98) + (((77 * 32) + 55) % 72)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 642, "answer": -106}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 13 // ((-72 * (44 - (30 - -73))) + -57)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 643, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -47 + ((87 - (82 + 14)) - (((-60 + 66) + -6) - -14))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 644, "answer": -70}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -48 + (((-37 + 22) * (-26 - 30)) // -56)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 645, "answer": -63}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-7 - 62) + 71) - (-61 - (-41 + -64))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 646, "answer": -42}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((33 + 75) + (-92 + 14)) + (98 % (84 // 33))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 647, "answer": 30}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -13 + (((12 + -84) // 1) - (70 // 65))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 648, "answer": -86}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (62 + (((3 + 75) - 80) - 42)) - -22", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 649, "answer": 40}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-28 + 36) * 57) - (80 + (15 + 65))) % (40 - 60)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 650, "answer": -4}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((((99 - -49) + -22) * -78) // (38 + -14)) - (86 - 85)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 651, "answer": -411}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-45 + -76) * ((((-94 - -92) * 39) + (-38 * 99)) + -22)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 652, "answer": 467302}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((88 + (-4 // -33)) - 61) + (((-87 - 94) // 67) + -68)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 653, "answer": -44}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (17 + (-39 * 91)) - ((-10 - (-27 - 71)) - 84)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 654, "answer": -3536}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((34 - 89) * (-73 * ((-7 + 17) - -74))) + (83 + 9)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 655, "answer": 337352}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -76 + (9 + ((-45 + 15) * (-5 - (51 - 44))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 656, "answer": 293}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((63 - 9) + (77 * 26)) // ((-63 - 30) + -67)) // 25", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 657, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (81 - (78 + (17 + 22))) * (92 * (44 * (-69 + 55)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 658, "answer": 2040192}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -69 * (((34 * -60) - -69) - ((-4 + -22) * -24))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 659, "answer": 179055}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -63 % (((-88 - (24 * 47)) // (45 - 16)) + -13)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 660, "answer": -8}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((96 - (30 - 63)) - 18) - ((-61 - 87) + -16)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 661, "answer": 275}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((2 // -13) // (72 + 14)) * 89) * -28", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 662, "answer": 2492}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -57 % ((47 + ((65 * (-50 - 59)) * (46 + 34))) // -51)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 663, "answer": 11055}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-69 + ((-95 + (-47 + -37)) * 81)) + (-78 // 37)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 664, "answer": -14571}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((26 + -94) % -12) - ((7 + (36 // (-2 * -34))) * -76)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 665, "answer": 524}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 39 + ((-63 - -53) - ((-60 * -21) - 5))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 666, "answer": -1226}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (58 * -16) + ((83 + -85) * ((-74 * -18) - (6 + -17)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 667, "answer": -3614}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-86 - (-38 + (27 + 31))) * ((-31 // -84) + -18)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 668, "answer": 1908}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((24 // (5 - (-95 - -31))) + 42) + (-36 - 96)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 669, "answer": -90}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((46 + 5) - ((63 + 29) - (-63 + -4))) + (-37 - 38)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 670, "answer": -183}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-99 % ((68 + -57) - -99)) + -84) - (-30 // 54)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 671, "answer": -72}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((50 - 31) + (-88 - -58)) - (-23 + -77)) - 2", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 672, "answer": 87}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -64 * (((((57 // 30) - -18) * (63 + -33)) + 93) - 82)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 673, "answer": -37184}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (70 * (-12 // -46)) + ((-95 * 78) % (66 * -99))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 674, "answer": -876}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-97 + (6 + (96 + 1))) + ((67 - (38 - -92)) - 72)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 675, "answer": -129}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-9 - ((((-54 * 97) + 79) - -97) - -68)) + 19", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 676, "answer": 5004}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-97 + -43) - (95 + ((-50 * -76) - (84 // -43)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 677, "answer": -4037}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-28 * 27) + (-98 * -49)) * (-71 + -28)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 678, "answer": -400554}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((42 + (69 + (-83 - 51))) - -67) - (-67 % (46 // -41))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 679, "answer": 45}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((74 + (78 - 74)) - ((-99 - 10) - 65)) + (-17 - 11)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 680, "answer": 224}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (75 + (27 + -7)) - ((85 + (-87 + -28)) % 8)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 681, "answer": 93}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((1 - -50) % (-79 // 47)) + (89 + (77 * (-80 - -36)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 682, "answer": -3300}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-20 - -83) + ((-92 * (11 * -93)) + 52)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 683, "answer": 94231}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-72 - 22) + -38) // ((-14 * (-81 - 99)) * (96 * -75))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 684, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-78 * (-91 - -3)) - -19) - ((-67 + (14 + -85)) + -22)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 685, "answer": 7043}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-73 + (44 // (-24 - -2))) % (-75 + 59)) - (-40 + 54)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 686, "answer": -25}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (17 + ((10 - 59) + (-13 - 67))) - (17 - (51 + -50))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 687, "answer": -128}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -96 - (52 + (47 * (64 - (-9 + 8))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 688, "answer": -3203}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-37 + (-88 + (-67 * -20))) - 50) // 12) * 32", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 689, "answer": 3104}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-62 - 21) * -20) + (((-5 - -97) - 33) - 51)) * 69", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 690, "answer": 115092}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-39 - 30) * ((9 + ((-48 - 64) + (-82 // -12))) + -51)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 691, "answer": 10212}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((49 * 45) + -14) * 58) - ((-15 - -58) - (17 * -89))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 692, "answer": 125522}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (64 // -42) - ((60 + -45) % (24 - (90 + -3)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 693, "answer": 46}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-98 - ((-81 + -8) - -92)) - (-63 + -25)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 694, "answer": -13}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-88 % -92) // ((-27 - -55) + (-32 - (-13 - 42)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 695, "answer": -2}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-94 - -54) - ((-94 - 74) - (-2 - 68))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 696, "answer": 58}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-21 * (-38 + -5)) % ((35 // 60) - 12)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 697, "answer": -9}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -69 + ((-51 + -50) - ((((54 - 10) - 63) - -37) - -88))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 698, "answer": -276}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-61 - -16) + (-86 * (-67 + 31))) - ((87 + -79) - 21)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 699, "answer": 3064}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-57 * (((28 // 33) - 19) - -54)) - ((35 - 78) + 24)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 700, "answer": -1976}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((49 // 3) + (-46 - -43)) - (16 - (2 + (-21 + 9)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 701, "answer": -13}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-34 + 41) - (-65 * (-24 // 14))) + (-41 * 50)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 702, "answer": -2173}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((16 - 20) - 11) * 5) + (28 * -18)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 703, "answer": -579}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-54 // ((-32 // 66) + -80)) * ((-24 % 29) + 32)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 704, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-29 // ((-69 + -81) - ((40 - -48) - -14))) - (73 * -15)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 705, "answer": 1095}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((81 * 55) % -64) * (((98 + -23) % -27) + -11)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 706, "answer": 425}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((21 + (2 + -41)) - -41) + (22 - (33 - 51))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 707, "answer": 63}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((((-78 - -19) // -51) - 10) + ((13 + 16) - 43)) * -92", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 708, "answer": 2116}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-21 * 89) * (28 - (((-42 - 8) - 9) * 76))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 709, "answer": -8432928}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((((46 - -91) * -64) - (-15 - 46)) % 62) - 55", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 710, "answer": -20}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((1 - -83) - (-51 + 22)) - -72) - ((64 + -22) + -76)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 711, "answer": 219}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 73 + ((77 * 55) - ((-52 - -49) + -82))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 712, "answer": 4393}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-40 + (69 - 35)) + (17 - (-5 + (-56 + -16)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 713, "answer": 88}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-71 - (38 - (23 - 91))) + (0 // (-66 - -47))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 714, "answer": -177}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((55 - 48) + -20) + 51) // (29 - (-29 - -48))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 715, "answer": 3}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-83 - 3) + ((35 + (46 % 26)) + 18)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 716, "answer": -13}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (89 + (-26 - ((80 + 83) - -23))) // (57 % -55)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 717, "answer": 2}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (59 + 88) - (((69 + -53) + (1 + 79)) + -88)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 718, "answer": 139}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (61 + 38) % ((79 - 86) * (27 % 6))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 719, "answer": -6}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -5 - (94 * (30 + (((-57 + -35) - -46) + (19 - -93))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 720, "answer": -9029}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((91 - 3) - (2 - -90)) - (-35 + -70)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 721, "answer": 101}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (72 + 92) - (((-82 + -78) - (83 % 13)) + (21 * -28))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 722, "answer": 917}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (56 + -74) * (-24 * (37 + (-56 + -80)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 723, "answer": -42768}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (74 - ((13 - (-54 - -44)) + (73 + (14 // 79)))) * -87", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 724, "answer": 1914}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((0 * (((-86 % 54) + -98) // -87)) - (97 + -48)) - -36", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 725, "answer": -13}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-76 % -95) - ((-96 - ((75 + 72) * -83)) * -43)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 726, "answer": 520439}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-88 - 7) + ((-16 * (44 * 61)) // -51)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 727, "answer": 747}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (10 * -69) % ((-72 + -8) - ((-96 - 3) - (-96 - 0)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 728, "answer": -74}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-83 - ((-88 + -82) * -44)) + (-22 + 97)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 729, "answer": -7488}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (83 // (-35 // (54 % -16))) * (((-14 % -55) + 63) - 95)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 730, "answer": -1242}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-14 - -95) - 56) - (((29 - 51) - (-40 - -94)) + 58)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 731, "answer": 43}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (89 - (94 - -37)) + (-84 * (-4 + 28))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 732, "answer": -2058}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-3 - -47) - (-39 * (((-65 * -28) - -18) + 65))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 733, "answer": 74261}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((((-41 * 88) * -15) - -12) - -37) + -47", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 734, "answer": 54122}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 71 - ((56 + -2) + ((14 - (-83 - 26)) + (-50 - -86)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 735, "answer": -142}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-67 + -76) - ((-39 * 30) + (10 // ((-57 + 85) - -49)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 736, "answer": 1027}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (56 - (-22 - (48 + 15))) - (-30 - 24)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 737, "answer": 195}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-57 // 21) + 13) - ((95 + -60) // 24)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 738, "answer": 9}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((95 // -23) * (42 - 87)) * (-34 - -2)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 739, "answer": -7200}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-3 // 44) - 56) + ((-14 + -65) + (-49 + -60))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 740, "answer": -245}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -96 - (((7 + 2) - 91) - (-1 - 26))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 741, "answer": -41}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((5 - (-68 + ((-50 + 96) + 12))) + -34) + 98", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 742, "answer": 79}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((79 - -85) * 67) // (((-37 + 23) * (-7 - 62)) * 81)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 743, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 79 * (((55 + 17) - ((-34 // (55 + 49)) - 70)) - -58)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 744, "answer": 15879}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 98 // (65 + (((81 // 51) % -79) * 33))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 745, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (10 // ((29 + 37) + 69)) + (51 + -21)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 746, "answer": 30}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-72 // (-63 + -31)) - 92) * (92 * ((-98 * -56) + 26))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 747, "answer": -46670496}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -82 - ((((88 + 11) - -56) + -54) % -4)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 748, "answer": -79}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (25 // -53) * ((16 * (-52 + -48)) * -84)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 749, "answer": -134400}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-33 % 5) + (((63 + (-79 - -24)) * -78) - (-68 * -29))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 750, "answer": -2594}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (50 + (23 - 25)) * (-97 - (-31 - 93))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 751, "answer": 1296}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-75 + (34 + (-3 - (25 + 22)))) * 94", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 752, "answer": -8554}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((75 // -12) * (-38 - -7)) // 71) + (-3 // 57)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 753, "answer": 2}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-99 % 17) - 79) - ((-93 - 55) + -68)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 754, "answer": 140}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-5 + (59 + 76)) // ((((-99 + 64) * -17) // -95) + 63)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 755, "answer": 2}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 89 * (((56 // 25) * 3) % (-10 * (22 + 69)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 756, "answer": -80456}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 88 * (((83 + -63) - (-67 - 28)) + (-22 + (-56 - 15)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 757, "answer": 1936}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-37 + (-56 // 93)) % 69) - (-72 + 12)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 758, "answer": 91}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -58 * (((-43 * 85) * -34) + (((71 % -65) + 37) // 63))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 759, "answer": -7207602}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (78 + ((48 * 97) * 54)) * (65 + ((84 // 91) + 89))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 760, "answer": 38731308}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-42 - -33) // -70) - -25) + (-71 - (-12 // (91 + -70)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 761, "answer": -45}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-19 - (48 * 89)) * (-20 * (52 * (0 - (-18 - 98))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 762, "answer": 517666240}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-72 + 2) - (38 * ((-62 // -24) * -43))) // 28", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 763, "answer": 114}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (54 - ((92 * 71) + 80)) * (54 % ((29 // 77) + -68))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 764, "answer": 91812}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((((27 + (81 - -3)) + -84) // -14) + -60) * 84", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 765, "answer": -5208}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (99 - -54) % ((-23 + 69) - (-94 + 41))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 766, "answer": 54}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-10 - 94) - 1) // ((36 - 87) - (-27 - 79))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 767, "answer": -2}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-66 + ((82 - -22) - 18)) % 68) + -58", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 768, "answer": -38}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (79 + 24) + ((-46 - (92 - -49)) * (-7 - (74 - -62)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 769, "answer": 26844}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-85 - (-8 * 22)) - -54) * (-69 + (52 - 12))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 770, "answer": -4205}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-91 - (-38 + (26 - -22))) - (68 % 91)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 771, "answer": -169}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (19 - (((-5 // -97) + (-70 - -78)) + -68)) + 26", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 772, "answer": 105}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((51 + 47) * ((78 // 91) // -75)) + 52) + (-1 + 24)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 773, "answer": 75}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-74 * -16) - (83 // 38)) - (4 + 80)) - (1 - 43)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 774, "answer": 1140}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((33 + (93 * (69 - -69))) + -53) + (-98 % 43)) + 15", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 775, "answer": 12860}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -89 - ((68 + -58) - (44 * ((-78 + -68) - 30)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 776, "answer": -7843}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (9 - (-36 * -23)) * (33 + ((-64 // 48) // 26))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 777, "answer": -26208}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((77 - -74) % 70) - (-39 + (-51 * (-23 % (-65 - 55))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 778, "answer": -1123}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-28 % -67) - (((41 * ((-2 // 67) + -58)) - 3) + 17)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 779, "answer": 2377}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((38 + -47) * -81) + ((83 - -4) * 45)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 780, "answer": 4644}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-60 + -19) + ((-93 + 55) + -36)) + -80) + (-68 - 37)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 781, "answer": -338}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-15 // (-7 - (-30 - -62))) // -42) - -29", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 782, "answer": 29}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -3 + ((-73 + -68) + (35 % (51 + 26)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 783, "answer": -109}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((56 + -74) + -87) * (-18 + 93)) + 0", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 784, "answer": -7875}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((52 - -67) + -33) + (76 // (69 + -67))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 785, "answer": 124}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((86 * 64) - -5) + 82) + (74 % 56)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 786, "answer": 5609}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((13 // ((29 // -26) + -29)) - (34 + 84)) * -41", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 787, "answer": 4879}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-21 + (((63 // -79) * (87 // -38)) // -76)) + -57", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 788, "answer": -79}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -78 + ((((9 + 74) - 31) + (23 - (32 - 76))) * 74)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 789, "answer": 8728}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (4 - (58 * (91 * (83 - (80 + 37))))) - (-37 + 90)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 790, "answer": 179403}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((56 + ((73 + 96) - (-55 - -80))) % (-65 + 32)) % -9", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 791, "answer": -4}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-56 - -4) + (-13 + 74)) % (39 - 97)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 792, "answer": -49}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-24 + -32) * -45) - (89 % (-44 + -21))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 793, "answer": 2561}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (19 + (((-8 * -98) - 58) - 18)) // ((3 // -9) - -97)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 794, "answer": 7}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-78 * 36) - (6 + -68)) - (-98 + -60)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 795, "answer": -2588}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (21 + (-4 - -23)) + (((38 - -31) * -72) + (69 - 13))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 796, "answer": -4872}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (92 + 12) * (-8 - (-71 - (-27 + -89)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 797, "answer": -5512}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-91 - -58) + (23 * 71)) * (-69 - 8)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 798, "answer": -123200}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-16 + (29 + 86)) // 90) - 0) + (-71 * -72)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 799, "answer": 5113}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-11 * 29) + (97 - (-86 + (10 + 53)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 800, "answer": -199}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 12 + (((25 - -78) + (-36 + 59)) // (87 + (-36 + -28)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 801, "answer": 17}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (71 + (-49 - 22)) + (80 // (-51 + 52))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 802, "answer": 80}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-69 % -66) // ((-29 + -50) - (10 * -95))) - (-76 - -86)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 803, "answer": -11}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-43 + -13) + 10) // 23) * (31 - (65 + -86))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 804, "answer": -104}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -31 + (((83 - 8) % -36) // ((-53 * -89) - -99))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 805, "answer": -32}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-26 - (-28 + 56)) // (11 * (-35 + 26))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 806, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-75 - 72) - -96) - ((-15 - (90 % -7)) - 91)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 807, "answer": 54}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((67 - (-46 // 50)) * (-77 * -72)) // (62 - (-89 - 51))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 808, "answer": 1866}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((81 - 15) * (-80 * (((86 * 22) // 95) - -48))) // 37", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 809, "answer": -9562}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-67 - -50) - ((((-6 + 15) - 62) * 84) * (12 - -82))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 810, "answer": 418471}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-57 + (79 - -66)) * -25) + (45 + (78 - -51))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 811, "answer": -2026}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-57 * 13) + (44 - 0)) % ((-47 % -52) * -99)) - -59", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 812, "answer": 4015}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (32 - 17) + ((((-24 // 82) - -31) + (-56 * -42)) - -88)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 813, "answer": 2485}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-89 + 64) // ((-65 + -30) - (65 + (-46 % (-99 + 67))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 814, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((((81 - 41) + -32) - (5 * 57)) * -24) * -16", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 815, "answer": -106368}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -8 + ((-54 % -34) - (38 - (85 - 91)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 816, "answer": -72}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((14 // -43) + -16) + -31) - (49 - ((15 * -40) - 87))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 817, "answer": -784}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((23 // -76) // (-53 - 18)) + (-54 // (46 * (87 + -53)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 818, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-20 + (-54 - 1)) + ((-63 * -81) + ((17 - 66) - 4))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 819, "answer": 4975}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((55 + -74) // ((-94 + -71) - -96)) * 96", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 820, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -66 + ((-31 - -63) + (-97 - (39 // ((-48 % -64) * 23))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 821, "answer": -130}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-21 + ((-60 * -37) + -85)) + (((-94 - -88) - -73) - 40)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 822, "answer": 2141}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 31 * ((-99 % (-93 - (10 - -1))) // (-9 * 68))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 823, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (76 - 84) - (26 - (-71 - (-73 * (-8 + -80))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 824, "answer": -6529}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-7 - (-88 - 55)) + ((10 - 36) + ((74 + 9) * -61))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 825, "answer": -4953}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-73 - -30) - 28) - ((83 - -80) + -99)) // (68 - -62)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 826, "answer": -2}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (15 // 85) - ((-71 * ((-62 - -76) + -17)) + -67)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 827, "answer": -146}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((27 - 9) + (78 // 6)) * (-64 - 68)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 828, "answer": -4092}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((38 - 37) % (37 + 38)) - (-1 - -78)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 829, "answer": -76}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((80 - (-39 + -7)) - -99) + (-95 + -7)) + (-65 // -71)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 830, "answer": 123}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-24 + 18) - -63) - ((-46 * -42) + -85)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 831, "answer": -1790}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (79 + 81) - ((88 + -93) + (((-86 + 80) // -72) + 70))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 832, "answer": 95}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 23 - (((-62 // -6) + (-79 - (-80 + -96))) - (-61 - 96))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 833, "answer": -241}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((92 + (21 + 6)) + 85) + (14 - 66)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 834, "answer": 152}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -26 + (-60 * (65 - (55 // (29 % (-97 % (9 * 75))))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 835, "answer": -3866}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((9 - -59) - -30) * (34 - -3)) + (91 + -45)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 836, "answer": 3672}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-43 // ((91 // 44) - (78 + 20))) - (-19 - 68)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 837, "answer": 87}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-86 + -4) // (-50 - -30)) + (-73 + (-7 - (-92 - -38)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 838, "answer": -22}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-83 % -45) // (94 * ((42 - -48) + (-38 - -31)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 839, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (45 * ((-87 - -19) - (-20 + -97))) - -8", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 840, "answer": 2213}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-19 - (86 // -8)) // -66) + (-15 + (90 - 29))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 841, "answer": 46}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((51 + -2) * ((-25 // -58) * -61)) + 75", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 842, "answer": 75}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 61 + (84 - ((75 + 68) + (97 - (29 * 33))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 843, "answer": 862}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-13 + -25) - -7) % (-89 + 83)) + ((-46 + 57) + 56)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 844, "answer": 66}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-75 * -96) + (97 + ((28 - -75) - 17))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 845, "answer": 7383}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-58 - -82) // (((-77 * -81) // -54) - (-33 + 22))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 846, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-68 * (-89 - -6)) + -26) // ((32 * 60) - -19)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 847, "answer": 2}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 75 // ((((75 // -89) + 59) + 65) * (90 * -37))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 848, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-60 + (-25 * ((46 + 3) * -81))) + (0 - 19)) + 72", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 849, "answer": 99218}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((65 % 37) - 20) - (-78 % (88 * -72))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 850, "answer": 86}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (3 // ((-18 * -12) - 55)) + ((80 + 90) % 22)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 851, "answer": 16}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((40 + -60) * 21) - (64 - (-18 - 46))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 852, "answer": -548}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-7 + ((-45 * -86) + -45)) + -94) - 95", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 853, "answer": 3629}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((63 + -54) - (-63 - -82)) + ((-79 + -23) // (8 - 35))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 854, "answer": -7}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-86 - (10 - -12)) - ((-49 - -10) * 8)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 855, "answer": 204}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((79 + (-9 - 78)) * 47) - ((44 - 53) + -49)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 856, "answer": -318}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((71 % 88) // ((-61 - 18) - -62)) * 28", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 857, "answer": -140}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 73 - (((16 - -67) // (64 * 49)) - (-90 - -44))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 858, "answer": 27}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (79 % 40) - ((-44 * -10) + (-51 - (-5 // (-95 + -22))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 859, "answer": -350}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (80 * ((6 - 6) + (-9 // 39))) + (34 - 96)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 860, "answer": -142}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -54 + (((-54 % 42) + (39 - 12)) // (-27 - 69))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 861, "answer": -55}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((((-77 + -73) + -77) + 67) - (58 * 6)) + (28 + 92)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 862, "answer": -388}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (63 % ((71 + -25) - (-45 // -42))) // (-10 * (6 - 66))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 863, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-4 + (30 + (-31 % 69))) + (-21 * 7)) + 73) + -38", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 864, "answer": -48}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-96 + (-60 * (33 + 90))) - (-14 - -56)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 865, "answer": -7518}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (43 * ((58 - 65) + 1)) - (48 // ((63 + 0) * 87))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 866, "answer": -258}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((12 - -40) - (82 - -67)) // (62 // 48)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 867, "answer": -97}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-17 - (-76 - -76)) - (12 % (-92 - 59))) + 82", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 868, "answer": 204}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 47 % ((91 - (17 + (-52 % -38))) - (-23 + (38 + -37)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 869, "answer": 47}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-29 + -78) + (61 - -94)) - (-71 - (53 + -68))) + -72", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 870, "answer": 32}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-76 + -80) + 27) % ((1 + -74) % 26)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 871, "answer": 1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (25 // (-46 - (-3 - -19))) * (-58 + -53)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 872, "answer": 111}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -54 + ((-69 % ((24 % 58) + (-59 + 34))) - 90)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 873, "answer": -144}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -50 + ((38 * (33 * (-44 - (-70 + -44)))) % -92)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 874, "answer": -130}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-78 - 87) // ((-29 - 24) % (-76 + (82 - 42)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 875, "answer": 9}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((12 - 32) - 3) % ((-55 + -49) - ((-73 - 50) * 97))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 876, "answer": 11804}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-47 - (11 - 15)) - ((((60 * -72) + 56) - -1) - 10)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 877, "answer": 4230}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((16 * -57) - -91) - (51 * 5)) - -24", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 878, "answer": -1052}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((((-70 * -53) + -17) - (-52 + -8)) + -37) + -81) - -44", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 879, "answer": 3679}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-19 - -68) - -97) - ((84 - (-45 % 20)) + (-40 // 44))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 880, "answer": 78}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((35 // -44) * (44 - -28)) + (47 - 66)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 881, "answer": -91}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-49 - -49) // (27 - 28)) % (-29 + 8)) % -69", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 882, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (54 // ((-39 + 48) - -94)) - (-95 % 65)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 883, "answer": -35}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 19 + ((4 - (37 + 36)) + (-13 * (-82 + (-75 * 7))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 884, "answer": 7841}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((93 - -11) - 3) + (43 + ((57 + -87) + (-23 - 79)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 885, "answer": 12}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-4 - (-92 % -42)) - -87) + (-64 % (-17 - 77))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 886, "answer": 27}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-56 - (-51 * (38 * -98))) - ((-33 * (-71 + -87)) + -22)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 887, "answer": -195172}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-30 * 79) + -56) // (50 + (-69 // -67))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 888, "answer": -48}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (64 - 15) + (34 + ((48 + (70 + 26)) % -28))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 889, "answer": 59}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-76 - ((83 - -78) - -9)) + (69 + 66)) + 89", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 890, "answer": -22}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -80 - ((-45 * (72 - (20 + -1))) + -51)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 891, "answer": 2356}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -12 + ((95 - -20) + (((30 % -72) % -66) * -43))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 892, "answer": 1909}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((3 + -51) - (-28 + 9)) // (-62 * (-72 - 91))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 893, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (18 + -52) - ((22 + 70) + (-9 * -32))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 894, "answer": -414}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-9 + ((-61 + 2) * (31 * -14))) * -86", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 895, "answer": -2201342}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-87 + 67) - -2) + (((-24 * -51) * 4) % -54)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 896, "answer": -36}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-72 - 75) - -87) + ((-43 // -70) - (-90 * (-38 + -83)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 897, "answer": -10950}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -29 - ((1 - 1) - (-43 - (((-47 - -56) - -47) // -11)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 898, "answer": -66}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-75 + -52) + 29) + ((((-56 - -19) + 75) + -82) - -57)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 899, "answer": -85}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-96 + 71) - 22) // ((-94 + -54) // -32)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 900, "answer": -12}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (53 * -9) * ((26 + -36) * (-71 * -88))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 901, "answer": 29802960}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((35 - (94 + -62)) - (-74 // -22)) - 89", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 902, "answer": -89}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((40 - -34) + (-35 - -6)) - ((-9 - -22) + 82)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 903, "answer": -50}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-30 + (-62 - (-43 + 69))) * -63) + (28 * -92)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 904, "answer": 4858}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((91 + -77) // (-3 + 64)) - -72) - -29", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 905, "answer": 101}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((((-32 - (-15 + 1)) // 51) * 7) - -29) + (-51 + -89)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 906, "answer": -118}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((11 + (46 + -11)) + (-71 + -97)) - ((20 - 75) // -61)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 907, "answer": -122}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-22 * (-26 // -83)) - ((17 * (-44 + -27)) - (-86 + 26))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 908, "answer": 1147}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 11 * ((-87 + (-64 % -10)) + ((-77 + 83) // -30))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 909, "answer": -1012}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (50 * -79) + ((-91 // 22) % (-36 % 74))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 910, "answer": -3917}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-74 * -33) - (53 - -20)) // (45 % ((49 + -64) - 75))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 911, "answer": -53}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (7 + (-22 - -21)) * (-23 * (40 - -53))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 912, "answer": -12834}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-64 - ((29 - 76) + 83)) - ((-9 - 10) // 20)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 913, "answer": -99}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((44 + -93) + (-77 - 94)) - (58 - (-37 % 49))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 914, "answer": -266}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (59 * (-86 - 94)) + ((4 + (19 * (-86 - -78))) + -85)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 915, "answer": -10853}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-14 // (-25 // (((-84 - -68) + 90) - 50))) - 73", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 916, "answer": -66}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (80 + ((44 - 90) * ((-42 + 73) * 64))) // (-22 - 61)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 917, "answer": 1098}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (25 + ((-82 // -99) + (55 - (34 + -75)))) // -36", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 918, "answer": -4}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 22 - (30 // ((-85 * -68) + (4 * 24)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 919, "answer": 22}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (57 - 75) - ((11 - -62) * (-52 + -63))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 920, "answer": 8377}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((31 + 90) - ((22 + (-25 + -25)) + 71)) + (51 // 27)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 921, "answer": 79}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((79 + -72) - 19) - ((-62 * -92) + -27)) - 18", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 922, "answer": -5707}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((49 * ((66 + 67) + 69)) - 59) - 14", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 923, "answer": 9825}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (20 * (-29 * -97)) + (-8 - (-10 + 81))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 924, "answer": 56181}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-55 * (-9 + 68)) // 85) + (((84 % -64) - -28) + 96)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 925, "answer": 41}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((66 * 24) - -3) + (((48 * (-66 - 79)) * -17) // 51)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 926, "answer": 3907}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-88 * -92) // 88) + ((-75 + 71) % (28 + (-17 - 95)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 927, "answer": 88}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-55 - 87) + ((-83 + -84) + (-70 * -90))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 928, "answer": 5991}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 14 // ((-55 // (-72 - 79)) - ((-65 + 64) * (-49 + -35)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 929, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-48 + 90) - -58) + 12) - (-77 * (62 + 72))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 930, "answer": 10430}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-64 * -98) % ((46 + 40) - (-12 - -52))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 931, "answer": 16}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-46 - ((-8 + 59) + 44)) - -64) + -82) + (10 // 61)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 932, "answer": -159}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 46 % (-67 + ((-69 + (-40 // -86)) // (-94 - -42)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 933, "answer": -20}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-82 - -59) % -26) + (37 + (33 + (3 * 59)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 934, "answer": 224}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (50 - ((68 + -92) + (-13 + 8))) * -33", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 935, "answer": -2607}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-64 + (41 + 88)) + ((-39 - 27) + -81)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 936, "answer": -82}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-11 - (7 * (42 // (-66 + -30)))) * (-73 - (28 - 30))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 937, "answer": 284}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-22 * -41) - -94) - (-93 + (37 + 56))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 938, "answer": 996}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (42 + ((0 * ((11 // 80) - 10)) % 41)) * -64", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 939, "answer": -2688}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (58 % (-39 + (-76 * 51))) + (-41 * 6)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 940, "answer": -4103}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-96 - ((-85 // (-85 * -67)) - 13)) - (-27 - -88)) + -19", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 941, "answer": -162}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-66 * 56) + ((69 // -68) // 69)) * (-80 // -35)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 942, "answer": -7394}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (81 + 89) + ((14 + (-6 + 42)) * ((35 // -31) - -18))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 943, "answer": 970}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-86 - ((81 * 60) - (-28 + -79))) + (-64 * (-21 + 90))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 944, "answer": -9469}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-4 - 86) + ((-39 - 79) // ((-70 - -94) + (-91 + -30)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 945, "answer": -89}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-84 * -28) + (27 % -95)) + -2) % (14 - -88)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 946, "answer": 38}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-52 // 69) % ((70 - -21) + (39 * 96))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 947, "answer": 3834}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 56 * (((94 % -92) + -12) + ((87 + 89) + 93))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 948, "answer": 9352}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 42 - ((((9 - 47) + 85) - 46) % 97)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 949, "answer": 41}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-2 + (91 - -39)) + ((-28 % 75) + ((-36 * 98) + 39))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 950, "answer": -3314}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((58 + -29) - -7) - ((68 // 98) // (-68 - -21))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 951, "answer": 36}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((14 * 19) * -95) - ((20 + -90) - -8)) - (64 + 43)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 952, "answer": -25315}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (49 - (-29 % (-83 - 13))) - (-33 * 97)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 953, "answer": 3279}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-41 * 62) - -55) - (59 - (-40 - (68 // -90)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 954, "answer": -2585}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((((42 - 84) + -41) + -84) + 83) // -33", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 955, "answer": 2}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 74 + ((54 + (-10 + -72)) - (30 + (-71 * 31)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 956, "answer": 2217}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-16 % 47) * ((-81 // 65) - (-27 // -63))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 957, "answer": -62}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((5 + 67) + -4) - ((60 + -92) - -58)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 958, "answer": 42}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -25 * ((-72 - 56) - (-19 * ((-3 + 50) - -91)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 959, "answer": -62350}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((96 + 67) + (-80 + (45 - (38 * 88)))) * (36 - -86)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 960, "answer": -392352}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-31 - -50) + 48) // -24) + (-15 - (97 - (-40 * 17)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 961, "answer": -795}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (78 - ((88 - 5) - ((-9 - 44) % 30))) - -80", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 962, "answer": 82}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((15 * (-41 // 46)) - -67) - (99 * 5)) - 73", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 963, "answer": -516}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-26 + -12) - ((-79 - 5) // (30 + -62))) - (62 % 98)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 964, "answer": -102}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-96 - -57) + (8 - ((91 - -74) + -67))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 965, "answer": -129}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (77 * (-81 - (32 - 36))) + (9 + -9)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 966, "answer": -5929}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((83 // (-69 - -13)) * -13) - (85 - -88)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 967, "answer": -147}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((62 + 16) % 90) - ((94 - 23) + 80)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 968, "answer": -73}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-61 + -98) + (((-2 % -17) + 13) - -54)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 969, "answer": -94}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-40 * (27 * -12)) - (45 * 33)) // 35) + (-26 + -17)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 970, "answer": 284}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-63 % (89 + 88)) + (11 * ((-74 - -11) * -27))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 971, "answer": 18825}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -26 + (((-42 + -56) + -26) + (56 - 93))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 972, "answer": -187}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-63 // -75) + (42 - (-92 - (39 % 38)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 973, "answer": 135}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 26 * (-5 + (-27 + ((34 * -67) * 17)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 974, "answer": -1007708}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 84 * (14 - (((-77 - -64) - (88 + 72)) + -70))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 975, "answer": 21588}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 91 - ((-16 * -59) * (((17 - 62) % 89) - 32))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 976, "answer": -11237}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (81 * ((11 // (81 // 34)) * ((43 + 70) // 61))) + -90", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 977, "answer": 315}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-37 + ((-43 * 73) % (-32 + (-61 // 25)))) - (88 + 28)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 978, "answer": -177}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (63 - -77) + ((12 - -82) + ((82 + -54) % -90))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 979, "answer": 172}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((64 + -10) - 24) * (-23 - (-25 // 72))) + 25", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 980, "answer": -635}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((((-24 - -75) - -43) - -71) * (8 + 15)) - -16", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 981, "answer": 3811}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-54 + ((70 * -70) - -11)) + (81 - -67)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 982, "answer": -4795}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-92 // -25) - -31) + 30) + (5 - (44 % 98))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 983, "answer": 25}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((1 - 14) + 9) - ((-86 * -31) % (87 * -43))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 984, "answer": 1071}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-21 - (((47 - -57) + (61 * -71)) - 58)) + 57", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 985, "answer": 4321}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (85 - -94) + ((81 + ((97 // 97) // 42)) + -83)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 986, "answer": 177}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 33 * ((38 // -49) - ((84 + -41) - ((-4 * -15) + 6)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 987, "answer": 726}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-90 + -94) * (29 + (25 - -89))) // -59", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 988, "answer": 445}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-41 // (-91 + -30)) + ((-3 + (-66 - 90)) - -30)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 989, "answer": -129}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -81 * ((-96 + (-75 * (-50 * 56))) - -20)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 990, "answer": -17003844}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-22 - (18 // -48)) % -74) // ((-3 - -25) - 10)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 991, "answer": -2}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (44 - -28) * ((80 - 37) // (-2 - -95))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 992, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((16 - -42) - (2 + 98)) + (15 - -5)) * 23", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 993, "answer": -506}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 65 + (((62 - -78) - -75) + ((-46 + (52 + -36)) % -78))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 994, "answer": 250}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-84 - 97) + 27) + -35) - (-20 + 90)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 995, "answer": -259}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-17 - 77) + ((-31 % (94 - (40 - 28))) - -19)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 996, "answer": -24}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (19 + 82) - (((-73 * (80 - -80)) + -3) + (94 * -96))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 997, "answer": 20808}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-57 + (13 - (-90 - (27 * -56)))) * 61", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 998, "answer": -89426}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (92 + ((-97 + -24) // -69)) + ((85 // 74) * (34 - -17))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 999, "answer": 144}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-63 + (34 // 76)) // ((33 + 55) + ((19 - -46) + -15))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1000, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((35 % 84) + ((-18 - 7) - (-61 // 21))) - (-98 * -20)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1001, "answer": -1947}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (78 % -75) % ((((-84 + 60) + (53 * -59)) + -82) + -10)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1002, "answer": -72}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((61 * -96) + (-29 - (10 * 50))) - ((60 + 97) + 4)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1003, "answer": -6546}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((52 * -60) + (88 + (-28 - -54))) - (45 + -73)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1004, "answer": -2978}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((89 // 58) * (-46 - -56)) - -99) - -40", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1005, "answer": 149}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 58 - ((-57 + 22) + (-17 * (-86 // -64)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1006, "answer": 110}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-16 - -22) % (-38 - 44)) + ((99 - -1) - 81)) + 22", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1007, "answer": -35}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((55 + -45) + -57) // (((12 * 44) * 14) + 26)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1008, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((43 + (67 + -10)) - (-93 + ((98 + 72) - -11))) - 87", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1009, "answer": -75}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-2 % -4) + ((-49 + 14) - ((-98 + 51) + -20))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1010, "answer": 30}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -5 + ((56 - (-91 // 66)) + ((2 - -88) - 79))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1011, "answer": 64}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((47 + -92) - 84) * ((((-55 + 22) + 92) % 66) + 93)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1012, "answer": -19608}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-90 - ((57 + (81 * 89)) * (-66 + (8 + -69)))) * -85", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1013, "answer": -78428820}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-19 // (40 + ((68 // 58) + (-14 * 73)))) + -18", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1014, "answer": -18}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (33 + -96) % (((-83 * -50) // (87 - -31)) + (-55 - 14))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1015, "answer": -29}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (77 - (-55 + 63)) - (-20 + (44 - -10))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1016, "answer": 35}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((45 + 19) - -77) * (-76 * (87 - -77))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1017, "answer": -1757424}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (97 - (-97 + -44)) * ((-79 - 86) + -36)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1018, "answer": -47838}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-20 * -86) - ((-54 + -28) + (45 - -19))) + 6", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1019, "answer": 1744}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-48 % -54) // ((79 * 13) - (-76 - 26))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1020, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((62 - 76) + -56) // (50 - -1)) - (38 - 46)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1021, "answer": 6}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-46 // -12) // (-76 // 32)) - (-33 + -44)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1022, "answer": 76}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-70 * (22 * -64)) * ((-4 - 45) * (69 + 51))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1023, "answer": -579532800}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (62 - (-97 + -59)) + ((-14 + -13) - 66)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1024, "answer": 125}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-21 - -58) // ((93 - -94) - (58 - 17))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1025, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((((-37 + -35) + 86) // -4) + 54) - ((74 % 3) // -23)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1026, "answer": 51}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (8 % 10) - ((52 + -92) - (32 + -57))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1027, "answer": 23}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-66 // 70) - ((-76 + -20) - 97)) + (-11 - 18)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1028, "answer": 163}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-99 - 69) * ((-55 // -22) - ((-52 + -39) * -47))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1029, "answer": 718200}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 86 % ((76 * 43) - ((23 + -59) // (-74 - 21)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1030, "answer": 86}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((21 + (19 - 81)) - -37) + (0 % -67)) // (96 // -65)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1031, "answer": 2}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((53 - 1) + 37) - (-11 * ((-43 * 56) + -54))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1032, "answer": -26993}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((29 - -99) * 57) - ((66 - -41) - -64)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1033, "answer": 7125}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-45 - -22) * ((-13 - ((9 - -61) * -27)) - -20)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1034, "answer": -43631}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-33 // ((-58 + 2) + 75)) - (20 * -78)) - -11", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1035, "answer": 1569}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (68 - ((-58 - ((48 + 30) - -1)) - 76)) + (-97 + 25)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1036, "answer": 209}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-22 % 9) - (90 - 63)) + (55 + 16)) - (22 * 83)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1037, "answer": -1777}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-54 + (37 - 95)) + (73 * -79)) - (-98 + -13)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1038, "answer": -5768}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((32 + (12 + -87)) - (-27 - -89)) + (26 - (-6 * -87))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1039, "answer": -601}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-13 + 73) % -24) + (39 * (-54 - -24))) + (7 - -95)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1040, "answer": -1080}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((53 - -71) // -8) % ((37 - (-36 % -55)) - -78)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1041, "answer": 135}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -67 - (((11 * -29) - ((77 + 59) + (88 - 35))) - 46)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1042, "answer": 487}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -80 - (((-62 - 56) + 86) - (-2 * (-13 - 64)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1043, "answer": 106}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-94 // -52) // 92) % ((11 + (-50 + 47)) * (-22 * 58))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1044, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-4 // 47) + ((95 - 12) - -29)) - (-29 - (55 + 3))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1045, "answer": 198}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((5 - -46) * -95) + ((-29 + -31) - 19)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1046, "answer": -4924}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-43 * (-95 - 82)) + ((-83 * 57) % -26)) - 87) + 83", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1047, "answer": 7582}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((((39 - 0) // 22) * 43) // (-12 + (-18 // -11))) + 14", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1048, "answer": 10}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((37 // 79) + -56) + 73) // (-34 - 4)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1049, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (62 - ((-78 + -46) // (-22 - -25))) + 93", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1050, "answer": 197}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-60 - 60) - 50) // -57) % ((7 * 96) - -94)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1051, "answer": 2}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-3 + (-3 + (-75 - 2))) - -44) % (-71 + 47)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1052, "answer": -15}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (97 * 89) // ((((93 + -44) - 8) * 54) // -28)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1053, "answer": -108}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (71 * (29 - 38)) + (((4 - 27) - 94) + 19)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1054, "answer": -737}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-54 + ((-99 - 37) + -14)) - ((75 * -74) + -1)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1055, "answer": 5347}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-51 - 63) - (59 % -42)) - (57 + 59)) % (54 // 47)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1056, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-16 // (-57 + (76 - -76))) + ((91 + 54) - (42 - 31))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1057, "answer": 133}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-5 - 86) + (-55 % ((-17 + -66) * -24))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1058, "answer": 1846}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -47 // (((76 * 55) - (-38 + -54)) + 19)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1059, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (55 % ((-37 - (85 * -82)) - (92 * -91))) // (34 * 21)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1060, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 7 - ((84 + (13 - 24)) - (-25 + (86 - 97)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1061, "answer": -102}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((10 - -68) + -73) % (-32 - (85 + -56))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1062, "answer": -56}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-37 - 24) - -46) * -32) - (-15 + (18 - 82))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1063, "answer": 559}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-12 + -24) + (((80 % -33) - (53 + -90)) + 95)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1064, "answer": 77}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-93 * -43) + ((83 + -25) - (84 + -59))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1065, "answer": 4032}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((73 + -24) * -60) // (-62 // (-1 * -34))) + (-92 * -45)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1066, "answer": 5610}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (50 // (-33 * -6)) * (((-11 * 65) + (51 - 29)) // -19)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1067, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((66 % -56) + 35) + ((24 * ((72 + -83) + -12)) + -42)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1068, "answer": -605}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-61 % -28) - (67 // (-8 - ((46 + 64) // -96)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1069, "answer": 7}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-6 // 71) + (3 + (-15 // 30))) * (-30 + 42)) // 37", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1070, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-85 * ((-37 - -34) + (77 - 67))) - (-41 + (-54 % -89))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1071, "answer": -500}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((91 + -51) - 88) - (-66 - (((-46 - -41) + -37) - 50))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1072, "answer": -74}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((38 - -86) * (63 + -81)) * (23 + (14 - (22 * -49)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1073, "answer": -2488680}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-23 % 46) + (49 + (-71 + 85))) - 14", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1074, "answer": 72}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-99 + -35) - ((((62 - -54) * -15) - 30) - (32 - -27))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1075, "answer": 1695}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-12 + -29) + 74) + (((94 // -53) + 25) // (-18 * 31))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1076, "answer": 32}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-54 // (-50 * (96 + -40))) + (-21 - (-18 - 97))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1077, "answer": 94}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (76 - ((47 + 73) * -60)) * ((-50 + 97) // (-56 - -59))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1078, "answer": 109140}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((33 + 22) - (((-41 + -32) + 21) // -22)) - (-62 - -21)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1079, "answer": 94}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-21 - 9) * 45) + ((-98 - 96) + 4)) - -85", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1080, "answer": -1455}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (17 + (-95 // 81)) + (-46 + ((-4 // -93) * -17))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1081, "answer": -31}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-44 + 59) + (-29 * -72)) * (-37 - (-16 - 86))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1082, "answer": 136695}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((69 - ((-36 + -28) - 56)) - 51) * -3) + -84", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1083, "answer": -498}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 64 - (((13 * -27) * -71) * (-65 - 92))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1084, "answer": 3912661}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-61 + 51) - -23) - (44 - (13 - -37))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1085, "answer": 19}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-64 // 98) - 98) - (80 + 83)) * (-7 * 98)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1086, "answer": 179732}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-17 - 20) // (18 - ((-49 // 74) + 81))) // -33", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1087, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-64 // (65 + ((2 * 25) // -87))) + (32 + -4)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1088, "answer": 27}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((30 + ((-27 + 48) - -14)) + 63) + -82", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1089, "answer": 46}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 45 * (43 // (37 * ((47 + 20) - (93 - (97 - 76)))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1090, "answer": -45}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((90 + -61) * 67) * ((-53 + 66) - (17 + 36))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1091, "answer": -77720}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((3 + ((60 + 0) + -95)) - (-42 // -17)) - (-61 + -33)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1092, "answer": 60}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((98 - 48) - -9) // (-51 + 98)) + -62", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1093, "answer": -61}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-74 + (37 * 55)) - (-67 - (-82 - -16))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1094, "answer": 1962}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-48 + -22) - ((-30 * -40) * (98 * (-93 + -64)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1095, "answer": 18463130}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -3 - (14 + ((-87 * 15) * ((-49 - -47) - 98)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1096, "answer": -130517}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-76 - (30 + (-58 - (-69 * 26)))) // (92 * -18)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1097, "answer": 1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-76 - 30) * (((31 - -71) // 17) + (-98 + -2))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1098, "answer": 9964}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-9 - ((-83 * 12) // 67)) + ((80 + -78) - 67)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1099, "answer": -59}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-29 + 87) + (-88 * -63)) - (-54 - (-67 * 33))) + -60", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1100, "answer": 3385}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-84 % (90 + (-4 - 59))) - (-59 * 8)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1101, "answer": 496}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (90 + 72) - (-6 + (-58 - (28 // -47)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1102, "answer": 225}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((60 // -17) + -92) + -93) + ((21 // -91) + 89)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1103, "answer": -101}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (39 - ((-59 - -74) // -96)) * (-42 % -76)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1104, "answer": -1680}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -71 + (((38 + 13) - (55 % 64)) - (-20 + 22))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1105, "answer": -77}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-17 + (58 + 72)) % ((23 // (92 - 47)) - -49)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1106, "answer": 15}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-63 + -42) + ((91 + (84 + 4)) + -27)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1107, "answer": 47}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -36 + ((-52 * 87) + (((72 // 52) % 34) // (95 + -66)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1108, "answer": -4560}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((49 // 89) + (92 - -1)) * (-49 + (-96 - -63))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1109, "answer": -7626}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -39 + ((-17 - -97) - (((-51 % 61) - (16 + -45)) - 17))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1110, "answer": 19}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((91 * -28) // 68) * (((-34 // -12) * 25) - (70 // -75))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1111, "answer": -1938}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-6 + 10) - 65) % (40 + (-75 - (18 + -71)))) + -69", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1112, "answer": -58}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-11 - (16 + 12)) + (30 + (2 + 31))) - (-63 - 75)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1113, "answer": 162}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -49 + ((45 * (37 * -7)) - (78 - 36))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1114, "answer": -11746}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-74 + (63 * 63)) - (93 * (39 + 57))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1115, "answer": -5033}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-87 + 3) - (((22 + 20) // -17) * (85 // -23))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1116, "answer": -96}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -35 * ((88 % (-84 - 94)) + (-64 % -63))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1117, "answer": 3185}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (1 + -59) + (((-36 + -10) - (-42 * -29)) // -64)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1118, "answer": -39}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 86 - (((14 - -63) + ((-97 // 64) // -69)) - 34)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1119, "answer": 43}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (98 + (((70 + 13) % -23) // -68)) + (-60 + -81)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1120, "answer": -43}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-2 // -34) + -71) + (((82 - 78) - (95 - -25)) + -42)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1121, "answer": -229}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -77 + ((((71 // (80 // 11)) + (-85 * 64)) + -73) - 98)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1122, "answer": -5678}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((8 // 71) - -35) % ((-96 + -74) // 83)) + 25", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1123, "answer": 24}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((52 - ((-73 - 82) + 25)) + 44) - 56", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1124, "answer": 170}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((55 % -72) - 52) + 65) - (48 // (-69 - (-7 - 49)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1125, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((((-11 + 66) * (18 + 47)) + 34) * -90) + (61 + 91)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1126, "answer": -324658}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-44 - ((62 - -15) + (-25 // (-92 // 87)))) + 17", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1127, "answer": -116}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-36 - -29) - 15) - (-16 - ((97 // -58) // -46))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1128, "answer": -6}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((((-55 // 28) * -77) + (-9 + 58)) + (-18 - -21)) + -74", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1129, "answer": 132}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 64 // (((64 + -52) + (-48 - -32)) * ((-13 + 13) + -7))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1130, "answer": 2}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-95 - -71) + (49 + ((94 - 44) % 38))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1131, "answer": 37}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-49 + (-76 + 83)) - 54) - (-32 // -62)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1132, "answer": -96}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-65 - -1) // -73) + ((-17 + (14 + -89)) - (41 - -60))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1133, "answer": -193}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (27 - (78 - -43)) - ((13 * 66) + (-62 + (-24 - -37)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1134, "answer": -903}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((43 + 42) - (6 % -52)) + 33) * 49", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1135, "answer": 8036}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((((-32 - 11) + -5) * -6) // -39) * -18) + 39", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1136, "answer": 183}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 78 + ((80 - -36) // ((-75 + (38 * -19)) + -73))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1137, "answer": 77}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (84 * 80) - (((-31 - 48) * (18 + (28 - 52))) - 12)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1138, "answer": 6258}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (44 * 15) - ((-11 % (81 * -62)) - -83)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1139, "answer": 588}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (85 - (46 % -35)) - (83 - (((81 + 96) + -65) // 2))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1140, "answer": 82}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-15 - -40) - (-63 + 97)) - (-98 + 57)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1141, "answer": 32}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (99 - (58 - -83)) * ((88 * -50) * -36)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1142, "answer": -6652800}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-92 + 67) // (((79 + 22) - (-12 - -53)) + -75)) + -20", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1143, "answer": -19}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-35 % 28) - (-52 // ((-48 + -41) + (66 + 63)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1144, "answer": 23}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((35 * -34) // -94) + (43 - (75 - -4))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1145, "answer": -24}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (36 + -96) - (-16 - ((-92 * 46) * 45))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1146, "answer": -190484}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -55 * ((-53 - 38) + (-11 + (75 + (54 + -4))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1147, "answer": -1265}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (81 + 98) - ((14 + -92) + ((38 // (-20 - -25)) + -72))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1148, "answer": 322}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-74 * 28) * (55 % (57 * (17 - 69)))) - 41", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1149, "answer": 6027407}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (72 % (-13 + (-6 - -63))) * (26 + (4 - -89))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1150, "answer": 3332}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 23 + ((34 - (70 - ((94 + 40) - 65))) // -48)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1151, "answer": 22}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (15 - (-25 - 61)) - ((12 - -3) - (26 * -93))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1152, "answer": -2332}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -17 + (((((28 + 98) // -26) - 98) * 76) + 79)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1153, "answer": -7766}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-51 // (-21 - (65 // (90 - -87)))) - 37", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1154, "answer": -35}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -22 // ((-9 * (76 + (90 - 31))) + 35)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1155, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-45 // (18 // -52)) * (83 - -18)) * -81", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1156, "answer": -368145}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-47 + 47) - ((-88 + ((77 - -70) - (-98 + -38))) + 69)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1157, "answer": -264}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-41 - -4) - ((-60 - (54 + (60 - 72))) + -33)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1158, "answer": 98}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((68 - (5 - 77)) - (7 * 6)) * -3) - -28", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1159, "answer": -266}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((61 - 78) + (-89 - 79)) - (-67 - 70)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1160, "answer": -48}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (64 + -70) - (-59 + ((-53 // ((90 + -34) + 75)) * 84))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1161, "answer": 137}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-27 - 46) + (-72 // 95)) + (2 + (-77 // (-48 + -67)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1162, "answer": -72}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 21 // ((-71 + (-90 - (-52 % -78))) + (-38 + (58 + -5)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1163, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((53 - 97) + (70 - (97 // (86 * -18)))) - -88", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1164, "answer": 115}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -60 + (((-10 // 19) * -48) // ((1 * (-60 + -25)) - 30))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1165, "answer": -61}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (61 - -50) + ((-93 // 13) - (-37 - 55))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1166, "answer": 195}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-63 + (-85 + -71)) + (5 * ((59 + (86 % -17)) - -5))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1167, "answer": 21}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (76 - -40) + (-2 * (45 // (-42 - 96)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1168, "answer": 118}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 45 * ((-94 + (((-27 % 76) + 58) * 0)) * (92 // -39))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1169, "answer": 12690}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((63 + 17) - 23) - -60) // ((-42 * -63) % (64 + 88))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1170, "answer": 1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-5 + 90) - (11 * -23)) + (-89 - 18)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1171, "answer": 231}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-67 - 61) - ((4 * 8) - 7)) * 18) * 88", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1172, "answer": -242352}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-6 + -13) - (71 // 3)) - (86 + (-37 + -44))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1173, "answer": -47}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (87 // 69) * ((((-4 - 65) * -21) - (1 + -63)) % 21)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1174, "answer": 20}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-86 + -48) + (-13 - 42)) - -59) * 69", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1175, "answer": -8970}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((14 // (78 + (-1 * 46))) - 71) - (-30 - 91)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1176, "answer": 50}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((48 - -49) - (6 - (20 - -37))) - (96 * (-19 + 57))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1177, "answer": -3500}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (74 % (-83 // (-94 * (-86 + -15)))) - (-19 + (-48 - 91))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1178, "answer": 158}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-83 + -7) - (((22 // -13) + 81) + -55)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1179, "answer": -114}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (44 * (-61 - -58)) - ((37 - 59) + (-59 + 44))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1180, "answer": -95}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((((-70 + 70) - -62) - 14) // (94 * -89)) % (-2 // 22)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1181, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (97 + (51 + (13 + 50))) % (15 % (-82 + -54))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1182, "answer": -31}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-71 - 72) + -49) + (-25 - 83)) - -78", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1183, "answer": -222}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((60 - ((-6 - -35) - -50)) // 32) - (34 - -93)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1184, "answer": -128}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-86 // (80 * -21)) + ((11 + -13) + (-30 - 92))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1185, "answer": -124}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-14 // (-66 * 60)) + -97) + ((-22 // (-48 * 21)) // -2)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1186, "answer": -97}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 78 * (((-6 // 32) + 9) + ((-66 - -11) + 85))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1187, "answer": 2964}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-27 - -31) * (16 + (71 + -18))) * (-94 + -67)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1188, "answer": -44436}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-54 + -4) - (-60 - (-77 - (-97 + 86)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1189, "answer": -64}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-60 % (62 + -15)) - (57 + (-85 - 81))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1190, "answer": 143}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-52 // -76) - ((-99 + (76 + -40)) * -46)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1191, "answer": -2898}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 0 + ((22 + (82 - 27)) - (21 + -26))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1192, "answer": 82}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((14 % (30 + (-79 - (-49 - -32)))) // -63) + (80 * -68)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1193, "answer": -5440}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-51 - ((94 + -41) + (2 % ((30 - 64) + -26)))) - -44", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1194, "answer": -2}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((36 - -98) + 68) + (((94 - -58) + -83) // -84)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1195, "answer": 201}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((59 // 94) + (-79 * 73)) + (-96 * 91)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1196, "answer": -14503}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -18 + (((46 - (87 % -18)) - (-8 + 91)) % (-5 + 28))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1197, "answer": -6}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-41 - 51) % (-89 - 77)) - ((20 + 19) - -16)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1198, "answer": -147}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-60 * -63) + (8 + -93)) + (-18 * (62 + -61))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1199, "answer": 3677}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (12 + (-61 - 52)) - (-44 - (-95 // (21 // -61)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1200, "answer": 38}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-94 + (1 + -59)) // ((-41 + -51) - (56 - 86))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1201, "answer": 2}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((25 - 71) - (-9 * -72)) - (-17 + (56 - -25))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1202, "answer": -758}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-44 - 7) + ((-21 * 62) + (-13 // 62))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1203, "answer": -1354}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((((54 - (36 - -27)) + -12) * 86) % -4) % 77", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1204, "answer": 75}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-95 + 15) // -5) - ((-46 * -16) - 77)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1205, "answer": -643}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((43 // -12) - 48) - ((-67 - -17) - 62)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1206, "answer": 60}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-36 + 26) + (((-19 - (-1 * (60 // -17))) + -79) - 36)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1207, "answer": -148}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((16 + 0) - -50) - 98) - ((-6 - -84) + 22)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1208, "answer": -132}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-16 + -8) + (((-30 % -18) - 25) * -19)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1209, "answer": 679}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((53 + 55) - (-24 + (89 % -50))) * ((-3 - 9) + 80)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1210, "answer": 9724}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-63 - -24) + -93) // (67 + (-79 + -5))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1211, "answer": 7}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (61 * -2) - ((95 + -19) - (-29 * (-29 + -49)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1212, "answer": 2064}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((51 - -67) * (-95 + -68)) % -86) - ((-5 + -63) - -19)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1213, "answer": -7}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((61 + (66 - -17)) * 2) + (-16 + (65 - (-17 - 45)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1214, "answer": 399}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 31 - (86 - ((-83 + -82) - (-61 * (34 + (83 * -39)))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1215, "answer": -195603}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-79 - 6) + -12) - (27 - (40 + -84))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1216, "answer": -168}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((41 + -77) - -46) + 15) + (-70 // ((-38 + -85) + 66))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1217, "answer": 26}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-86 - ((23 + (-89 + -43)) + 95)) - (-60 + (29 + -18))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1218, "answer": -23}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((31 - 96) * -25) - 27) + (72 - (41 + -82))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1219, "answer": 1711}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-46 - -41) // (((-10 - 80) + -79) - 49)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1220, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-45 % -61) + (61 - (-31 - 43))) - (31 + 0)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1221, "answer": 59}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-14 - -49) - ((1 // -69) - (16 - -92))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1222, "answer": 144}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-52 - (-89 - (-72 // 91))) - -47) + (95 * 46)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1223, "answer": 4453}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((52 - (-7 // 19)) * (66 - (46 - -35))) // (31 + -93)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1224, "answer": 12}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -44 - ((-47 - 28) - (((18 - 1) + 55) - 93))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1225, "answer": 10}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((71 * -36) % (58 - -72)) * (-92 - 59)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1226, "answer": -6644}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -29 // (-22 - ((87 + 46) - (-75 - -86)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1227, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (9 + 90) - ((-28 // (68 + -94)) * (98 + -91))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1228, "answer": 92}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-32 + (-47 * -69)) % (22 - (-96 + -71))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1229, "answer": 187}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (49 - 78) // (((-94 + 80) - 45) // 23)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1230, "answer": 9}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-83 % 2) * (((-90 + 28) + 11) - 20)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1231, "answer": -71}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (48 + -88) - (98 - ((85 + 23) + (-31 * -93)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1232, "answer": 2853}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-39 * (-99 - 67)) - (45 - ((-40 - 84) - (-26 - -6)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1233, "answer": 6325}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((40 + -58) + -4) + (86 + 42)) - 39", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1234, "answer": 67}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-55 // 49) * 3) - ((-11 * 97) - -25)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1235, "answer": 1036}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((11 - -77) + 55) + -35) % (-14 - -8)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1236, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-89 + -12) * (54 + -12)) % ((47 * (-47 + 78)) * 2)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1237, "answer": 1586}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (29 - (34 - (48 - -98))) - (41 - 71)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1238, "answer": 171}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (26 + -70) * ((41 - 2) * (-43 - 48))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1239, "answer": 156156}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-42 + (-60 - 78)) * 93) // (84 - -99)) // 30", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1240, "answer": -4}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-81 + ((94 + 4) * -22)) - (39 - 64)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1241, "answer": -2212}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-95 + -92) - ((-46 * -52) + (-82 + -35))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1242, "answer": -2462}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 9 + (((79 * 53) // -23) - ((-4 * -46) * -22))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1243, "answer": 3874}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((74 - (-91 + 28)) * -18) - -10) - (-34 * 80)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1244, "answer": 264}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((9 + (76 + 26)) // -93) + ((25 * 95) // -77)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1245, "answer": -33}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-78 + (86 % 84)) * ((17 % (92 + -13)) + -38)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1246, "answer": 1596}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-17 // ((-44 + 58) - 6)) - (-97 + (52 * (30 + 14)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1247, "answer": -2194}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-29 - 79) + ((-35 + 50) + -69)) // 79", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1248, "answer": -3}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (16 - ((-89 - -25) + 54)) - ((-71 + 76) % (-80 * -49))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1249, "answer": 21}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-98 + ((98 // -3) - -88)) - ((-42 * -12) - 75)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1250, "answer": -472}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((83 // ((-74 // -57) - -64)) - (90 - (13 * 28))) + -6", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1251, "answer": 269}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (82 + ((8 % 22) * -91)) + ((43 + 80) + (-82 - -83))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1252, "answer": -522}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((3 - 30) + -37) + (-69 + (-58 - -77))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1253, "answer": -114}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (15 * 69) + ((((-82 - 69) + -52) - (-70 + 44)) + -89)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1254, "answer": 769}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-23 + -65) * (((-4 * -84) * 31) * -96)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1255, "answer": 87994368}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-22 - (-18 * -37)) + (-45 - -51)) - 70", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1256, "answer": -752}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-74 * -55) - (42 - 63)) * (-62 - (31 + -62))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1257, "answer": -126821}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((45 - (-36 // 61)) * 93) // (61 - -7)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1258, "answer": 62}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((93 - 11) - -89) % ((-92 - -50) * 72)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1259, "answer": -2853}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((56 + -42) + 92) + ((58 // 31) - ((-38 - 54) - 34))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1260, "answer": 233}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (11 + (7 * (44 * -78))) + (98 // (-5 + -28))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1261, "answer": -24016}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-22 // 38) + 55) - ((21 - 31) * (-1 // 94))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1262, "answer": 44}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-13 * -76) % ((37 - 33) + 58)) - (-35 - (-30 * -26))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1263, "answer": 873}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-17 + -38) * (-10 - (-50 + -14))) + ((-32 - 54) // 9)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1264, "answer": -2980}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((98 - 77) % ((76 + 76) + (83 - 39))) // (-47 + 19)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1265, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((86 - 86) // ((-47 % 54) - 63)) // ((66 + 28) * -4)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1266, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((46 + 18) - (-62 + -34)) - (-35 // -68)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1267, "answer": 160}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-82 + (-34 + (17 - 41))) * 50) - (31 + 46)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1268, "answer": -7077}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-86 // 10) + (((22 - (0 + -19)) + -69) - -64)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1269, "answer": 27}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -7 + (-89 - (-28 - (41 + (-67 * -75))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1270, "answer": 4998}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-89 - (-97 + (-13 * 60))) * (-27 + 11)) - (-40 + -43)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1271, "answer": -12525}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-61 + -94) * 42) // (96 + -43)) - (-1 + (39 // 58))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1272, "answer": -122}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (47 + 90) - (((-68 - -75) * -36) - 5)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1273, "answer": 394}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (57 + -57) - (-43 * ((-99 - -38) + 72))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1274, "answer": 473}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-45 * -40) + -74) + -79) - ((14 - -61) + 90)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1275, "answer": 1482}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((39 - ((73 * 26) // 12)) - 35) // (-17 + -94)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1276, "answer": 1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-4 + -63) - (54 % 79)) - 75) + (-56 // 4)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1277, "answer": -210}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-9 - 4) - ((84 - -25) - (-2 + 54))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1278, "answer": -70}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 76 + (((16 * 83) + (0 // (-7 + -2))) + -94)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1279, "answer": 1310}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-77 + 12) + -34) % -10) + (-31 + (-33 + 23))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1280, "answer": -50}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (50 * 66) + ((-90 + (-6 // -87)) + 95)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1281, "answer": 3305}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 82 - ((58 + 79) + (-35 - (35 + -34)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1282, "answer": -19}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-63 + 12) - ((-41 // (-40 - -76)) - (47 - 68))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1283, "answer": -70}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (41 * 21) - ((-39 // (-31 - (37 - -68))) + (42 + 95))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1284, "answer": 724}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((37 + -52) - (-97 - ((97 // -30) + 32))) * -94", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1285, "answer": -10340}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (1 - (-57 - (21 // (-66 - -38)))) * ((19 + -37) - 17)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1286, "answer": -1995}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 83 + ((64 - 56) + (-82 - (-65 * -99)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1287, "answer": -6426}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((41 + 39) * 86) * 4) - ((56 + 48) - 84)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1288, "answer": 27500}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-57 - 29) + (-67 + -90)) + (-81 + ((-70 + 55) + 6))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1289, "answer": -333}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-93 - -19) % (-49 + 93)) - (-44 - (99 + 64))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1290, "answer": 221}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((67 // (2 + -37)) + -63) // (-41 // 13)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1291, "answer": 16}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((83 - 20) - (-47 - 19)) + (7 - (-37 - -62))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1292, "answer": 111}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -24 + ((-10 - (-1 + 68)) * ((54 - -24) + (32 // 42)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1293, "answer": -6030}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 23 * (-9 - ((-20 + (-97 - -74)) + (91 - 83)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1294, "answer": 598}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-93 - (62 - 34)) // ((15 * (-14 // 57)) + (-11 - 60))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1295, "answer": 1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((33 - 50) + -68) % ((11 + 96) + (71 * 41))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1296, "answer": 2933}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-60 - ((70 + 83) - (88 * 85))) // 63) - (-63 - -63)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1297, "answer": 115}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 58 + (((-43 + -89) + (-22 + -96)) * -65)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1298, "answer": 16308}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((7 - (10 + 41)) - 46) + (-46 * -99)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1299, "answer": 4464}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-32 + 87) // ((-43 // 20) // (73 + 27))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1300, "answer": -55}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 72 - (((21 * -33) * (62 + 71)) * -16)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1301, "answer": -1474632}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (53 - -37) - ((12 + 24) - ((31 + -23) - (86 - 4)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1302, "answer": -20}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-62 - 43) - -42) + (-36 // 19)) - -60", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1303, "answer": -5}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((8 + 46) - -15) // (-79 * -37)) + -58", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1304, "answer": -58}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((99 + (-85 % 12)) - 4) * ((7 + 22) - (-14 // -5))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1305, "answer": 2862}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (25 + (2 * 51)) + (4 // (-39 + -26))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1306, "answer": 126}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-59 + 54) + ((-78 - -74) - -78)) + -78", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1307, "answer": -9}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -61 // ((((79 + 66) // (-86 - -99)) % 21) + (-91 - -65))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1308, "answer": 4}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-89 - -57) + -20) * ((-90 // 50) * (-89 * 58))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1309, "answer": -536848}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (1 + 26) - (-31 + ((57 + -27) * -64))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1310, "answer": 1978}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((65 * 99) * 80) - 32) // (28 * 56)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1311, "answer": 328}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (1 + (71 - -58)) + ((-8 + 31) + -21)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1312, "answer": 132}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-20 + 71) - (-46 + -38)) + (-61 // 81)) * -60", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1313, "answer": -8040}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -84 - (-62 - (15 // (-61 + (-27 * 98))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1314, "answer": -23}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((84 + (12 * 5)) // (65 + (82 * -46))) - 22", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1315, "answer": -23}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -6 - ((-50 - -11) - (-87 - (-35 * ((28 + 19) * 69))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1316, "answer": 113451}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-16 // 91) - 82) - ((93 // 46) * 80)) + -52", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1317, "answer": -295}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (7 - -76) * ((-62 * -89) - (-38 + 32))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1318, "answer": 458492}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((85 - -53) + (-90 - 98)) + (62 + ((58 + -4) * -13))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1319, "answer": -690}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 24 + ((-62 // -14) % ((36 - 52) % 57))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1320, "answer": 28}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (98 + 88) // (17 + (((-27 * -14) - -95) * (51 + 61)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1321, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((56 + 47) + (-19 + 52)) * (16 % -32)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1322, "answer": -2176}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-41 - (((-98 * 36) - -41) + (-43 - 16))) - -38", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1323, "answer": 3543}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 11 + (-80 % (((29 - 88) + 97) + (97 % 54)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1324, "answer": 12}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 28 * (((-70 - -39) - ((-54 - 40) - 68)) - (-96 - 76))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1325, "answer": 8484}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -15 - ((-94 * -74) - (92 - ((69 * -25) + 72)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1326, "answer": -5226}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (10 + (87 + (-7 - -75))) * ((39 + 78) + 41)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1327, "answer": 26070}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -80 // ((-99 - -38) // (((24 - (-78 - -8)) % -76) - -9))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1328, "answer": -80}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (40 - ((59 + 97) + -77)) * (-58 - -62)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1329, "answer": -156}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (23 % 94) + ((-12 + (94 - 11)) - (32 * 99))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1330, "answer": -3074}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-51 - 59) % (((91 * (69 * 27)) - 43) + 98)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1331, "answer": 169478}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-49 - -89) + (16 - -51)) + (47 + (-95 * 71))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1332, "answer": -6591}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-19 - 19) + -78) - (-75 + (52 - -65))) + 22", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1333, "answer": -136}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((60 + (64 + -18)) // (-20 // 38)) * (-24 + -90)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1334, "answer": 12084}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -23 + ((-2 - -60) * ((6 % -80) - 36))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1335, "answer": -6403}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 28 * (((-94 - -93) % -27) + ((83 - -76) + -64))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1336, "answer": 2632}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-7 + (-75 % ((-18 - -68) - -53))) + (50 // (-40 + -87))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1337, "answer": 20}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (83 - (42 + 69)) * ((4 * 93) // (-20 + 8))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1338, "answer": 868}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-64 + -82) * -75) * (-72 - (-89 - 21))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1339, "answer": 416100}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-32 + (52 % 44)) - -36) - (-14 - (-52 - 67))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1340, "answer": -93}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (62 * (21 + (87 - (-56 * (5 + -98))))) - (48 * 87)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1341, "answer": -320376}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-84 - (-45 + 57)) + 71) * (-50 + 36)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1342, "answer": 350}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (4 + (49 + -26)) % ((58 + -68) + (-34 + 66))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1343, "answer": 5}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-70 + ((92 + -35) + 77)) // (48 - (65 - (72 // -36)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1344, "answer": -4}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -40 + ((88 - -81) - ((-44 - -29) + -71))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1345, "answer": 215}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 67 // ((79 * -96) - ((-12 + (15 - (-62 + 86))) + 66))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1346, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-3 - 69) - 33) + ((70 + -48) + 63)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1347, "answer": -20}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-9 + -51) + ((26 + (-29 + 12)) * -87)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1348, "answer": -843}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 11 + ((-84 - (92 - (35 - -25))) + (6 - -71))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1349, "answer": -28}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-28 * -54) - ((22 + (51 + (-10 // -22))) // 65)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1350, "answer": 1511}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (77 + ((0 - -30) - -58)) - (-43 - 13)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1351, "answer": 221}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -39 + (((42 + 31) * (-71 - -31)) - 85)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1352, "answer": -3044}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-30 * (92 - 4)) - (-83 * 46)) * (-38 + -27)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1353, "answer": -76570}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (61 * 28) + (-61 * (-16 + ((-99 + 24) - -50)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1354, "answer": 4209}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 88 % ((-2 - (60 + -49)) // (-16 - -88))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1355, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((37 + -14) % 27) + (11 + (77 * (-73 - 45)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1356, "answer": -9052}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-88 * -47) - ((37 + 90) + (-73 * 75))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1357, "answer": 9484}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-43 - (-44 - -5)) * -75) - (-34 + (51 + (-69 - -28)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1358, "answer": 324}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-76 - ((57 - -69) * -76)) - -35) - (-88 + (77 - -29))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1359, "answer": 9517}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (26 % -44) + (((-77 // 29) - (48 + -28)) - (10 // 79))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1360, "answer": -41}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-93 + 90) - -75) + ((71 * (-50 % -55)) + -59)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1361, "answer": -3537}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 88 + ((-46 * -49) - (-24 - (-84 // 70)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1362, "answer": 2364}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-91 * -69) + ((61 * 94) + ((-60 + 77) * -83))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1363, "answer": 10602}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-56 + -4) - (37 + -55)) - (-72 - -78)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1364, "answer": -48}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-60 - 7) - (12 - (80 + (-31 + 83)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1365, "answer": 53}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((((53 + 37) // 70) // (15 * 9)) - -55) * (-28 + -19)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1366, "answer": -2585}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-49 + 4) * ((98 - 38) + 20)) // (49 + -70)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1367, "answer": 171}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-41 // 89) * ((44 * ((67 - 49) - (-86 * 33))) - -53)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1368, "answer": -125717}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-38 - -87) - ((-38 * ((-13 - (-33 // -33)) - -14)) * 41)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1369, "answer": 49}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (10 + 26) * (-64 * (79 % (33 - -62)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1370, "answer": -182016}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (9 - (89 - (18 + -57))) - (((-92 * -91) + 96) // -97)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1371, "answer": -31}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 86 + (-78 - ((94 + 91) + (-78 + 77)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1372, "answer": -176}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (13 + ((62 + 92) * 55)) - (85 + -61)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1373, "answer": 8459}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((30 - 66) * -25) + ((-59 - -78) - (54 * 72))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1374, "answer": -2969}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((34 + 97) - (-61 - -55)) * 96) + ((-19 - -2) - 21)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1375, "answer": 13114}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-88 + 54) - (-99 - 70)) - -33) + -37", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1376, "answer": 131}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-7 - 86) // 33) + ((4 + -3) % (-39 - 6))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1377, "answer": -47}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-17 + (70 - -87)) % ((-56 - 48) + -3)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1378, "answer": -74}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 42 % ((61 - ((5 * (-38 * (55 * 58))) - 43)) // 18)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1379, "answer": 42}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (98 // (-67 - -83)) + (-31 + (-68 - ((36 - -68) - 43)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1380, "answer": -154}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-33 % ((41 - (28 + -36)) - (-3 - 84))) - (36 - 66)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1381, "answer": 133}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-60 + 73) * (-63 + 79)) * (59 - 74)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1382, "answer": -3120}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((5 + -23) + (-94 + (8 + (-5 - 85)))) + 86", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1383, "answer": -108}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-73 % ((-78 + 19) + -89)) - ((62 + 0) + (-9 + 93))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1384, "answer": -219}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-52 // (-41 + 85)) + (((40 % 75) + -52) - -24)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1385, "answer": 10}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 72 - (21 + ((6 - -28) + (32 - 48)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1386, "answer": 33}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (98 - (88 * (-5 + (43 - 79)))) * (-29 + (86 // -65))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1387, "answer": -114886}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (73 - (((-25 * 76) + 64) * -85)) + (-38 % -47)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1388, "answer": -156025}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-50 - 35) % ((82 - -68) + (87 % -43))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1389, "answer": 23}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -76 + (83 % (((85 // -68) + 40) * -87))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1390, "answer": -3299}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (52 - -76) - ((-44 - -65) + ((-42 + -89) + (-91 + 86)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1391, "answer": 243}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 93 - (((-75 + 19) * (42 // 85)) + 35)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1392, "answer": 58}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -52 // ((-92 - 51) + (-14 + (-71 % 41)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1393, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-37 + (((21 // 64) * 80) * 28)) - -32", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1394, "answer": -5}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (86 + (-99 + 59)) + ((-5 * 57) // ((-85 + -80) - -20))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1395, "answer": 47}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -68 + (((39 % (-42 % -40)) + (36 - 23)) - (-93 + 51))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1396, "answer": -14}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-56 + (-44 % (-81 + -38))) + (-29 * -14)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1397, "answer": 306}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-76 + ((79 - 91) // 88)) * ((34 + 38) - 5)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1398, "answer": -5159}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -6 // ((-13 // ((2 * 10) % ((33 + 78) + -75))) - -70)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1399, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-95 - -89) - ((34 - -47) + ((2 + 56) - (96 - -93)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1400, "answer": 44}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-81 * -17) - ((-55 * 97) + (-34 // (-8 - -86)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1401, "answer": 6713}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((47 * -72) + ((9 - 96) + 44)) - (60 // -46)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1402, "answer": -3425}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-70 // -38) - -22) - ((36 * (-50 * -12)) - -23)) - -39", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1403, "answer": -21561}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-88 * -45) + (66 - (58 - 86))) // -68) + -86", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1404, "answer": -146}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((56 - -87) - 30) + ((-25 - -26) * 47)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1405, "answer": 160}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 83 // (((4 - 94) * (97 * 60)) + 47)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1406, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((34 - -24) // -62) // ((64 - 46) - -36)) // -62", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1407, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-24 - (98 - ((-55 - -51) + -72))) + (-42 + -24)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1408, "answer": -264}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((5 // 60) * (43 + 22)) - (2 + 64)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1409, "answer": -66}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((65 + 14) * (92 + -44)) + (44 // 86)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1410, "answer": 3792}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((72 - 70) * ((34 - -64) // 69)) - 44", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1411, "answer": -42}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-11 // (70 * -69)) // (78 - (-12 + -92))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1412, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((52 * 96) - ((12 - (-76 - 41)) - (47 - -3))) - -11", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1413, "answer": 4924}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-44 - (44 - ((-74 * 73) + (97 // -51)))) * 36", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1414, "answer": -197712}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-35 - (99 + -31)) - (39 // -61)) % (31 + -30)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1415, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -92 % ((93 + -42) + (-98 + (((0 % -83) % -85) + -70)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1416, "answer": -92}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-79 + 72) + (57 // (-93 - -87))) + (-3 - 36)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1417, "answer": -56}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-24 + (89 // -17)) * (17 * 5)) + 99", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1418, "answer": -2451}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((65 + 6) * (-87 + (-43 - 64))) * -28", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1419, "answer": 385672}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 27 + (((1 - -58) - (83 - 15)) - (86 * 4))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1420, "answer": -326}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-11 + -95) + ((91 - (86 - 61)) - 22)) * -1", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1421, "answer": 62}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (97 + -32) - (2 + ((-50 + -49) - -48))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1422, "answer": 114}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-66 - -19) // ((-48 - (3 - -72)) + (40 + -79))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1423, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -47 - ((-79 - 55) - (-99 - ((-43 - 93) + 9)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1424, "answer": 115}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((20 + (40 * 47)) * (-3 + -68)) % -51", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1425, "answer": -5}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (71 + ((-32 + 52) - -87)) + (49 + -17)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1426, "answer": 210}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-24 + 31) + (-75 + ((-27 * -86) - -39))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1427, "answer": 2293}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-73 * 2) + (((-63 - (90 + 28)) - 71) - 32)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1428, "answer": -430}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-96 + -58) - ((26 + (-73 + 61)) - -50)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1429, "answer": -218}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((47 - ((88 + 76) + 56)) - 13) - (95 % 10)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1430, "answer": -191}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((32 - -54) * ((-92 - -13) // -41)) + 47", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1431, "answer": 133}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (27 - (((17 + 23) - (4 + 28)) * -39)) + 4", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1432, "answer": 343}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-6 * 96) // (-3 - ((-78 + (-53 * -42)) - 62))) // -10", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1433, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((1 - 74) + (((99 * -14) // 39) - 15)) * -73", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1434, "answer": 9052}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((88 + -81) - 34) - ((47 // -64) + ((17 * 94) - 53))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1435, "answer": -1571}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((11 + (40 + -95)) + (-67 * -90)) - -15", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1436, "answer": 6001}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((85 - 54) + ((66 % -66) - -23)) + 56", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1437, "answer": 110}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((66 - (-27 - ((61 - 40) - 30))) + 18) - 93", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1438, "answer": 9}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-8 + (-39 + (15 - 0))) + (-49 + 39)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1439, "answer": -42}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (58 - 16) + (((58 + -83) + 85) // ((57 + 37) % 27))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1440, "answer": 46}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((30 + 28) + (-66 - (33 + 48))) - (27 * 92)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1441, "answer": -2573}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((3 + (75 // 61)) * (-5 * -86)) + 79", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1442, "answer": 1799}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 70 - (((87 - 59) + -15) - ((-92 + 73) + -68))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1443, "answer": -30}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (92 + (-4 % -31)) * ((35 % 1) + 18)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1444, "answer": 1584}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-64 // ((-52 - 64) + -36)) - ((75 - (1 + -43)) - -50)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1445, "answer": -167}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-12 * ((-33 - -79) + (-52 * 37))) + ((-54 // -12) + 0)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1446, "answer": 22540}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((51 * -43) + (-12 - (-73 - -42))) - 30", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1447, "answer": -2204}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-93 + 66) * (33 - -32)) + -1) - 44", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1448, "answer": -1800}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 57 + (((-33 % -42) * -98) * (-21 - (73 // 32)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1449, "answer": -74325}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -71 * ((((-87 + -49) + 34) - 81) - ((-31 // -90) - -77))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1450, "answer": 18460}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-21 - -77) % (((-72 - -16) - -16) + (-72 - -44))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1451, "answer": -12}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (59 + -45) - (((-39 + 10) + (-18 // -88)) + (59 - -31))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1452, "answer": -47}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -27 - (-90 * ((17 + -1) - (79 - 52)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1453, "answer": -1017}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((55 + (94 // 23)) - -98) - ((-66 - -39) + (3 // -58))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1454, "answer": 185}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-85 // -16) + 98) * ((38 // 14) + -28)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1455, "answer": -2678}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (27 // 81) - (((39 - 62) - -13) // (-6 + -18))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1456, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((29 * (-22 + 58)) + (-78 - 78)) + (-14 + -93)) - -65", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1457, "answer": 846}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -89 - ((-4 - 64) // (51 * (-81 - -39)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1458, "answer": -89}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -16 - ((-46 * (-17 + -12)) - (-91 - 34))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1459, "answer": -1475}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((75 // (-27 - -22)) + -27) + (-1 * 51)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1460, "answer": -93}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((28 + (9 + (64 // 13))) - (65 + 6)) - (92 + -98)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1461, "answer": -24}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-5 + (-46 - -82)) * (-55 * (89 + -65))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1462, "answer": -40920}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -67 + ((66 * -98) + ((-84 * -3) + 90))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1463, "answer": -6193}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 34 + ((-32 * 26) + (-47 - (-11 % -93)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1464, "answer": -834}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (4 + 33) * (71 // ((-53 // ((19 - -17) + -33)) - 92))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1465, "answer": -37}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-2 * -60) - 47) - (-16 - -63)) - (31 - 99)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1466, "answer": 94}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((87 % -73) * (-86 * 41)) + (84 // 13)) - (66 + 21)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1467, "answer": 207953}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 18 - ((14 - 84) - (45 - (-92 * -16)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1468, "answer": -1339}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (48 + 46) - ((90 * (-56 - -74)) + 88)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1469, "answer": -1614}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (64 + (-39 - 42)) + ((-39 % (-16 + 68)) - -6)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1470, "answer": 2}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-18 + 43) - (((-68 * 26) - 86) // ((-43 - -58) + 1))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1471, "answer": 141}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (47 + -14) + (((57 - 84) - 86) // (-53 // 15))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1472, "answer": 61}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-52 // ((71 + 53) - 20)) + 95) + (85 * -71)) - -45", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1473, "answer": -5896}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((49 + (-66 - -61)) - (73 // (-65 - -6))) // 2", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1474, "answer": 23}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((41 - ((-90 + -88) + ((56 - 76) - 20))) - 33) - 29", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1475, "answer": 197}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((((78 * 90) + (71 - 32)) + -8) + (-39 - 64)) + 37", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1476, "answer": 6985}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 93 + (-48 - (-28 * ((0 - 66) + (47 - 47))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1477, "answer": -1803}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 18 * (-11 + ((87 * 47) - (-94 - (65 - 48))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1478, "answer": 75402}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-76 // (-49 - 23)) - (68 * 89)) + 31", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1479, "answer": -6020}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 57 - ((48 + 7) + ((-46 - 76) - 52))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1480, "answer": 176}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 56 - (-62 // ((63 + (88 % (-70 + -46))) // -59))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1481, "answer": -6}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((93 * 70) - (-86 - -70)) + (-70 - -71)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1482, "answer": 6527}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-66 - (-89 - (59 - 85))) + (15 - (86 + -12))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1483, "answer": -62}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-49 + (-90 + (47 + -50))) + 11) * -2) - (-46 + 38)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1484, "answer": 270}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (67 + 71) - ((-61 // 96) + (-54 - -74))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1485, "answer": 119}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (43 - (61 - 35)) - (-13 % (48 + 71))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1486, "answer": -89}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (53 - -26) * ((-95 * (80 - (-10 * 85))) - -2)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1487, "answer": -6979492}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -45 + ((78 // (-95 + 99)) + (-41 * 17))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1488, "answer": -723}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-51 + 9) + ((39 % -6) - (-21 + 96))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1489, "answer": -120}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-33 - -80) * ((-93 % (24 - -86)) - 9)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1490, "answer": 376}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (23 + (43 - 27)) % ((-57 + 54) - 59)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1491, "answer": -23}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((11 + (52 // -94)) + 6) // (-66 + -67)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1492, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-12 - ((-59 // 76) - (-43 * 80))) + (-91 - -36)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1493, "answer": -3506}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -95 * (((45 - 97) + 64) // (-5 + 9))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1494, "answer": -285}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-5 * ((-4 - -27) - (-55 - -36))) * (23 * -72)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1495, "answer": 347760}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-99 * -71) + -88) + (97 - (32 - -68))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1496, "answer": 6938}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (89 * 6) % ((-74 + (3 + -29)) - 96)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1497, "answer": -54}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (9 - (40 - (33 + -75))) - (15 + -72)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1498, "answer": -16}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (85 + (-12 // (19 - (-49 * 31)))) + -89", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1499, "answer": -5}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-36 - (19 - (-14 // -79))) * (-26 + (36 * -29))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1500, "answer": 58850}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (3 + (-70 + 81)) * (-93 + (45 * (-53 + -10)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1501, "answer": -40992}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((((81 // 10) - 53) - (28 - -92)) - (-69 + 44)) - -98", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1502, "answer": -42}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (56 % 4) - ((-34 // 12) - ((-61 // -79) // -9))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1503, "answer": 3}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 35 % ((80 // 22) * (-91 - (-31 - ((9 - -74) % -20))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1504, "answer": -196}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((94 + (-70 - (15 * (71 + 20)))) * -68) - -35", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1505, "answer": 91223}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 92 - ((40 + (84 - 45)) - (47 - -99))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1506, "answer": 159}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-18 + -55) - (-34 - ((51 - (66 % 54)) * 28))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1507, "answer": 1053}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((66 - (-49 - 19)) - 52) - 13) + (7 - -2)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1508, "answer": 78}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((6 + (-74 - -61)) // (25 + -26)) - (25 - (47 - -31))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1509, "answer": 60}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (96 // -17) % ((-46 - 89) - (50 * 46))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1510, "answer": -6}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-82 + ((11 * 70) // -64)) + -93) + -45", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1511, "answer": -233}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 32 + (((-72 // (6 + -85)) + -59) + (62 + 70))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1512, "answer": 105}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (40 * (-39 + -5)) + ((-71 - (14 + (88 - 38))) - 29)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1513, "answer": -1924}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-81 * (-33 * -22)) * (-58 * 95)) * (16 % (34 + 32))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1514, "answer": 5184336960}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (30 // -4) * ((39 * (-84 // (-33 + 39))) + (8 // 22))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1515, "answer": 4368}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-53 * (-2 % 45)) - -78) - ((-76 % 96) - 66)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1516, "answer": -2155}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -59 - (((((54 - 72) // 9) + 44) - 30) * (19 * 86))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1517, "answer": -19667}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-31 // (51 // -9)) + -41) - 83) + (-33 + -77)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1518, "answer": -229}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-9 // ((27 - 42) // 65)) - (-54 - ((73 + 77) + 42))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1519, "answer": 255}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (86 + -3) * ((18 // (-53 // -25)) - (55 // (80 - 64)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1520, "answer": 498}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((85 - -32) // (-93 + -31)) - 16) - (-61 * -83)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1521, "answer": -5080}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -60 * (((-1 + (-59 + -8)) * (62 - 5)) - -29)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1522, "answer": 230820}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((29 * 47) // (-31 - (37 * 79))) + (58 - (12 - -64))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1523, "answer": -19}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((93 + 35) - (55 + 48)) * (9 + (60 + -83))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1524, "answer": -350}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-45 + (51 + 94)) + (-8 * (-47 + 83))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1525, "answer": -188}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -40 + ((85 - 5) * (-12 - (-36 * (-34 - -17))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1526, "answer": -49960}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (3 + ((-57 + -7) + (93 + -22))) - ((-32 + -68) - 58)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1527, "answer": 168}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-50 - 79) - (-29 * -92)) - (3 + -83)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1528, "answer": -2717}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((98 + (80 + -33)) - 53) * (40 // 39)) + 87", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1529, "answer": 179}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-75 // -30) - (14 * -30)) - (33 * -73)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1530, "answer": 2831}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (1 - (-32 + 40)) - ((79 - 49) - 2)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1531, "answer": -35}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((46 % -20) // (-16 // -12)) * 51) + ((69 // -87) + -71)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1532, "answer": -786}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-85 - 76) * ((-36 // 79) - -2)) + 78", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1533, "answer": -83}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-81 * (-79 + 9)) + (-41 - (-46 + 8))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1534, "answer": 5667}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (82 - 66) * ((32 * 49) + ((-4 - 54) - -85))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1535, "answer": 25520}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-87 * (53 - (-65 - -23))) - ((-87 + -24) // -3)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1536, "answer": -8302}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((28 - 6) + -87) + ((-32 // -58) * -96)) - -20", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1537, "answer": -45}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((94 * 14) * (38 * -92)) - ((97 - -18) * -43)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1538, "answer": -4595791}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (9 + (-37 % ((4 + -2) - -66))) - 63", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1539, "answer": -23}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-86 * -72) // (62 - -14)) + (-41 * -86)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1540, "answer": 3607}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-52 // (-55 * (-24 % -53))) // (10 - 23)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1541, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-65 + 96) // (57 - -82)) + (-92 + -73)) // (-54 * -28)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1542, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -76 + (((-84 + -98) // 95) - ((-72 - (51 * 33)) * 2))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1543, "answer": 3432}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-49 - (-55 + 48)) - 53) * (14 * -96)) - -30", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1544, "answer": 127710}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-32 * -57) + ((-62 // (-57 + (-47 + 36))) + -35)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1545, "answer": 1789}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((11 * -11) // (93 - 37)) + (19 + 42)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1546, "answer": 58}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-32 + 32) // (-20 - (-68 - (29 - -16)))) // -35", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1547, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-91 - (-34 + -21)) + (((67 - 20) % -13) % 90)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1548, "answer": 49}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-71 * -64) - (-60 + ((98 - 38) + 58))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1549, "answer": 4486}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((16 + (99 - 2)) * 96) - (-37 + 71)) + (66 + 65)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1550, "answer": 10945}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-56 - -92) - (43 + ((-81 + 22) - -9))) * (68 + 39)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1551, "answer": 4601}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 56 - ((-89 - ((83 * 63) + -50)) + -91)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1552, "answer": 5415}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((85 + 40) // (-31 - (-15 - -41))) - (-96 - -90)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1553, "answer": 3}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((32 // (84 + ((22 - 30) * (32 % -82)))) - 9) * -11", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1554, "answer": 99}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((72 * -7) + -33) + ((-86 * 37) + -46)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1555, "answer": -3765}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (22 * (16 + 81)) + (-96 + (((65 + 53) + -68) * -62))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1556, "answer": -1062}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((60 + 46) - 49) - 9) + ((96 % (-21 + -19)) * 24)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1557, "answer": -528}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-73 + -29) + ((-35 - -3) + (-90 - -77))) + (82 // -35)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1558, "answer": -150}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-47 // (52 - 16)) * (34 - (-39 - 46))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1559, "answer": -238}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (66 + 69) % (((1 * -59) - 46) * -46)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1560, "answer": 135}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (83 - ((-57 // (-96 - -52)) - -41)) * -55", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1561, "answer": -2255}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -83 % ((((-97 // 41) + -78) + -24) + -51)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1562, "answer": -83}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-26 * (86 - (42 + -25))) + ((65 // -78) - 51)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1563, "answer": -1846}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (24 - (((-50 + -19) + -20) + ((74 - -74) - -91))) + -99", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1564, "answer": -225}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 18 % ((-99 - ((-15 - 91) - 51)) - -2)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1565, "answer": 18}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -15 - (77 // (12 - ((9 + -31) * (-81 - -96))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1566, "answer": -15}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-77 - 82) - (81 + -42)) - ((15 + 39) - (-74 + 3))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1567, "answer": -323}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((((34 + 58) * -96) + (98 - 44)) * (11 - 8)) - 41", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1568, "answer": -26375}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-3 + (-59 - 0)) * ((36 - -40) // 39)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1569, "answer": -62}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (21 + (((-6 + -92) - -5) // 52)) % (-53 % -7)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1570, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 46 - (((78 + 53) - (-67 // -94)) - (-66 // 11))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1571, "answer": -91}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-2 - -96) * -22) - (42 + (95 - (-64 + -81)))) - 19", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1572, "answer": -2369}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((18 - 25) - 17) - ((72 + 92) + (25 + -24))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1573, "answer": -189}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-75 % 39) * (-28 % (56 + 83))) - (-64 - 12)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1574, "answer": 409}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-63 * 55) * (((16 + -86) * (85 - 88)) - -6)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1575, "answer": -748440}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (42 + -11) - (((-88 * -18) - 12) - (-99 - 48))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1576, "answer": -1688}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (28 // -99) + ((88 * (-83 - 62)) - 3)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1577, "answer": -12764}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-86 + 18) + -56) * (-65 - (21 - -54))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1578, "answer": 17360}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (85 * -28) + (-85 + (25 - ((-58 + (84 + 16)) + -38)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1579, "answer": -2444}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-81 // 39) - ((24 * -83) - (-10 + 44))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1580, "answer": 2023}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-76 - (48 * ((57 * -54) + (-72 - 69)))) - (-19 + -52)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1581, "answer": 154507}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 92 * (91 + ((13 - (46 - -65)) - (-88 + -91)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1582, "answer": 15824}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 11 - (((-98 + (-34 + 80)) * (30 - 47)) * -20)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1583, "answer": 17691}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((66 + -63) * 46) // ((52 * 43) + 47)) % (6 + -11)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1584, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((97 // -70) * 6) * (60 // 85)) + 32", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1585, "answer": 32}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-20 - (-45 + (-90 - -33))) - (-88 * -60)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1586, "answer": -5198}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((76 // (-82 - (-24 + -45))) + 87) + (13 - -34)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1587, "answer": 128}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-61 * 8) // (4 + ((-90 + 91) + (15 - -50)))) + 51", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1588, "answer": 44}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-23 - 39) - (((-54 + -18) + (-2 - (4 - -64))) + 39)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1589, "answer": 41}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((15 * 14) * -29) + (1 - (15 - 59))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1590, "answer": -6045}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-6 + (-59 + -47)) - ((87 + (53 + -91)) - 39)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1591, "answer": -122}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-89 + (62 % 80)) + ((71 - 54) - (-40 * -74))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1592, "answer": -2970}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 19 + ((54 + (-63 + (-24 + 81))) * 14)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1593, "answer": 691}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (76 * (-56 * (4 + 84))) + (((-19 - -31) * 79) - -78)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1594, "answer": -373502}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-78 - 71) - ((13 - -19) + (((-97 % -59) + 7) - 95))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1595, "answer": -55}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -79 + ((-13 + (85 + -53)) + ((13 * 63) - (-91 - 13)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1596, "answer": 863}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 27 // (96 - (((-66 // (53 - 41)) % -87) - -9))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1597, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-40 - (-87 - -97)) * (-26 + 74)) - 60) * (-22 * 98)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1598, "answer": 5303760}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -47 - (((-99 - ((-67 + -91) * (10 * -88))) + 30) + 57)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1599, "answer": 139005}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-81 - (61 - 58)) + (-43 + ((40 + -8) // -11))) - 95", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1600, "answer": -225}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-88 - -7) + 0) * (-91 + (5 + 25))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1601, "answer": 4941}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (65 * (2 * ((-81 * 40) - 0))) * ((-32 + -88) % 79)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1602, "answer": -16005600}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((84 + -44) + 70) + -50) * (-21 + 49)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1603, "answer": 1680}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-94 * (1 - 26)) + (((-14 * -16) * (-44 - -58)) + 63)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1604, "answer": 5549}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -81 + ((-2 + ((-66 - 1) + -52)) * (-72 // 18))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1605, "answer": 403}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (50 * (61 * -52)) + ((-43 + -21) - ((-82 + -96) // 89))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1606, "answer": -158662}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (65 + ((-8 - -37) + (64 * 96))) + 39", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1607, "answer": 6277}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-96 % -61) + -70) - -77) % ((14 // -43) % (58 + -98))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1608, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((94 // 45) + 43) % ((45 - -52) * -77)) + -56", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1609, "answer": -7480}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((((2 * -88) + (-38 - 8)) - 72) * -54) - (78 - -63)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1610, "answer": 15735}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-80 % -34) - 19) * ((78 - 53) - (-99 - 14))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1611, "answer": -4278}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -11 + ((83 // 93) + (-53 * (11 - 80)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1612, "answer": 3646}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 66 + ((-9 - 35) - (34 + (86 + -98)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1613, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (12 - (98 + -71)) // ((38 - ((41 - 41) // -79)) - 87)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1614, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-57 * 81) + 77) * (-2 * ((82 * (93 + 98)) - -13))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1615, "answer": 142329000}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-82 % (56 - -60)) - 31) * (-55 + 31)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1616, "answer": -72}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((69 + -75) * 32) - (-56 - ((-99 % -86) * -54))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1617, "answer": 566}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (38 - -67) - ((70 - -60) + (-35 * (-28 * (25 - -28))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1618, "answer": -51965}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (92 * 35) // (-83 - (((80 - -97) * (89 - 61)) - 89))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1619, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (63 + -46) // (-29 + (-43 + (-66 % 84)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1620, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((79 + -73) * (-4 * 84)) + (-89 % (29 // -76))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1621, "answer": -2016}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (5 + (2 * -49)) - (75 - (-11 // (13 - 17)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1622, "answer": -166}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((57 - 38) - -42) // (97 - (76 + (67 % -58)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1623, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 7 - ((21 + (((-59 - 50) + 92) + (-69 - -92))) // -32)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1624, "answer": 8}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((59 * (1 // -58)) + (46 * -79)) - -48", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1625, "answer": -3645}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((29 + -85) + (4 // 43)) - (7 + 1)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1626, "answer": -64}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -1 - ((-60 + -78) + (((-7 + -84) - -22) + 49))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1627, "answer": 157}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((13 * 11) - 1) // (76 - ((84 - -42) - 46))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1628, "answer": -36}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-22 * (-57 + 17)) + (-66 + (-1 * (12 // -69)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1629, "answer": 815}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-34 + (6 * 71)) * (90 * (68 * 43))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1630, "answer": 103158720}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-74 + 74) * 32) - (37 + (((90 * 60) * 5) + -62))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1631, "answer": -26975}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (83 + -78) + ((((-48 - 44) - (-38 // -65)) // 85) + -27)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1632, "answer": -24}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (71 + -85) - ((-42 // (-33 + -48)) - (77 + -38))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1633, "answer": 25}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 81 - (((-92 // -4) + 85) + (-5 + 20))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1634, "answer": -42}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-15 + 17) // 3) - 51) - (((-48 - -7) - -38) + 12)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1635, "answer": -60}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-1 % 87) // (-83 // 11)) * -46) + (-67 + -79)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1636, "answer": 360}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-94 + 38) + 79) * (47 - (59 + -21))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1637, "answer": 207}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -12 + ((53 // -63) - (((2 * -22) // 15) + (-71 + -38)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1638, "answer": 99}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-38 + -5) + (-31 + -53)) - (-68 - -26)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1639, "answer": -85}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-36 * (7 - -70)) + ((-20 - -45) + 84)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1640, "answer": -2663}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((69 - 98) * 18) * -42) + (75 * -95)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1641, "answer": 14799}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (27 - (((-63 - -69) - -79) - -5)) - 87", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1642, "answer": -150}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (43 + ((-59 - -46) * -7)) % (((11 * 30) + 18) + -33)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1643, "answer": 134}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-71 - ((65 % -58) + 66)) - (78 + 36)) * 6", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1644, "answer": -1200}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((14 % 19) + ((48 - 11) - (75 - -17))) // 5", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1645, "answer": -9}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-99 // -71) + ((66 - -88) + (-60 + 13))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1646, "answer": 108}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -93 // (((-90 * -93) - -61) + ((87 + -67) * (-20 - -52)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1647, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-69 % (-93 // 55)) - -22) + (47 - (97 + -44))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1648, "answer": 15}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (27 // (-91 - (-68 - (-3 + 60)))) - (-10 + 82)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1649, "answer": -72}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((85 // (54 * (48 * 86))) * 62) // 25", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1650, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (85 - (58 + -9)) + (-39 + (-56 + -61))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1651, "answer": -120}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((80 + (34 + (-99 + -26))) // (22 + 77)) * (-9 + -42)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1652, "answer": 51}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (10 + -77) * (((21 // 2) // -76) - -87)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1653, "answer": -5762}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (31 // (-48 - (-90 // -74))) - (26 + (-60 // (-74 - -9)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1654, "answer": -27}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((81 + -77) + ((82 // 96) + -32)) * (4 - 23)) - -48", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1655, "answer": 580}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-62 + -46) * (77 + -60)) - (-58 * (63 % -72))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1656, "answer": -2358}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-11 // 44) - 72) - ((-54 - 88) * ((-85 - -3) - -53))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1657, "answer": -4191}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-4 + (0 + -37)) - ((-82 + (37 - (-30 + 2))) + 76)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1658, "answer": -100}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-39 * (25 * 72)) * ((44 - -21) // (68 // 44))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1659, "answer": -4563000}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (69 - -81) - ((-55 + 3) + (31 + (70 % 3)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1660, "answer": 170}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((((-83 + -19) % 88) - -29) - 22) - -88", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1661, "answer": 169}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-55 - 61) + 69) * (-5 - (10 * (-81 - -80)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1662, "answer": -235}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((((-30 + -95) + 46) // (48 - (52 + -45))) * 52) - -17", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1663, "answer": -87}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-84 - 23) + (-64 * -95)) + -35) - (12 % -59)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1664, "answer": 5985}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -81 + (((-65 * (-61 - (-81 % -48))) + 47) - (93 + 84))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1665, "answer": 1609}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((4 + -90) + (-44 + -81)) * -57) + (26 - 24)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1666, "answer": 12029}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 55 * ((13 + 67) + ((18 + -13) - 79))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1667, "answer": 330}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((((-39 + 64) + -46) // 62) * 76) - ((-70 + 55) * -76)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1668, "answer": -1216}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-51 // -92) * (-53 - -40)) - (-62 + (-59 % -69))) - 51", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1669, "answer": 70}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (99 + (25 + -3)) - ((45 + 64) - 17)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1670, "answer": 29}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (83 - (-99 + (8 - 44))) - ((-21 // -20) - 40)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1671, "answer": 257}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-23 * 47) - (52 * 16)) // ((77 + -91) + -34)) + -15", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1672, "answer": 24}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 5 // ((-19 * 79) + (21 + (-90 - 51)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1673, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((58 // -52) - (13 - -79)) + (63 // ((46 - 79) - -2))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1674, "answer": -97}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-87 - (52 - 20)) - (-54 - (-10 - -71))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1675, "answer": -4}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((6 + 73) + (10 + (-39 - -79))) + -19", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1676, "answer": 110}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-10 * -27) - 6) - ((-23 * ((-25 - 91) * -43)) - -21)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1677, "answer": 114967}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-21 - (2 - 46)) + ((81 - -33) + ((-27 // -42) // 48))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1678, "answer": 137}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((35 - 95) + (-62 + -42)) // (52 + (29 // 8))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1679, "answer": -3}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((48 * (-74 * -36)) + -59) + -73) - -97", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1680, "answer": 127837}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-84 + (-70 + (95 + -88))) + ((-22 + 33) * (-50 + -26))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1681, "answer": -983}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((21 + 50) % (-67 - -90)) + (-97 + -89)) // (-28 - 46)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1682, "answer": 2}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-62 * 86) - 57) * (46 + (-92 - (89 + -8)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1683, "answer": 684403}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-47 * 88) - ((1 % -8) + (-51 + -15))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1684, "answer": -4063}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((43 * 11) * -79) // ((-33 + 81) + ((-51 + -33) - 79))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1685, "answer": 324}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-78 - -81) - (39 * 41)) * ((-47 * -24) + -53)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1686, "answer": -1715700}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (72 + (-91 - (-50 + -20))) + (-25 - -53)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1687, "answer": 79}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (68 + (-95 % (-40 + 70))) + ((30 * 90) % 78)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1688, "answer": 141}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((((-91 + (82 * 82)) + -63) // (-2 - 93)) + 50) - -87", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1689, "answer": 67}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 66 * (((-83 - 20) + (-51 // -90)) * -22)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1690, "answer": 149556}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-60 // (38 * -6)) - (-58 + (44 * 57))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1691, "answer": -2450}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-53 - 15) - (87 + 93)) % (-49 - (-65 - 34))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1692, "answer": 2}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-65 + -95) - (-15 - (47 // -72))) * -44", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1693, "answer": 6424}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -41 // (-43 - (-35 - ((13 - -82) - 88)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1694, "answer": 41}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 72 + (((-97 * 13) + (-63 + 99)) - ((93 - -19) + -36))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1695, "answer": -1229}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -55 // (((-85 - -79) + -55) % (89 - ((-56 + -39) * -92)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1696, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-88 + (39 - -24)) * ((49 // 90) // 98)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1697, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 17 // ((70 + -66) * ((-4 % -85) + 13))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1698, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((87 + 99) + (22 // 65)) + (((-33 % 6) + -72) % 60)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1699, "answer": 237}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-87 * -1) + ((38 - (-60 - 74)) * (62 + -62))) - -13", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1700, "answer": 100}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-53 - ((54 + -89) + (((1 % 95) + 37) + -27))) + 83", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1701, "answer": 54}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((25 - -36) - (16 * (-52 // -74))) * (-78 + -77)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1702, "answer": -9455}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 36 - (((-39 * (77 + 42)) + 7) - 91)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1703, "answer": 4761}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 72 - (17 // (25 * ((62 + (54 // -61)) + (-73 - 51))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1704, "answer": 73}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((54 - -18) // 89) - (27 - -73)) + (-55 * (27 - 0))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1705, "answer": -1585}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-43 - (-53 * -58)) - (-7 + ((-63 + -71) - (-54 * -3)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1706, "answer": -2814}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-50 // -50) // 90) * (78 - ((-48 // (-24 % -22)) + 14))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1707, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-96 - -30) - 19) // (-57 - (-4 - 58))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1708, "answer": -17}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((57 - 97) - -19) % -51) * (((-34 - 60) + 80) - -53)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1709, "answer": -819}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-59 * (7 * -40)) * -31) // (16 // (22 + -18))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1710, "answer": -128030}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (46 + -60) // (8 // (3 % (39 + -78)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1711, "answer": 14}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((68 // -5) - (-61 - (-70 - -81))) + -17", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1712, "answer": 41}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-61 * 52) + (((-40 - 12) - -37) - (72 - 85))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1713, "answer": -3174}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (60 + ((-89 + 11) + -3)) + (-14 % 70)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1714, "answer": 35}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (66 + (((-50 + -47) - 86) - -72)) * (68 * 38)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1715, "answer": -116280}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -30 * ((-83 + 65) * (-54 // (-75 + -55)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1716, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((83 + -4) - 38) - (12 + (38 - 28))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1717, "answer": 19}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-73 + (36 - -16)) // ((0 * -20) + (93 // -65))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1718, "answer": 10}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -89 // ((46 + ((64 + 35) // 23)) - (-19 - (99 + 89)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1719, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((92 - -20) - (53 + 12)) - (-44 - -24)) * 69", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1720, "answer": 4623}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 57 * ((-62 * -54) + (-50 % (-95 // -21)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1721, "answer": 190950}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -88 // ((95 - ((48 // 77) * 35)) + (67 - (32 + 79)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1722, "answer": -2}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 89 // (-85 % (11 - ((-94 - 89) - 77)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1723, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-84 + -98) - ((92 - (39 - -13)) - (40 * (-51 - -75)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1724, "answer": 738}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-16 * (-30 // -37)) - (41 * (-9 + 42))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1725, "answer": -1353}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (58 + -56) * ((-84 + ((37 + 79) - (-58 - 18))) * 94)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1726, "answer": 20304}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-54 + 43) - ((73 + -47) // (24 + (92 // -78)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1727, "answer": -12}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (62 + (-54 + 2)) + ((-36 + ((99 + -72) + -99)) - -80)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1728, "answer": -18}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-48 - -42) + ((-74 + (-10 - -52)) + 19)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1729, "answer": -19}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (36 * ((82 + 96) + (4 * 24))) - ((-75 - 67) - -88)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1730, "answer": 9918}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-98 + (68 * -31)) + (98 - (60 + -67))) - 20", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1731, "answer": -2121}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((18 - 29) - (-9 - 52)) - ((39 - 78) * (-10 * 70))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1732, "answer": -27250}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (84 * 88) - ((-3 // -5) * ((96 - -56) - 57))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1733, "answer": 7392}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-64 * ((-47 + -21) + (-12 // -16))) % (55 * -30)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1734, "answer": -598}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((96 - (89 + -23)) - -65) - ((14 + (61 + 22)) - -63)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1735, "answer": -65}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-83 + 96) * (47 - 59)) % ((-94 * 44) - (42 // 53))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1736, "answer": -156}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((44 // -9) + 76) - (((-29 + -80) - 31) - -50)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1737, "answer": 161}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((6 * (-37 - -26)) + (33 - 62)) + (-47 // 3)) % 88", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1738, "answer": 65}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-2 + ((-32 + -25) + (-97 % 55))) // (70 * (-97 + -16))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1739, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -91 // ((-64 - 18) - (2 - (-25 // 42)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1740, "answer": 1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -95 + (((37 + -35) // ((98 - -43) // -99)) // (71 % -89))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1741, "answer": -95}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((59 * 53) % (-32 - 91)) - (42 - (7 - -39))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1742, "answer": -67}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-5 + -96) + (-99 * (-88 // (85 + 0)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1743, "answer": 97}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (52 - ((-95 * -8) - 0)) - ((43 + -33) * (13 // 39))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1744, "answer": -708}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((46 - -86) + 29) - ((68 - -69) + (-58 + 7))) // 65", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1745, "answer": 1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -71 * ((-4 - 77) // (-87 - (-30 + -24)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1746, "answer": -142}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (54 - (1 // 24)) - ((9 * 44) - (-4 + -57))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1747, "answer": -403}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -3 - ((-70 - -17) + ((23 // -64) + (9 // 97)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1748, "answer": 51}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-68 + 56) - (-15 % (-44 // (13 - -92)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1749, "answer": -12}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((0 // -22) + (76 - -16)) * ((54 - 12) - -16)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1750, "answer": 5336}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -40 - ((-98 + 26) % (-64 - (-14 - 87)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1751, "answer": -42}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-57 * 80) - (-99 // ((1 + (69 * -52)) - -76))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1752, "answer": -4560}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (64 + (63 + (27 % -59))) // (98 // -30)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1753, "answer": -24}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((43 % -17) * ((-56 * -53) // 50)) // 72) - (-56 - 75)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1754, "answer": 124}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-74 // 4) - (29 - ((-5 - 58) - (15 - -82)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1755, "answer": -208}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (36 // (-7 + -21)) + (-33 - (17 - -21))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1756, "answer": -73}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (96 * ((-8 + 98) + -63)) + ((36 + 88) // 91)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1757, "answer": 2593}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (19 + (-8 + 49)) + (((-33 + -25) * 55) - (-90 // -14))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1758, "answer": -3136}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-43 - (-68 + 36)) % -44) * (-78 + -82)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1759, "answer": 1760}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (65 - 34) * (((-90 + 32) * ((43 - -82) + -9)) + -55)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1760, "answer": -210273}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-97 + ((-52 + -19) % 76)) // -83) % (-53 * -68)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1761, "answer": 1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((70 - -45) * -16) - (24 + (-74 - 32))) + 45", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1762, "answer": -1713}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-51 % -25) + -28) - ((-77 - 89) - 23)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1763, "answer": 160}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((52 - ((-20 - -42) + -46)) // (-65 + 51)) * 55", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1764, "answer": -330}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-32 % -12) + -86) * (77 + (-71 + (37 + (23 + -41))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1765, "answer": -2350}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 37 - ((-58 + -75) - (39 - (((-26 - -56) // 67) * -24)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1766, "answer": 209}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((50 + -5) - 13) - (44 * ((-15 - 63) // 82))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1767, "answer": 76}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (33 + (52 - -86)) + ((-81 * 13) + ((-64 - -23) + 36))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1768, "answer": -887}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-79 * 19) // (-15 // (((-74 + -31) - -47) - (28 - 95)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1769, "answer": 750}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-78 + (86 - -44)) - 64) - -92) - -46", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1770, "answer": 126}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((99 - -79) + 48) + (57 - 26)) * (-29 - (48 * -97))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1771, "answer": 1189139}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((14 + 20) + (-5 * (-62 - 44))) * 9", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1772, "answer": 5076}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-4 - -77) - ((94 - 85) - 19)) - (97 - 72)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1773, "answer": 58}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (73 * 2) + (92 + ((-68 + (50 - -79)) + -97))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1774, "answer": 202}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-21 * -65) % ((-68 * -37) + 86)) - 10", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1775, "answer": 1355}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (77 + (((29 // 84) * -68) * -89)) + -27", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1776, "answer": 50}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -65 * ((83 * (-47 + 3)) - (-12 * (-47 - -2)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1777, "answer": 272480}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-79 + -44) * (((-46 + -9) - -38) - (81 - -98))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1778, "answer": 24108}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-76 + -6) - 63) + (((-77 // 67) + -14) % (46 + -52))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1779, "answer": -149}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-74 * (-25 - -36)) + ((69 - -65) * (21 - 25))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1780, "answer": -1350}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-59 - ((5 * -98) * -12)) * (-24 // -54)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1781, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -3 * (((81 + 75) - 6) + (-91 % (60 + (-17 - 63))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1782, "answer": -417}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-32 - -89) + -4) - (-90 // (72 // 44))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1783, "answer": 143}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -65 - ((-97 - ((25 + 8) + -46)) % ((31 + -73) - -32))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1784, "answer": -61}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-70 // 36) - 94) + ((-45 - -94) // ((8 // 27) - 3))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1785, "answer": -113}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((46 // (-55 - ((96 + -30) // -18))) // 94) + -10", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1786, "answer": -11}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (38 - 92) + ((26 - -68) * (-31 - -49))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1787, "answer": 1638}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-72 * (-30 - 99)) + 85) - (-48 * -21)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1788, "answer": 8365}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (30 - ((41 % 21) + (67 - 92))) + -8", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1789, "answer": 27}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-45 % 4) - (((-96 + -35) * -75) + (84 - (55 - -96)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1790, "answer": -9755}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -10 + ((-94 - -52) - ((-65 + -10) - ((-89 // -32) + -82)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1791, "answer": -57}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-78 // 57) - (86 - (((19 - -65) + -98) - -31))) * 95", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1792, "answer": -6745}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -94 + (82 // ((((45 + -44) + -59) * -30) + -4))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1793, "answer": -94}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-84 + (((-74 // 63) - -63) - -63)) + 93", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1794, "answer": 133}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((51 + ((91 + 0) + -34)) - 48) * (-47 - -53)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1795, "answer": 360}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (27 - (-63 - -52)) - ((-32 - 78) - 66)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1796, "answer": 214}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (8 // -74) // (37 // (-90 + (-21 - ((-74 + 77) + -2))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1797, "answer": 1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 22 + (-61 - (((78 + 68) + -56) - -85))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1798, "answer": -214}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -91 * ((1 - (85 * -65)) + (47 + -7))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1799, "answer": -506506}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-97 // (20 + 22)) - 55) // (-92 - -84)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1800, "answer": 7}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-65 + ((-93 // 19) - -44)) - (-77 * -51)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1801, "answer": -3953}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-58 + (-72 // (39 + -2))) + (91 + 31)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1802, "answer": 62}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 68 * (((-52 - -69) + (-35 - -19)) - (91 + 5))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1803, "answer": -6460}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (46 + (41 // (22 + -98))) + (-34 % -21)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1804, "answer": 32}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-62 + (95 + (-24 * -66))) // (66 - 2)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1805, "answer": 25}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-53 * -45) - (((-63 - 88) // 71) + 87)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1806, "answer": 2301}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((22 - -53) - -3) + (-46 // 73)) + -53", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1807, "answer": 24}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-42 - -66) - 21) % ((67 + 20) - 55)) + -23", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1808, "answer": -20}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (74 // (-30 - ((50 * 39) * -10))) - (-2 - (-66 * -72))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1809, "answer": 4754}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-18 - ((-56 - (39 * 4)) // 94)) + 80", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1810, "answer": 65}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((((43 + 10) + (-67 + -45)) // 19) * -2) - -84", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1811, "answer": 92}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-33 - -93) // 31) // (13 - 69)) - 43", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1812, "answer": -44}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (47 - (26 + ((-78 // 12) * -23))) - -88", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1813, "answer": -52}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((1 - (-49 + -16)) + -41) % (39 + -31)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1814, "answer": 1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-89 - 30) * (-69 // -42)) % (((-29 - 11) - -52) * -62)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1815, "answer": -119}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-56 + (-57 * ((76 + 91) // (-84 % (-95 - 41))))) // 33", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1816, "answer": 1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (91 - 83) * (((52 - -71) + (-99 - 33)) - 34)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1817, "answer": -344}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-68 - ((4 + -99) + (49 + -76))) * (46 * 93)) % 90", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1818, "answer": 72}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-64 - 76) // ((17 * ((0 + -97) // 39)) * (-23 - 40))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1819, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((0 * -37) * (-87 - -94)) + 53) - 51", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1820, "answer": 2}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-36 + (-69 - -75)) % ((-78 + -75) * (-18 - (70 + 55)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1821, "answer": 21849}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((29 - -63) - 95) * ((-95 // -51) + 63)) + (71 * -96)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1822, "answer": -7008}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-17 * (-28 // 6)) + ((15 + -17) + -3)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1823, "answer": 80}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((4 - 11) - 14) + (84 - -86)) + (-85 - (-31 // 65))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1824, "answer": 65}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -64 % (((77 + ((-64 - (32 + 15)) - 53)) + 97) * -26)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1825, "answer": -64}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-63 + -91) - (((28 - -32) - 77) * -16)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1826, "answer": -426}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-8 - (6 - (-59 // -43))) % (17 - -95)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1827, "answer": 99}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-59 + (98 * 44)) + (42 - (-72 + 41))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1828, "answer": 4326}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (61 * (62 * (-11 * 45))) + (-26 % 71)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1829, "answer": -1872045}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -91 * (19 + ((-85 // -32) * ((-93 * -86) - -78)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1830, "answer": -1471561}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((18 - -77) - (-77 - (-48 + -67))) + 46", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1831, "answer": 103}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-10 - (-67 - (68 + -32))) // (-97 // 28)) * (12 - 93)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1832, "answer": 1944}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-20 - -2) + (-21 - ((-63 + (8 * -43)) - 63))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1833, "answer": 431}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-72 - (-14 // (-98 * -6))) * ((88 - -20) // 26)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1834, "answer": -284}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-10 + (-78 + 26)) + ((-58 * -18) - 94)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1835, "answer": 888}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (72 + -53) * ((-99 // 31) % (8 * 81))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1836, "answer": 12236}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-66 // -29) + -80) - (((40 * 14) + 31) * -30)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1837, "answer": 17652}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-79 - 70) // -59) - (64 - (-7 - (-90 + (-72 // 31))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1838, "answer": 24}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-67 * -39) // (-30 + -46)) + -21) * (-21 - 86)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1839, "answer": 5992}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-71 + (-77 + -13)) // 64) + (-35 * 55)) - 89", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1840, "answer": -2017}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-34 + 48) * ((3 + 69) // ((65 - -77) + 97))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1841, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 72 - ((40 // (36 * (19 // -36))) - -99)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1842, "answer": -25}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-21 + (-13 - (29 % 29))) - (86 * (36 // (51 * 8)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1843, "answer": -34}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 4 - (((-11 * -74) + (-88 % -53)) - (-58 + (-20 * -49)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1844, "answer": 147}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((86 + (-36 + -92)) + (82 + (-86 - -20))) + (-98 // -38)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1845, "answer": -24}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (83 - 87) * ((-85 - (-58 + (79 // -48))) - -73)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1846, "answer": -192}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-79 // (-46 * -23)) + 22) * (-38 + (93 - (92 + -74)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1847, "answer": 777}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((((92 - -73) + 62) // 94) * ((95 + -9) - 76)) - 84", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1848, "answer": -64}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (85 - (((49 + (63 - 20)) * (-6 - -97)) // 61)) - -69", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1849, "answer": 17}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-12 * -42) * ((81 // -69) - (21 + -57))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1850, "answer": 17136}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((21 + (20 - 54)) - 95) + -85) // (20 - (7 - -72))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1851, "answer": 3}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 42 - ((58 // ((-66 - -48) + (-35 + 24))) + 26)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1852, "answer": 18}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-13 + -41) - (15 - (44 * -72))) - -98", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1853, "answer": -3139}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (73 - (-9 // 20)) // ((97 + -65) % -45)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1854, "answer": -6}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-68 + 1) + (-1 + (((17 - -33) // 2) + 71))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1855, "answer": 28}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 0 + ((((12 - 59) - 77) * -69) * (48 // -6))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1856, "answer": -68448}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-17 // -85) - ((5 + (-62 + 0)) + -81)) + (23 + -97)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1857, "answer": 64}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-88 + 67) * (((-27 + -45) - 80) * 92)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1858, "answer": 293664}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 59 % (((-26 + 39) + ((-43 + -93) % -97)) + (-72 // 90))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1859, "answer": -22}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-96 - ((-88 - -62) * (-5 - -81))) - (22 + 85)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1860, "answer": 1773}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((((83 * -37) + -40) + 71) - 58) + -15) - -40", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1861, "answer": -3073}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-76 - (-16 + (-69 - (28 + 8)))) + (97 + -60)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1862, "answer": 82}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-18 + ((42 + -13) % -17)) * 91) + (-64 + 40)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1863, "answer": -2117}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-74 - -65) % (52 - -4)) * (30 % -74)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1864, "answer": -2068}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-3 - 64) - -88) - (((-41 - 88) % -1) - -95)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1865, "answer": -74}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((95 + 89) + -5) - ((98 % 19) + 20)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1866, "answer": 156}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -8 + (14 // (-93 + ((-84 + 29) // 19)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1867, "answer": -9}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((94 // 67) * 24) + (24 - (-44 + -74))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1868, "answer": 166}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((36 + -95) // 99) - (14 + ((-22 - 29) - -16))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1869, "answer": 20}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-1 - (-58 // 45)) % -55) // ((98 % 93) + (76 + 36))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1870, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-52 - 43) + ((15 + (10 + -35)) * (-97 - 15))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1871, "answer": 1025}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-63 // (-82 + 81)) * -47) * ((87 - 41) - (22 * 7))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1872, "answer": 319788}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (55 - -67) // ((85 + 30) - ((5 * 72) % (-32 - 33)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1873, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-54 + (78 // -14)) * -5) * (-33 - (-11 // (76 - 35)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1874, "answer": -9600}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-48 - 48) - (((-16 + (10 + -34)) - 99) * -97)) * -19", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1875, "answer": 258001}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-85 + 89) - 22) % ((82 + -13) * -11)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1876, "answer": -18}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-80 - 51) * (-38 - (((-53 + 23) + -46) - 4))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1877, "answer": -5502}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((87 + -47) + ((81 * -54) - (65 + (24 * -73)))) - -72", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1878, "answer": -2575}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((10 // 56) // (26 - -72)) + (-57 - -85)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1879, "answer": 28}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-70 - -26) + (((-91 - -4) - -55) - (9 + 49))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1880, "answer": -134}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-52 + -92) - (92 // ((-75 - -31) + -52))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1881, "answer": -143}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-80 * -84) * (40 - -93)) * (16 - ((-44 + -79) // 3))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1882, "answer": 50944320}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-12 * (-91 + (50 - -49))) - (-52 + 6)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1883, "answer": -50}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-28 + -3) - ((13 - -59) * ((11 % -38) - 43))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1884, "answer": 5009}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((90 - 2) * ((-84 // -59) // -10)) + 58", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1885, "answer": -30}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((79 + (89 - 55)) - (-67 - 19)) - (95 // (-53 * 39))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1886, "answer": 200}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (0 + -43) + ((-23 // 98) - (-84 + -67))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1887, "answer": 107}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((66 - -15) + (17 % -57)) + (-8 - -47)) // 51", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1888, "answer": 1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((16 // 86) + -99) * (((-99 + 8) - 92) - 27)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1889, "answer": 20790}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-56 * (40 + (71 + 84))) + (45 // (53 + -88))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1890, "answer": -10922}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-4 + 99) + ((59 % -91) * (-33 - 39))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1891, "answer": 2399}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 50 - ((-59 - -10) - ((-47 * -55) - (-57 * (-8 + -82))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1892, "answer": -2446}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (67 - -15) - ((-70 + 59) - (-13 - -27))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1893, "answer": 107}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-42 - ((((60 * -50) - 94) // 99) + -37)) * -50", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1894, "answer": -1350}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (1 - (52 - 10)) + (-98 - (-11 + 45))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1895, "answer": -173}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-67 % -31) * ((-58 + 49) // -85)) - 14) // (93 - 54)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1896, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-85 + (-63 // -37)) - ((-49 - -80) + (18 - -20))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1897, "answer": -153}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-83 // -96) - -1) * ((65 * -76) + (15 - (60 - -74)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1898, "answer": -5059}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (2 // 15) * (80 - ((24 * -4) + (85 + (-67 + 9))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1899, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((71 + 31) - (-35 // -1)) + (-63 % (59 * 9))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1900, "answer": 535}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-93 - (47 + (69 // 90))) // (-84 - -51)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1901, "answer": 4}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -83 * ((-15 * (-97 - -18)) + (-30 * -46))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1902, "answer": -212895}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((49 - 64) - (-23 % (71 - (33 - (25 - 52))))) % 19", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1903, "answer": 13}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (20 + 55) // ((78 * 90) - ((-60 * -76) - (82 * -34)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1904, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((52 + (89 * -98)) + ((27 // -89) - 11)) // 27) - 63", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1905, "answer": -385}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-39 * 94) - (51 + (-9 + -75))) * (59 + -85)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1906, "answer": 94458}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((11 + -29) - -85) * ((89 + 35) + 36)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1907, "answer": 10720}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((80 + 12) * ((4 - -55) // -95)) * 90", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1908, "answer": -8280}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-67 + 69) + 50) - ((-21 // -44) - ((-79 * 50) - 1))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1909, "answer": -3899}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-53 + -10) - (94 * (37 * -53))) // -9", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1910, "answer": -20475}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((94 // ((-55 - 42) + 6)) - (51 * 95)) + -35) + -53", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1911, "answer": -4935}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -76 * ((-37 - -29) - (-26 * ((53 // (-96 - 56)) % 80)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1912, "answer": -155496}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((78 - 14) + (-65 + 5)) + ((-32 - -12) + (49 // -7))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1913, "answer": -23}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-82 % 23) // ((-95 * (58 + -80)) + (89 + 95))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1914, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-5 + 96) + (38 + (-65 - -58))) + -23", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1915, "answer": 99}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -77 - (((-98 + 78) - (8 * (36 + -63))) - 19)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1916, "answer": -254}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-17 + (((-71 // 76) * (-85 // 22)) // 12)) - -66", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1917, "answer": 49}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (82 - (-97 - -96)) * (((19 - -55) - -48) % -30)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1918, "answer": -2324}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 14 - (((-42 * (-47 - -49)) + 6) - (-96 + 65))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1919, "answer": 61}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((12 + -23) * -64) // ((0 - -10) + ((-70 - 92) + -49))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1920, "answer": -4}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (21 - 69) // ((((8 % 93) % -91) - 9) + 78)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1921, "answer": 3}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((60 % -88) - -28) - ((22 * -16) * -12)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1922, "answer": -4224}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-77 * ((-55 - -23) * 79)) + -53) - -89", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1923, "answer": 194692}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (14 + (-31 + 98)) + ((97 // 28) + -56)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1924, "answer": 28}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-14 + -49) - 29) + ((15 - 46) + 95)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1925, "answer": -28}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-24 + 98) - (((-3 - 95) + -64) % 8)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1926, "answer": 68}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-28 - (((-49 + 33) * 12) + 88)) * ((68 + -96) - -99)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1927, "answer": 5396}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (29 + (61 // -19)) + ((((-76 - 1) - 86) // -28) // -39)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1928, "answer": 24}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-91 - ((23 - (-32 + 73)) + 10)) - (-21 + 26)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1929, "answer": -88}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-24 % (17 % 30)) - 34) // (-29 - -45)) * (-86 + 2)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1930, "answer": 168}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (39 - ((7 - -34) + 7)) + ((74 + 0) + (4 * 42))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1931, "answer": 233}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((33 + -4) // 33) - (-84 - (16 - 22))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1932, "answer": 78}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-97 - 99) + ((((79 + 17) * 67) + (-94 + -25)) * -39)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1933, "answer": -246403}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-13 + -90) - (81 - -36)) - ((9 * 52) - 31)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1934, "answer": -657}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (2 * 24) + (((-94 + 4) + 21) - 80)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1935, "answer": -101}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((89 % -53) + ((22 * 48) + 65)) + -28", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1936, "answer": 1076}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (98 // (((-15 + -44) + 29) - 95)) * -15", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1937, "answer": 15}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (0 * ((47 + 7) - (-22 - 75))) - (79 // (3 // -93))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1938, "answer": 79}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((72 * 64) + -22) - ((-64 + (78 - 17)) - -84)) + -32", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1939, "answer": 4473}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((((40 + (75 + 86)) + 14) + -92) + (1 + -47)) + -52", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1940, "answer": 25}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 3 // ((22 % -50) - (97 + (73 + 46)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1941, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-69 * 44) // ((80 + -17) - (98 * (19 * (18 - 89))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1942, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-56 // 4) - (-59 - -92)) - -47) * 84", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1943, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((73 + 98) - (-16 + (76 % 64))) - (-71 + (-8 // 99))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1944, "answer": 247}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-2 + 54) + (-83 - 58)) - -12) % ((-99 - -5) % -33)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1945, "answer": -21}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-40 + 44) + ((-86 * 79) + -62)) // (20 % (7 + 21))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1946, "answer": -343}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-1 + ((((74 + -70) + -12) + 66) - (-73 - -2))) * 67", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1947, "answer": 8576}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-15 + -99) - (15 - (-70 // 22))) * (54 * -60)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1948, "answer": 430920}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((15 - (-47 + -92)) + (33 + (17 // -59))) - 3", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1949, "answer": 183}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((41 * -55) - ((35 * -16) // 93)) + -92", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1950, "answer": -2340}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (18 - ((45 - -52) + (((-77 * -80) + 8) + 39))) // -99", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1951, "answer": 63}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (85 // (((-56 * 21) % 4) + 1)) + (-96 * 43)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1952, "answer": -4043}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-38 % 60) // (8 - (73 * -32))) + -28", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1953, "answer": -28}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (53 - -2) + ((-14 - 34) // ((-79 * -54) * -97))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1954, "answer": 55}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-23 // (69 * -4)) + (5 + (50 * -76))) - (-42 + 18)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1955, "answer": -3771}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-53 - 42) * (((81 % -84) - -36) - (67 + 95))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1956, "answer": 12255}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -66 - ((-3 * (-65 // 96)) // ((-9 - -9) - -43))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1957, "answer": -66}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((80 + 37) + (-5 + -28)) + (-37 + (80 * -30))) + 31", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1958, "answer": -2322}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-9 - 84) - ((((33 - -5) + (83 * 3)) + 6) - -61)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1959, "answer": -447}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (10 + -90) + ((19 + 55) * (-27 // 50))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1960, "answer": -154}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (49 + -20) * (((-65 % 92) * -87) - -34)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1961, "answer": -67135}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-57 - ((-97 * -1) * 7)) - 2) + -81", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1962, "answer": -819}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-51 + ((57 // 52) - 54)) // 69) % (-44 // -17)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1963, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((82 % 27) // (57 + -52)) + (12 * -96)) % (-68 + -36)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1964, "answer": -8}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((34 + -35) + (-75 + (-48 // 55))) + (96 - 54)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1965, "answer": -35}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (4 * -97) - (-98 + (-25 + (-87 - 68)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1966, "answer": -110}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((58 + 86) - (-21 * 90)) - (-91 + -27)) + (-44 + -23)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1967, "answer": 2085}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -47 + (((63 + 40) // (65 * -16)) - 72)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1968, "answer": -120}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (91 * (-24 - -97)) * ((-85 % 33) + (-40 + -13))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1969, "answer": -259077}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 46 - (((56 * -73) * (44 // 59)) % 3)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1970, "answer": 46}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (67 + ((37 // -66) // (-78 % 22))) + 69", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1971, "answer": 135}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (15 - 58) * (((35 - 11) + (23 // -60)) + 94)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1972, "answer": -5031}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-20 + (-21 + 26)) + ((82 - -58) - -18)) - (-81 // 69)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1973, "answer": 145}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-75 // -96) - -86) + 28) + (27 + -49)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1974, "answer": 92}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (28 - -10) * (-42 + ((94 - (-88 - (78 + -14))) + 60))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1975, "answer": 10032}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((52 % (33 + ((-46 % 18) + -89))) % (-23 + 88)) + -52", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1976, "answer": -31}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-26 // 41) + 56) + (-30 - ((-93 // 14) + 92))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1977, "answer": -60}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (99 - (-19 * (-98 + 78))) - ((-17 // -80) // (21 - 62))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1978, "answer": -281}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((24 % (69 % -57)) // (-79 + -31)) // -9", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1979, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-90 + 55) + (43 + ((-11 - -11) // (87 + 89)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1980, "answer": 8}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-30 - 84) - 59) - ((-36 // 55) % 71)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1981, "answer": -243}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (66 - ((-99 + -87) * -27)) + (51 - -37)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1982, "answer": -4868}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-69 - 39) - -29) // (95 - (55 * 83))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1983, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-79 - 39) - (75 - ((1 + 97) + (97 - (-38 // 32))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1984, "answer": 4}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((((69 // 14) - 37) * 39) + -96) % (1 - -17)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1985, "answer": 3}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-2 + (78 * 12)) + (-47 + 85)) - -39", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1986, "answer": 1011}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-48 - (-51 * (-23 * -32))) - (29 * 30)) + -86", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1987, "answer": 36532}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (30 * ((53 - -56) % -89)) // (54 - (39 - 86))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1988, "answer": -21}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-79 + (-48 - 75)) + (0 // (-74 % -75))) - (38 - -29)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1989, "answer": -269}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-12 % (3 + -38)) + ((-71 - 53) - ((-24 // 17) + 76))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1990, "answer": -210}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-95 * -19) + ((74 - -98) + ((-30 - -6) + (-24 + 23)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1991, "answer": 1952}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (37 + ((-79 - 14) - (-25 - (91 - -81)))) + (87 + -37)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1992, "answer": 191}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((0 // 5) - -66) - ((-36 // ((-99 + -6) + -40)) * -96)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1993, "answer": 66}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (90 % ((-66 - -4) + 25)) + (-98 * -44)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1994, "answer": 4291}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-15 + (1 * (-89 // 2))) - 2) + (12 + -97)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1995, "answer": -147}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -66 - ((66 % (((-97 * 60) + 40) * 51)) + -69)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1996, "answer": 294717}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (52 * -69) - (-84 - (64 * (-63 * -6)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1997, "answer": 20688}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 56 + (((77 - -48) % 97) // (94 + -5))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1998, "answer": 56}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-71 % 48) * 67) - -52) + ((-87 - 60) + (-88 + -65))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 1999, "answer": 1427}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((70 + -17) - -34) // ((-88 * -18) + (92 - 43))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2000, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-42 - 32) % -76) + (43 - (62 - (84 + (-10 * 62))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2001, "answer": -629}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-27 + 96) - ((4 + -59) + -57)) + (-61 - -68)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2002, "answer": 188}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-19 + ((-96 * -39) - 5)) + -73) - (-64 + -20)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2003, "answer": 3731}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (15 - (-24 - (64 + -60))) - ((-95 - -66) - (-9 + -83))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2004, "answer": -20}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-81 * (-49 // 75)) - (-82 - 13)) // (74 - 86)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2005, "answer": -15}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 9 - ((-19 - ((-11 + 35) % 13)) - (-4 + (-54 * -34)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2006, "answer": 1871}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -46 + ((-21 + 14) - (((82 + -3) // -32) - 88))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2007, "answer": 38}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-75 * (78 * 20)) + (-18 - (((47 - 89) - -79) - 95))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2008, "answer": -116960}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((84 // 4) + (10 - -15)) - 0) + (42 + (-50 * -17))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2009, "answer": 938}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((2 * 41) * (-4 + 76)) + 20) + (98 + (-37 * 91))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2010, "answer": 2655}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((39 // -32) - (-98 - 65)) % (45 - (-58 - (55 + -7)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2011, "answer": 10}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-44 - (-63 - (-45 % 75))) + (-46 * (-25 - -33))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2012, "answer": -319}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-17 + -38) - (2 + ((59 + 52) + 68))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2013, "answer": -236}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (13 - (-39 * 60)) - (-42 + (67 - -63))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2014, "answer": 2265}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (76 + -53) + (48 + (-35 % (-83 - 9)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2015, "answer": 36}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (95 - -55) + ((((-45 % -23) * 27) - (55 // 52)) % 35)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2016, "answer": 150}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (73 + ((-17 + -78) // (-31 // 77))) + -12", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2017, "answer": 156}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (14 + ((46 + 77) + 56)) * (-48 % 42)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2018, "answer": 6948}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -92 - (84 * ((-37 * -45) - (-52 * 99)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2019, "answer": -572384}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((27 + 16) % ((-44 - -47) * (7 - 86))) - 30", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2020, "answer": -224}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 2 - (((-92 * 14) * (-46 + 43)) - ((-39 - -3) + -91))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2021, "answer": -3989}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((60 // (-65 + 62)) // (-78 + 87)) + (64 * 22)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2022, "answer": 1405}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-66 * (-30 - -95)) % (((30 - -57) - (17 * 8)) - -64)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2023, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (11 * (-96 + (-37 - (-51 + 31)))) + (63 * 4)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2024, "answer": -991}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-27 + (-31 + -19)) - 53) - ((-73 - 34) % -44)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2025, "answer": -111}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((((-34 + 54) // 81) - 30) - 10) + -91) // (-19 - -96)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2026, "answer": -2}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((7 - 99) // ((-44 - -67) - -66)) - (52 + -34)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2027, "answer": -20}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -66 - (-59 * (70 - (-15 * ((-41 % -35) + -95))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2028, "answer": -85321}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -53 + (((-64 + -50) + (28 * -23)) - -55)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2029, "answer": -756}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (2 + 84) + ((((32 % 99) - 29) % 35) - (-67 + -47))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2030, "answer": 203}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-15 + ((0 * 34) * -87)) // -1) - (88 + -48)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2031, "answer": -25}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-21 % 20) // 92) + ((-93 % 93) - 74)) - (32 + 10)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2032, "answer": -116}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-50 * 74) + 39) - -38) - (59 - ((-48 + 2) - -69))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2033, "answer": -3659}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (47 + (7 * (-1 + (-66 * -98)))) + -74", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2034, "answer": 45242}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((88 - 16) // 76) + (((-15 + 28) + 71) - 34)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2035, "answer": 50}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((27 * -9) * -74) - (-34 * ((-29 + -98) - -98))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2036, "answer": 16996}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((34 - 7) + 36) - -66) * (75 + -85)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2037, "answer": -1290}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 7 - (((-16 - -72) // (-55 + -34)) - (-33 + -82))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2038, "answer": -107}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-63 + -48) * (36 // 5)) + 37) // ((32 * 99) - -40)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2039, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (87 - (16 - (-37 + 5))) + (-88 - (-31 - -60))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2040, "answer": -78}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-55 % (78 - (88 * -87))) + 39) * 57", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2041, "answer": 439926}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((56 // 99) * ((-45 - -31) // 72)) + (50 - (64 - -83))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2042, "answer": -97}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-65 - -30) + -13) * -60) % (((-46 - -7) - 0) + 57)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2043, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-23 % ((19 + -47) + (93 + 98))) - (93 % 77)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2044, "answer": 124}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (47 + (28 // 64)) + ((47 + (74 % -95)) + -13)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2045, "answer": 60}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-64 % (((-56 - 84) * 58) - -35)) - -30) + -62) - 67", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2046, "answer": -163}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-9 * 36) + ((-14 - (57 * -95)) - 20)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2047, "answer": 5057}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-89 % (-75 - 45)) - ((21 + -26) // 37)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2048, "answer": -88}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-70 + 69) - (-82 % 32)) + ((76 + 34) + 85)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2049, "answer": 180}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (29 * 34) + ((56 // (65 - 34)) + 2)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2050, "answer": 989}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((47 - (-59 + -37)) * (-56 % 10)) * (89 // (85 + 41))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2051, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((18 * (24 + -25)) + (-74 + 14)) + -50) - 80", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2052, "answer": -208}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((52 - -45) + (-4 + -76)) % (20 * 39)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2053, "answer": 17}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-62 * -2) - (((7 + 60) + 41) - (8 + (-39 + -65)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2054, "answer": -80}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((68 * 22) * (16 + (-61 + (-41 * 21)))) - 74", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2055, "answer": -1355450}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -90 + ((((83 + 39) + (-85 - 72)) * (20 + 15)) // 49)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2056, "answer": -115}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((61 * (8 + 28)) + ((-48 + 52) - 35)) + -80", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2057, "answer": 2085}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (16 - ((19 * (-9 * 50)) + -83)) % ((55 + -85) + 43)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2058, "answer": 4}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-57 - 4) - 41) + ((41 * 32) + ((-47 // 35) * -94))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2059, "answer": 1398}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 76 % (((-61 - -39) % (75 - -72)) - -53)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2060, "answer": 76}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (62 % ((41 + 40) + (-60 // 46))) + 66", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2061, "answer": 128}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((31 * (-93 - 67)) - 26) - -98) - ((84 % 95) - 53)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2062, "answer": -4919}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -87 + (((-43 // (-62 + 51)) - 43) - -63)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2063, "answer": -64}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-29 - 81) - ((56 + 17) + -88)) + (83 + -19)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2064, "answer": -31}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((18 - 31) + (33 + 87)) - (-51 + -13)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2065, "answer": 171}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((25 + ((90 - -74) * 97)) + (69 + -44)) - -74", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2066, "answer": 16032}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((75 % 97) + -18) * ((-8 + -67) - (35 + 23))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2067, "answer": -7581}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((82 - -28) + ((-20 // -5) - 31)) - (-73 - (-20 + -83))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2068, "answer": 53}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (67 - (93 * (-41 - 66))) * ((-49 // 3) - 38)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2069, "answer": -550990}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -16 * (((91 * (50 + 64)) // 13) * (59 - 15))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2070, "answer": -561792}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -63 + ((61 + -31) + (((-32 - 6) + 22) * (-93 % 95)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2071, "answer": -65}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-94 - -83) - 11) + -44) - (57 - -18)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2072, "answer": -141}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (30 + 70) + ((-9 * 50) * ((16 // 81) * -58))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2073, "answer": 100}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-40 + -73) * (((82 + -90) * -65) % 45)) - (-15 // 44)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2074, "answer": -2824}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-41 - (-55 - -23)) * (-3 + (-82 + 41))) - -11", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2075, "answer": 407}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((50 - (0 - -93)) - ((-23 + -25) - -1)) * (82 - -34)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2076, "answer": 464}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-11 - 91) + (((61 - 25) // -31) // (9 // -83))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2077, "answer": -100}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -13 + (-58 - ((32 + 71) // (4 + (66 + -26))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2078, "answer": -73}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-29 + 71) // ((79 + -85) * (44 - -47))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2079, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-93 // 89) + (52 + 85)) - (38 // ((71 + 64) - -38))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2080, "answer": 135}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -61 - ((((48 * 86) - 66) + 50) + -1)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2081, "answer": -4172}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((43 * -51) * (((18 + -68) * (7 * 6)) - 12)) - -80", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2082, "answer": 4631696}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (92 * 1) - (-28 - (-91 % (-67 * -65)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2083, "answer": 4384}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((58 + 51) - ((-81 * (86 + 13)) // 9)) + (8 + 25)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2084, "answer": 1033}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-75 * ((58 - -81) + (-61 + 63))) - (-29 + 4)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2085, "answer": -10550}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((58 * -57) + -45) - (99 * (-83 - 18))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2086, "answer": 6648}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-21 - -64) // (-86 - -71)) + ((26 * 93) + -67)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2087, "answer": 2348}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (46 + 50) * (((-8 + 50) - 95) - (64 + -53))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2088, "answer": -6144}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-76 + -23) * (-93 * -44)) * (-99 + -54)) * 91", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2089, "answer": 5640318684}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (87 + (-30 - -26)) + (((24 - -63) // -53) - 37)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2090, "answer": 44}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-23 * 21) * ((-83 - -35) * ((-3 - 88) - (-4 * 76)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2091, "answer": 4938192}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-61 + (-76 - -70)) - ((35 // 33) + (51 // -18))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2092, "answer": -65}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -65 // (-25 + (50 * ((-37 + 13) * 27)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2093, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((32 + -50) - (79 * 36)) - ((-84 + -74) + (-37 + -78))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2094, "answer": -2589}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-16 - -76) * (-35 * (11 + ((-56 + 62) + -73)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2095, "answer": 117600}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((41 - (-75 + -88)) + 58) // (62 // 35)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2096, "answer": 262}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-15 * 95) * (-86 // 5)) + (-63 - (49 * 69))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2097, "answer": 22206}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-4 + -32) + (81 + (-96 - (-91 + -86)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2098, "answer": 126}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-52 - 29) * ((66 + 77) // (79 - -95))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2099, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-56 - (90 - -75)) + (-25 + (-93 // ((23 - -90) + -73)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2100, "answer": -249}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -34 + ((-95 + (3 * 9)) + (-47 + (-67 - -65)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2101, "answer": -151}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-91 - (-40 + 51)) // (-52 - (-87 // -4))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2102, "answer": 1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-75 + 70) - (-80 - (95 - (-34 + (-46 + -42))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2103, "answer": 292}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -50 * ((-6 * -53) - ((-45 // (-37 - (-14 - 6))) + 74))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2104, "answer": -12100}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-44 + (-52 - 29)) + ((98 - -23) - (10 - -98))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2105, "answer": -112}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-50 // -31) * -55) // (87 * (-36 - 12))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2106, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-29 + (-54 + 60)) - 21) + (-8 * 4)) % 99", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2107, "answer": 23}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-1 - (-5 - -14)) * (-31 + (96 + 0))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2108, "answer": -650}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (64 - (59 % 7)) - ((-73 % -31) * 22)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2109, "answer": 303}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (4 * 49) + ((-26 - (-30 - 96)) * (12 + 85))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2110, "answer": 9896}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-46 * 44) - (((96 * 63) + 97) + 48)) - 42", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2111, "answer": -8259}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-25 + -48) + (((52 - -61) + -23) + -73)) + -13", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2112, "answer": -69}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -59 - ((((91 * 61) % 41) - -42) + (-30 - -45))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2113, "answer": -132}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((29 + 92) - 10) - ((6 // -74) + ((-24 + 45) * 21))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2114, "answer": -329}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((7 + -75) - ((73 - 29) - (-74 + 1))) - (78 + 19)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2115, "answer": -282}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -37 // (28 + (22 + (-2 - (21 // 77))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2116, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -75 + (((42 - 83) - -95) - (-1 + 88))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2117, "answer": -108}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-66 // -68) - ((-49 // 52) + 97)) - (98 + 14)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2118, "answer": -208}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (65 // -28) - ((0 - 80) * ((93 - 4) + -47))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2119, "answer": 3357}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (18 % (92 - ((-44 - 2) + 47))) - -32", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2120, "answer": 50}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((71 + (-53 - (((84 - -25) - 46) * 18))) - -77) - 59", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2121, "answer": -1098}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((6 // (-44 * -15)) - -43) - (-91 % (0 + -72))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2122, "answer": 62}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-70 - (99 - 84)) * (46 + (88 - 50))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2123, "answer": -7140}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -50 + ((-30 * -30) + (22 - (24 - 69)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2124, "answer": 917}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-27 + (45 - 40)) - ((87 % -84) * -81)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2125, "answer": -6583}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-90 + (-35 - 40)) % -76) - (3 + (-27 - 49))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2126, "answer": 60}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((98 // (-87 + ((-90 // -61) // 36))) + 44) // (7 + -69)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2127, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (92 * (59 - (-36 - (-63 // -68)))) // (-33 * 29)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2128, "answer": -10}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-60 - -84) % -46) - ((-80 + (-84 % 79)) - (45 // 72))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2129, "answer": -16}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-47 + (-84 - -79)) - -17) + (-74 // 80)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2130, "answer": -36}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-47 - (81 // (50 - 75))) - (-95 - -65)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2131, "answer": -13}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-58 - (-25 - -76)) * -69) - (37 * (62 - -23))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2132, "answer": 4376}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (79 - -80) + ((22 - 31) + ((-2 * -24) - 10))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2133, "answer": 188}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-38 + ((-90 + (-22 + 58)) * -71)) * 69", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2134, "answer": 261924}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 48 + ((-36 + (-69 + -10)) // ((-80 - 82) + -39))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2135, "answer": 48}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-15 // (6 - 53)) - ((0 - -82) + 5)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2136, "answer": -87}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-57 * -17) % -55) + ((((-99 // -64) - 63) % -6) + -27)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2137, "answer": -50}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (82 - ((((10 * 0) + 55) + -27) + 30)) * 46", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2138, "answer": 1104}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-92 - -5) % (52 + (((-10 + 70) - 3) * (-6 // -6)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2139, "answer": 22}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-52 + (64 * 86)) - (17 + (0 * ((95 + 68) + -7)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2140, "answer": 5435}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-33 // (-97 + 22)) + (70 % (-78 // (68 - -29)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2141, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-3 - 31) + (((-33 + -89) // 80) - 32)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2142, "answer": -68}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -98 % (64 // ((21 - 5) + (-50 % (-68 + -10))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2143, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-41 - -63) + (((-55 + 43) % (-27 % (38 * -28))) + 21)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2144, "answer": 31}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-8 - 56) - ((-99 * (-76 - -90)) % (16 + 55))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2145, "answer": -98}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-73 // 81) - (-36 % ((99 - -19) - -50))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2146, "answer": -133}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-57 - (-98 % (26 * 43))) + (54 + (35 + -38))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2147, "answer": -1026}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-81 + -93) - ((60 + -26) - (-37 + -22))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2148, "answer": -267}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((96 + (68 + -32)) - (21 * 43)) - 5", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2149, "answer": -776}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (41 * (-55 - -78)) // ((-94 - (-43 - 94)) % -11)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2150, "answer": -943}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (73 - (19 + (71 - (-75 - -43)))) - (-35 % -38)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2151, "answer": -14}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-18 - (42 // -17)) % -11) + ((52 - 47) - (79 + 97))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2152, "answer": -175}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((48 * (8 + 55)) * (46 + 64)) + -87", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2153, "answer": 332553}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((34 + 56) % 40) // ((-3 - (87 - (0 - -15))) - 8)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2154, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (16 * 94) % (((-88 - -78) // 3) - (-63 + 14))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2155, "answer": 19}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -42 + (((-23 * (-64 - -8)) - -43) % (32 // -28))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2156, "answer": -43}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((64 + 57) - 2) * -24) + (-22 + 18)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2157, "answer": -2860}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-97 - 37) - ((-38 * (-35 % -55)) + (-22 - 32))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2158, "answer": -1410}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -29 + (17 % ((-21 + (85 + -15)) // -12))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2159, "answer": -32}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-16 + (-19 + 18)) - -27) + (-1 + -55)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2160, "answer": -46}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-58 * ((-5 + 16) * -84)) - -38) // (-43 - 69)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2161, "answer": -479}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-53 % -43) + -78) - (64 + 38)) + -64", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2162, "answer": -254}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-88 - ((-64 - 55) - 12)) + ((77 + 59) % (14 - -59))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2163, "answer": 106}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((54 - -64) + (-93 + -22)) + (5 - 19)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2164, "answer": -11}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-8 + 76) * ((4 + -2) + (22 * (2 - -43)))) + -67", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2165, "answer": 67389}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -44 + (-40 // ((-22 - 37) % ((-52 - -61) - -88)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2166, "answer": -46}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 72 + ((-72 + ((65 + (-45 // -4)) % 59)) - -42)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2167, "answer": 59}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((55 // (-99 * (66 + -94))) - -52) * (11 * -74)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2168, "answer": -42328}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-12 + -3) + (((32 + 90) + -5) + (54 - -20))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2169, "answer": 176}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-41 + (-26 + -11)) // 87) - (-65 + 91)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2170, "answer": -27}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -1 + (((-27 - -15) + (-25 - 13)) + 88)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2171, "answer": 37}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-96 - 90) - (58 - ((-49 + 74) * (-79 - 72)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2172, "answer": -4019}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((83 - 10) + (-85 // -11)) - (69 * (66 * 95))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2173, "answer": -432550}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -67 + (48 + ((80 + 66) + ((41 - -85) + 5)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2174, "answer": 258}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 85 - ((-60 // (-37 + (73 // (1 - 23)))) % (62 // 10))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2175, "answer": 84}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-65 - (-49 + 76)) % (-81 - (-3 - 63))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2176, "answer": -2}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-43 + 28) + -78) * (-26 - (56 - -20))) // (-94 - -89)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2177, "answer": -1898}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-13 - 98) * (46 // (-37 + (-46 // -63)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2178, "answer": 222}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-2 + 57) // (-67 + 23)) + ((26 + 69) - 42)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2179, "answer": 51}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((46 - -81) - (-46 // 35)) % (-89 - -75)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2180, "answer": -11}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (0 // (-58 * 80)) - ((-25 - -52) + 11)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2181, "answer": -38}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-83 * -63) * ((-28 + ((-43 + -36) + 26)) - -6)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2182, "answer": -392175}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((58 + 21) // (-33 * 36)) % ((51 + 10) % (-57 * -28))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2183, "answer": 60}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-94 + -21) + 5) - ((-98 + 6) * (46 * (-16 * -1)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2184, "answer": 67602}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-63 - (8 + 97)) + ((7 - 83) - ((53 * -40) - 90))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2185, "answer": 1966}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (58 + (((-34 + (-64 + -81)) + -66) - 48)) + -71", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2186, "answer": -306}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-52 * -62) + -49) * -25) % ((41 * 77) - 80)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2187, "answer": 627}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-26 + (((-64 + -4) * -70) // (79 % 68))) + (18 + -93)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2188, "answer": 331}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-76 - -25) * ((99 * -37) - (14 + 66))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2189, "answer": 190893}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (46 - 79) - (((84 // 2) * 25) + ((-96 + 2) - -49))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2190, "answer": -1038}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((34 % 10) + (-98 + (-82 - (-61 // -93)))) - -87", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2191, "answer": -89}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((((0 + -35) - 98) + (-47 + 93)) + -45) * (16 % 73)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2192, "answer": -2112}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (31 - (77 + (28 - 86))) - ((79 - (-2 + -97)) // -14)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2193, "answer": 25}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((54 - -65) - -93) - ((-28 // 46) // 84)) - (-70 + -51)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2194, "answer": 334}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((45 + -44) - -4) + (68 + (-80 - -72))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2195, "answer": 65}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((22 - -11) // 36) - ((39 * (-44 - 35)) - 88)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2196, "answer": 3169}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-26 - ((-84 - -27) + (-30 - -38))) % (-10 + (-1 + 31))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2197, "answer": 3}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 76 * ((-51 + 34) - ((-29 - (23 + -20)) // 18))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2198, "answer": -1140}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-49 + (60 // 64)) + (-73 * ((-2 - -27) - 15))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2199, "answer": -779}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-90 + -76) - (-60 * 19)) - (4 - 56)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2200, "answer": 1026}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((80 + -73) // ((-72 - -6) - 33)) + 0) - (33 // 9)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2201, "answer": -4}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 46 // (((-8 + 49) + (70 * -49)) % -59)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2202, "answer": -2}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 22 + (85 - ((-14 + (-4 + -51)) - (-8 - 65)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2203, "answer": 103}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 51 + (((13 - 81) + -61) // (((-6 // -38) * -36) - 49))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2204, "answer": 53}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-59 + 0) - ((-75 - 20) - 99)) - ((44 // -88) % -82)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2205, "answer": 136}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((10 * 41) + 25) + ((99 + -48) - (-61 - (-47 * -59)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2206, "answer": 3320}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (94 - -1) + (((-34 - (-82 + 64)) + -5) + 90)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2207, "answer": 164}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -57 + ((33 // (-23 + 10)) - (-38 - (40 + (-51 + -98))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2208, "answer": -131}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((85 - (64 % (96 + -42))) - 43) - (24 + (21 - 17))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2209, "answer": 4}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-69 + (((-18 // (78 - 88)) // (68 + 30)) + 0)) + -49", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2210, "answer": -118}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-97 + ((-62 + -81) - (-63 // 84))) % -28", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2211, "answer": -15}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (73 // -25) // ((74 * -86) + (90 // 69))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2212, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((94 * 59) * (-69 // 74)) * (-72 - -3)) + -6", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2213, "answer": 382668}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((4 + 98) // (5 + -24)) + -89) % ((-50 - -26) - -31)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2214, "answer": 3}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 58 - ((-58 * (-64 - 73)) - (75 // 83))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2215, "answer": -7888}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (60 * -48) - ((-77 // 49) // (95 + (-37 * 60)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2216, "answer": -2880}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 18 + (-7 // (((8 - -87) * 96) - (-14 * (64 + 51))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2217, "answer": 17}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -15 % (91 + ((-88 * (2 - 82)) + -61))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2218, "answer": 7055}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -92 - ((-65 - ((44 + 47) + (72 % -33))) * 20)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2219, "answer": 2488}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-43 - (-26 - 30)) // 29) + 83) + (-8 - 26)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2220, "answer": 49}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-27 - 47) - ((46 + -76) - -35)) + -1", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2221, "answer": -80}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((((74 + -38) * -60) - -94) // -46) * -76", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2222, "answer": -3344}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((9 + -6) % (33 * (-20 + (38 - -14)))) - -32", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2223, "answer": 35}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (72 * -67) - ((-89 - (77 + 89)) + (-94 + (71 // -87)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2224, "answer": -4474}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-18 * -77) - 51) - (44 + (-28 // -46))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2225, "answer": 1291}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (3 - (87 + (66 * 79))) + (-39 + -18)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2226, "answer": -5355}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((54 + 83) + (-96 * (-85 - (85 // -90)))) - 51", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2227, "answer": 8150}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((42 - 14) * (87 * (-20 % 37))) + -88", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2228, "answer": 41324}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((79 - -28) + (-14 // (60 - 75))) + -87", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2229, "answer": 20}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-32 - 81) - (63 // ((9 + -77) + -37))) * (1 // -56)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2230, "answer": 112}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (32 - (-64 // (73 + ((-10 + 95) - 47)))) + (18 - 79)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2231, "answer": -28}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-11 - (-81 + (-90 - -10))) + (73 // (-97 * 57))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2232, "answer": 149}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (55 + ((-64 - -75) // 43)) * (92 + (-64 // 71))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2233, "answer": 5005}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((5 - 88) + ((94 - 87) // -73)) - (25 - 10)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2234, "answer": -99}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (31 + (((-67 * 69) * (5 + -39)) - 11)) * 40", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2235, "answer": 6288080}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-77 - (99 + 64)) - (18 - (-55 + 52))) - (-52 - 9)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2236, "answer": -200}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((46 - 80) - (15 + 65)) + ((2 % -16) // -56)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2237, "answer": -114}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (19 - ((-18 + 45) - (-65 // -17))) * -12", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2238, "answer": 60}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-61 + 12) % (55 - 27)) + ((-93 * 41) + (43 + -5))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2239, "answer": -3768}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-18 // (-81 + ((98 * 13) + -72))) + ((24 + 42) + 50)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2240, "answer": 115}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-64 // (((-10 + -76) - 37) // 37)) - 13", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2241, "answer": 3}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -21 // ((-85 + ((-98 - 84) - 55)) + -52)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2242, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (34 + (44 + 26)) + ((-87 - 61) + (65 - -95))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2243, "answer": 116}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-68 - -73) - (-12 + (-83 * 65))) - 30", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2244, "answer": 5382}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (27 * ((47 + (3 // 70)) - (-61 + -53))) + -58", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2245, "answer": 4289}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (55 - -46) + (63 - (-1 + (-89 + -96)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2246, "answer": 350}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-65 // -33) - (-1 - ((-33 - 80) - 47))) + 16", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2247, "answer": -142}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (89 // 63) - ((79 + (27 % 77)) + (65 + 96))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2248, "answer": -266}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((5 - 74) // 99) * ((-87 * 85) - (39 - 27))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2249, "answer": 7407}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-4 - -43) - -34) - ((-28 - -2) - 68)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2250, "answer": 167}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((71 - 92) - (30 * -49)) - -24) - (70 * -9)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2251, "answer": 2103}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((7 + (-44 + 12)) - 1) - -23) - ((-60 % -92) - 70)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2252, "answer": 127}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-98 + 31) * (-37 + -59)) * ((69 + 67) - -35)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2253, "answer": 1099872}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (53 - 77) // ((53 + (37 + -31)) + (19 + -57))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2254, "answer": -2}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-86 + ((-28 - (95 - (46 % -88))) - (15 // -41))) // 90", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2255, "answer": -3}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-30 // 63) - ((-38 - (-83 // 8)) + (-14 * 44))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2256, "answer": 642}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -9 * (74 + ((-23 % -12) - (69 * (44 + -75))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2257, "answer": -19818}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-41 + -83) + ((53 - -32) + (-42 % (59 + 95)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2258, "answer": 73}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (85 + 86) - (-71 - (-38 * ((-29 % -57) * 3)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2259, "answer": 3548}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-32 + -61) - ((((71 - -11) + -71) % 78) * -86)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2260, "answer": 853}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((36 + -50) * 42) * (((-12 + -79) + -33) - (-89 + 55))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2261, "answer": 52920}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 50 % ((-75 + -79) + ((((-8 + -19) - 94) * 76) + -43))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2262, "answer": -9343}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((96 % (-65 % 22)) * -52) + ((7 + (-48 + -36)) - 14)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2263, "answer": -91}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-64 * (71 * (22 % -4))) * ((95 + 9) // -34)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2264, "answer": -36352}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-92 + 32) - ((31 // 68) + (1 + -59))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2265, "answer": -2}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (9 % ((-78 + (-38 - -94)) + -39)) * 59", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2266, "answer": -3068}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (12 + (-84 * -20)) + ((83 + (85 + 58)) + (-67 + 74))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2267, "answer": 1925}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((74 - -74) * (95 + -44)) - (-41 + 99)) - (-21 + 29)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2268, "answer": 7482}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 69 - ((-85 % (-5 + 56)) + (3 - (-6 * -88)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2269, "answer": 577}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (85 * -39) // (-36 * ((21 - (97 + -5)) * (-3 * 20)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2270, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-71 * (((52 // -93) - 92) - -26)) * 61", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2271, "answer": 290177}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (34 % 82) + ((-36 + 12) + ((-78 - -90) + 76))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2272, "answer": 98}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((24 * -69) + (-17 + (5 * (75 * (73 + 20))))) - 55", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2273, "answer": 33147}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((16 * -45) // (31 // -71)) - (-63 % 76)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2274, "answer": 707}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 91 * (88 - (((59 // (-59 * (52 // 41))) + -36) % 2))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2275, "answer": 7917}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -17 + ((74 + ((24 + -70) - 98)) * (-8 + (45 + 32)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2276, "answer": -4847}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((14 + 65) - (-11 + 53)) - ((-4 + (-85 + -34)) - -29)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2277, "answer": 131}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -97 - ((-66 + 99) - (((44 + 27) + 43) % 57))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2278, "answer": -130}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (64 + -11) - (-56 + ((16 - 95) + 2))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2279, "answer": 186}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-30 - -97) - ((-30 * (76 + 77)) % 18)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2280, "answer": 67}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((38 - 83) % 86) - ((9 * 39) + (-88 * (-37 - 41)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2281, "answer": -7174}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-55 + -81) - (93 - ((-37 - (-28 + -3)) * (-74 + 40)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2282, "answer": -25}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-99 + -74) + ((-7 + -39) + (-91 % (76 - 88)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2283, "answer": -226}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((86 + (-43 // 7)) // -97) - (38 - 45)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2284, "answer": 6}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (67 * ((89 + ((20 + 92) + 31)) // 52)) * (66 * 25)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2285, "answer": 442200}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-88 - (-94 - (-66 + -79))) - ((-87 * 22) + -97)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2286, "answer": 1872}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 12 * ((44 // -6) - (68 - ((-53 - -44) + 18)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2287, "answer": -804}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((96 - (50 % 93)) - (60 - -32)) + 65", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2288, "answer": 19}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((8 + 56) // 21) * (58 + ((-13 * 0) + -70))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2289, "answer": -36}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (10 * 28) - (-39 * (((77 // 94) // (93 + -63)) - 9))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2290, "answer": -71}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-65 + 90) % 3) + (99 + 13)) * 40", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2291, "answer": 4520}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -4 // (((18 - -74) // -49) - (92 - -26))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2292, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-44 + 76) + (((-82 // -22) + -23) // 1)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2293, "answer": 12}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (9 - -47) * ((-24 // 75) * (-81 * (7 - -75)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2294, "answer": 371952}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (61 - (-4 // -52)) - ((-71 + (37 + 89)) + (-46 + 7))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2295, "answer": 45}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-35 + ((-3 + 38) + 45)) - ((-94 * -44) - -3)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2296, "answer": -4094}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-92 // -28) - (25 % (3 + 87))) * (77 * (96 + -11))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2297, "answer": -143990}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (81 - 53) + (70 + ((-85 // -1) + ((-28 + -83) + -88)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2298, "answer": -16}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -3 % ((-79 // 40) // ((-67 + 32) - (-28 - 23)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2299, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-77 * 38) % (15 * (67 % -86))) * 23", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2300, "answer": -1748}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((((-27 + 49) - 58) - 15) + (-19 - -58)) - -65", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2301, "answer": 53}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-71 * ((-14 // 7) + -8)) % (42 * 59)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2302, "answer": 710}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-97 - ((27 - (62 * (5 // -37))) + -75)) // (-48 * -75)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2303, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((15 * -54) - (-73 + 8)) + 53) + -21", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2304, "answer": -713}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (25 // (-77 + (35 + 77))) - ((1 + (79 + -87)) % -70)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2305, "answer": 7}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 28 + (10 + ((-51 + 75) + (-70 + 0)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2306, "answer": -8}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-69 - -38) - (21 // ((49 + -90) - 94))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2307, "answer": -30}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-37 - (73 // -58)) + ((-4 - 33) * 99)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2308, "answer": -3698}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((78 + 8) * (75 - (-60 - 24))) - (88 // -44)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2309, "answer": 13676}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-17 - 99) // ((13 - -30) * (54 % 80))) * (-17 + 43)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2310, "answer": -26}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-54 + -72) + 81) % (81 + (4 // -90))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2311, "answer": 35}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((47 + ((-33 + -74) * -46)) - 86) + 98", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2312, "answer": 4981}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-75 - -19) - 0) - ((55 - -37) + (98 + (54 + 3)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2313, "answer": -303}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((67 // (79 * 70)) * ((49 + 38) - 19)) - (62 + -28)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2314, "answer": -34}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 44 + ((((18 - 24) + (-15 + (8 + 3))) - 31) + -83)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2315, "answer": -80}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (60 - 21) + (10 // ((23 + 78) + -65))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2316, "answer": 39}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((81 - (-97 - 81)) * -53) + (-66 - 67)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2317, "answer": -13860}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-75 // 77) % ((-84 * (73 - -37)) - -52)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2318, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-19 * -21) % ((72 * (-59 + 78)) + ((94 + -5) - -98))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2319, "answer": 399}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-10 - 80) // -76) - (72 + 89)) + ((-13 - 7) + -29)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2320, "answer": -209}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-20 + (-10 - -50)) % (-50 * 20)) + -90", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2321, "answer": -1070}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-23 - (-76 + 76)) - ((31 + (-1 * -80)) + 71)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2322, "answer": -205}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 65 * ((-1 % -18) % ((92 - 48) - 52))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2323, "answer": -65}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 63 // ((23 * -2) * ((50 - 70) % 9))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2324, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (46 * -11) - ((38 * -1) + (46 * ((-83 + 61) + 39)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2325, "answer": -1250}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (60 * (-21 + (-28 * (-24 + -99)))) - -3", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2326, "answer": 205383}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-30 + 5) - (-48 + ((-39 - -34) + -46))) + 21", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2327, "answer": 95}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 89 - ((((88 % -90) - (99 + -7)) - -26) - -55)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2328, "answer": 102}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-1 * 59) + ((-12 * -94) - ((-47 * -12) + -94))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2329, "answer": 599}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((95 - (56 + -30)) + ((-36 - 46) * (55 - 9))) + -27", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2330, "answer": -3730}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (54 + -75) - (((-88 * -33) - (-68 - 41)) * 34)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2331, "answer": -102463}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -90 + (((41 - 31) - 17) - (-29 - -27))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2332, "answer": -95}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((((11 + 16) + 51) - 38) // 57) - 49) * (17 + -95)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2333, "answer": 3822}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (18 + (11 // ((-78 // (60 * 13)) - -78))) + -79", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2334, "answer": -61}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (84 + 15) - (-13 - ((-8 * 8) + 11))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2335, "answer": 59}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (68 // (-80 + 39)) * ((76 * (-1 - (70 + -25))) + -33)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2336, "answer": 7058}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-27 * 78) - (-5 + ((-95 // -28) // -17))) + (66 + -14)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2337, "answer": -2048}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((25 + (-20 + -88)) // -65) - ((44 - 12) - -81)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2338, "answer": -112}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((15 - -68) - ((-66 % -15) + -85)) - 75) + -38", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2339, "answer": 61}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((91 - -55) * 94) * (((62 + 6) + (33 + 66)) * -26)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2340, "answer": -59589608}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (44 - -86) - ((-17 * ((-95 - 85) // -78)) * (98 * -79))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2341, "answer": -263098}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-78 - 57) // 67) // -46) + (95 + -24)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2342, "answer": 71}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((82 + (18 % -10)) - (95 // 22)) + (-44 + (-16 + 7))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2343, "answer": 23}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -50 - ((-35 * ((-45 + 61) - 53)) % -33)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2344, "answer": -25}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-40 - (38 - -81)) - 73) - -61) + (-43 + -5)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2345, "answer": -219}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((23 * (15 + (-68 + 15))) // (-28 + -8)) // 19", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2346, "answer": 1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (73 + ((0 % -37) // 1)) * ((79 - -89) + 31)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2347, "answer": 14527}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((27 // 98) - (57 // -30)) * 76) * ((-26 + 29) + 83)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2348, "answer": 13072}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-51 - 15) * (((93 % -38) // (0 + 20)) - 8)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2349, "answer": 660}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-32 * -61) + (23 // 8)) - ((-79 % -21) + (-10 + -48))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2350, "answer": 2028}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -80 % (((67 * 99) - -46) + (60 * (-91 * 65)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2351, "answer": -80}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 47 - ((5 // (2 + -8)) + ((-38 - (85 + -32)) - -12))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2352, "answer": 127}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-37 + -12) + -53) - (74 + -66)) * 6", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2353, "answer": -660}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 62 - (-90 * (((47 - 89) // -79) * (-84 - 89)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2354, "answer": 62}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-80 * -79) + 54) + ((-79 // -77) * 41)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2355, "answer": 6415}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (92 + (-29 * 3)) * ((-20 + 87) + -21)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2356, "answer": 230}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((31 * 65) + (31 * 25)) + (-28 * (88 - 50))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2357, "answer": 1726}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((82 - 58) + -95) + 90) + ((-5 - 4) - -12)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2358, "answer": 22}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((35 + (-29 + 84)) + (80 + -40)) - (-99 - (48 - 81))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2359, "answer": 196}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-95 * -19) + (24 * 75)) // (60 + 37)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2360, "answer": 37}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-82 + -35) % (-9 - (-44 - (37 + (-3 + -91))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2361, "answer": -7}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-37 // -45) - (-35 - 17)) + ((-33 + 17) + -23)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2362, "answer": 13}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-51 + -16) - (((-95 + 92) + 73) % (85 + -42))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2363, "answer": -94}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-8 - (38 % 92)) - 75) % (((-20 + 28) + 23) + -22)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2364, "answer": 5}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-47 % -6) + (30 - (-97 + (-9 + 32)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2365, "answer": 99}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (8 - 98) + ((-10 - (60 + 35)) - (64 + -57))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2366, "answer": -202}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 26 * ((((48 - 34) % -22) // (-56 + 42)) % (-15 // -7))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2367, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-3 * (((-44 - 38) + (-75 // 51)) % (-20 - 37))) % 96", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2368, "answer": 81}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 41 * ((88 - (-49 * ((-33 // (-51 * -33)) * -67))) // 81)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2369, "answer": 1681}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-59 // -73) - (((96 * -86) + 51) // (-55 + -83))) + 32", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2370, "answer": -27}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-50 + -24) - (-77 - ((-77 * -49) * (-78 // -14)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2371, "answer": 18868}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-86 + -83) + -17) - ((-51 // -84) - ((-97 + 16) - 13))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2372, "answer": -280}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 72 + ((-87 + (((70 // 97) * (-18 + 17)) + 5)) - 90)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2373, "answer": -100}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (92 + ((-22 * -69) - 43)) - ((53 - (-63 + 5)) * 58)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2374, "answer": -4871}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-85 - 7) * -21) * (59 - ((-94 + (-73 - 78)) - 92))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2375, "answer": 765072}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-95 % (93 - 80)) + 87) - (-59 % 71)) * -35", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2376, "answer": -2940}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 4 + ((29 + -67) * (76 * (63 - 28)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2377, "answer": -101076}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((67 % ((-62 - -92) + 36)) + (62 // -30)) // 28", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2378, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((91 - (-97 - ((-64 // 70) * (27 - -66)))) - 95) + -66", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2379, "answer": -66}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((81 * (-59 + (-92 - -88))) - (-31 - 44)) - (58 // 27)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2380, "answer": -5030}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-51 - 43) - ((-62 + ((-24 % -14) // -52)) % (-15 - 74))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2381, "answer": -32}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((81 * ((-95 - -2) * (-26 + (-55 + -53)))) % -32) * -96", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2382, "answer": 1728}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-32 + 16) + 3) // (((84 % 49) - -94) + -34)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2383, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((77 - -33) + -47) % (-75 // -15)) + 61", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2384, "answer": 64}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-43 - ((87 // -2) - -11)) + ((-81 // -47) % 69)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2385, "answer": -9}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-64 + (-77 + -74)) - 87) - (43 + -2)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2386, "answer": -343}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((71 + 93) - 15) + (93 // (-45 + 31))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2387, "answer": 142}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-68 + 95) + (((87 // -37) * 44) + -56)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2388, "answer": -161}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((51 * 83) - 93) - (-33 * 18)) * (-7 - (-21 - 13))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2389, "answer": 127818}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-76 // 89) + ((-44 + 64) - -85)) - 45", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2390, "answer": 59}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((69 // 87) // ((-97 - 43) - (31 // 95))) * 33", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2391, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((((77 + 70) - (52 + -57)) + -5) - 99) - 70", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2392, "answer": -22}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((35 % -57) // (95 * (35 - -44))) - (-37 + (-46 // -89))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2393, "answer": 36}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((75 - 9) - 25) * (64 - 27)) - (57 - 3)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2394, "answer": 1463}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (23 + (88 % -28)) - (((-14 - -62) * -79) + -40)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2395, "answer": 3831}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((23 + -17) - ((54 // 61) + (29 + 80))) + 60", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2396, "answer": -43}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-77 + 76) - -83) - (((76 - -59) - 10) - 14)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2397, "answer": -29}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 92 + (58 // (((-14 - -42) + (57 + 5)) * -8))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2398, "answer": 91}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 97 * (((-71 - 57) - 4) + ((-39 - 85) - -97))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2399, "answer": -15423}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((89 + 30) - (-84 * (2 - -50))) + -90", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2400, "answer": 4397}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-55 % -28) // -62) + (35 - (95 * 39))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2401, "answer": -3670}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (98 // 70) - (((-2 - 6) - (46 - (12 // 68))) % 78)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2402, "answer": -23}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 63 - (-29 + (-47 - (-23 + (-81 + -14))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2403, "answer": 21}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-4 * (3 - 92)) - 25) + (-11 % -16)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2404, "answer": 320}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-11 - -37) + 50) - (1 * (58 % (25 * -31)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2405, "answer": 793}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((27 // (-87 - 62)) // -14) % (2 - (60 % 47))) + -83", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2406, "answer": -83}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((5 + 14) * (29 + (89 + -89))) // -56", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2407, "answer": -10}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((43 * -37) - -94) - ((-12 - -18) * 41)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2408, "answer": -1743}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -59 // ((7 * ((56 // -5) * 2)) - 23)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2409, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-99 + 15) - 44) - (24 * -12)) - (71 - (56 // 30))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2410, "answer": 90}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-5 // -82) - (47 - 74)) + (-23 + -75)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2411, "answer": -71}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-47 - 73) * (10 // (59 + 39))) * (34 + 95)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2412, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((70 - 47) - (((14 + 12) - (-2 + -18)) * 50)) - -90", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2413, "answer": -2187}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -7 // (((67 * 82) * -46) - ((97 - 11) * 38))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2414, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-13 - ((-63 - 86) * -99)) - (97 + 57)) - -86", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2415, "answer": -14832}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-23 - (-11 * -46)) // -7) + ((-68 * -86) * 70)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2416, "answer": 409435}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -68 - (((17 % -41) // 97) + (58 * -32))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2417, "answer": 1789}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 69 - (((-55 + -9) - -6) - (29 + -13))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2418, "answer": 143}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-42 - (-30 - 66)) + (((-75 // 1) + 37) * -15)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2419, "answer": 624}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((59 + 71) + -19) + ((-62 * 38) - ((-10 - 42) // -95))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2420, "answer": -2245}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((((25 * -7) + 29) + (68 * 5)) - 4) % (-60 * 36)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2421, "answer": -1970}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (99 - ((-57 - -38) * (90 + (14 * -99)))) + -23", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2422, "answer": -24548}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-35 - ((63 + 84) + -75)) - (87 + 27)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2423, "answer": -221}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-25 + (43 % -10)) - 83) - -18) - ((33 // 83) - -44)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2424, "answer": -141}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-90 - -68) + 19) - (-51 + ((-95 + -80) - 18))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2425, "answer": 241}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (69 // (95 + (13 - (-1 + 18)))) + (48 // -91)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2426, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((36 - (-19 - 75)) + -74) - 2) // (-71 + 92)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2427, "answer": 2}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((14 // 3) // (-9 - (10 - 25))) % (-5 // 73)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2428, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((26 * (17 + (-65 + 37))) - 38) + -45) + -30", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2429, "answer": -399}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-11 // -72) - (57 // (-80 - (-51 // -87)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2430, "answer": 1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((27 * 63) + (58 - -41)) + ((73 - -42) - (23 - 83))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2431, "answer": 1975}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((78 % -31) + (-49 + 81)) - 97) * (71 - (17 - 73))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2432, "answer": -10160}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (99 - 61) + (((0 - -93) + (-12 * -53)) // (-39 - 87))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2433, "answer": 32}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-63 // (10 - 50)) - (-77 - -67)) + (-49 % -57)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2434, "answer": -38}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-17 // (-3 + -78)) - (50 - (65 // 40))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2435, "answer": -49}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((59 // -21) // (((-32 * 62) + (-3 + -4)) - 80)) // -45", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2436, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-26 % -80) // -71) * (98 - (-78 - -45))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2437, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (31 + (76 - (-63 * -85))) - (42 - (77 // 52))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2438, "answer": -5289}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-74 - 38) * -28) + 28) + (-33 // -2)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2439, "answer": 3180}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-92 + -80) + ((-49 * (-17 - -31)) // (-75 * (-52 % 14)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2440, "answer": -170}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-97 + -49) * (31 + (2 - -25))) * 20", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2441, "answer": -169360}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 88 - ((8 - (((-72 % 40) + -39) - 99)) + 20)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2442, "answer": -70}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-99 - 24) - ((((63 - 7) - -52) + -75) - 28)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2443, "answer": -128}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -27 + (((69 + (-73 + 29)) + 0) - 48)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2444, "answer": -50}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -42 - ((-23 - 68) * ((-34 * 58) - 10))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2445, "answer": -180404}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (51 * (3 - -90)) - ((56 - 75) - (0 * -35))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2446, "answer": 4762}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 45 - ((((-41 + (-66 * -13)) - 70) - (81 + 53)) + 16)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2447, "answer": -584}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -68 // ((89 % ((-51 * 2) - (49 * 1))) - (-97 - 19))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2448, "answer": -2}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-14 * -36) - (54 // (64 - ((-12 * -56) + 3)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2449, "answer": 505}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-71 * 9) - ((41 // (-6 - -29)) + 32)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2450, "answer": -672}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-49 + 98) * ((94 * 29) + (-50 * 75))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2451, "answer": -50176}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-98 - (((-38 - -16) - (23 + -20)) + -13)) * (-3 - 47)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2452, "answer": 3000}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-93 - (89 * -79)) * ((96 + -77) // -61)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2453, "answer": -6938}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-77 + 47) // (((45 * 49) + -96) - (-13 - (-74 - 27)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2454, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 25 - (-50 * (-11 // ((-85 - 47) % (-81 + -66))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2455, "answer": 25}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-15 + (1 * (39 + -40))) - (-46 + -38)) + 15", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2456, "answer": 83}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((94 - (96 + 4)) + (19 + 71)) + (-84 + -97)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2457, "answer": -97}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-20 * (68 * 83)) + (((-79 - 64) - 96) + 21)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2458, "answer": -113098}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -41 - ((-32 + 49) - ((-14 - 94) * 28))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2459, "answer": -3082}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-99 * (39 + -28)) * ((51 * (80 - 13)) - 86)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2460, "answer": -3627459}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 39 + (-11 - ((-12 // -25) - (24 // -86)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2461, "answer": 27}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((6 // -69) - -73) - (-86 + 24)) - (1 + -21)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2462, "answer": 154}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((8 - -12) - 19) // (32 * ((-57 + 0) // 75))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2463, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (30 - -13) + ((95 - (49 * -97)) - ((36 + -10) + 90))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2464, "answer": 4775}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 12 - (((67 + (-82 % -44)) - 33) + (5 - 41))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2465, "answer": 52}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 60 // (((13 + 53) + (20 * -89)) * (46 - 45))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2466, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-42 // 28) // (((91 - (-82 - 72)) - -78) * -85)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2467, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-68 + -66) - ((-52 - (5 * (-26 - -48))) + -58)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2468, "answer": 86}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-86 - -63) + (58 + (-35 - (-2 % -94)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2469, "answer": 2}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-3 * ((75 - (3 + 57)) + (68 - -66))) * -51", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2470, "answer": 22797}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-64 + 54) - -21) % -76) - (30 * (-37 - 24))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2471, "answer": 1765}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-91 + (((36 * 43) * (-26 * 37)) // (-70 - 49))) - 62", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2472, "answer": 12361}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-34 + ((-10 * -20) * (36 + (-17 + (14 - 6))))) - 95", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2473, "answer": 5271}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-14 * -92) + ((((40 - 2) + -92) + 74) + -53)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2474, "answer": 1255}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-56 - -68) + (-80 + ((-76 - 60) + 84))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2475, "answer": -120}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((52 % 99) // (39 - 21)) // 45) * (-59 - 33)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2476, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-35 + -59) * (((-55 * 48) + -71) + (71 * 48))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2477, "answer": -65518}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((10 + -97) // -39) - (95 - (39 - (21 + -98)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2478, "answer": 23}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (80 % (-54 - 35)) - ((-13 + 76) // -79)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2479, "answer": -8}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -62 - ((-78 * 86) // ((-23 - -6) - -30))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2480, "answer": 454}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((59 - -64) + (-85 + -31)) * (7 - -66)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2481, "answer": 511}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-74 + (-56 - 4)) // (((-29 - -56) - -86) - -41)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2482, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (24 // ((89 * 39) + -51)) * (-96 + ((-63 - -39) * 77))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2483, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (37 + 82) + (10 + (-77 + ((15 - 53) + (-41 + -65))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2484, "answer": -92}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-31 - ((59 * 63) + 18)) // (45 - (28 + 56))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2485, "answer": 96}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((59 + -66) - ((47 // -66) + (-69 - 44))) + -60", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2486, "answer": 47}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-39 * (81 - -61)) + ((-31 - 48) - 66)) + (94 + 23)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2487, "answer": -5566}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (52 + (-12 * 38)) - (((-80 - 10) - -45) - (-78 + -27))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2488, "answer": -464}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (20 - -14) + (((-20 - -53) + (44 - 20)) * (50 - 6))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2489, "answer": 2542}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-11 + (33 + (78 - -82))) // (-23 - 68)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2490, "answer": -2}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((((95 // 66) + 12) - 82) * ((-56 - 93) + -33)) * -23", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2491, "answer": -288834}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (62 + (-22 // 60)) * ((-57 + 55) * -3)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2492, "answer": 366}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-13 - ((-42 // 33) + 74)) - (-59 + (96 - -42))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2493, "answer": -164}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (65 - ((-24 - 21) + (-87 + 61))) // (85 - -87)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2494, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (54 + (8 - 79)) + (((23 % 7) // -67) * (-57 + 4))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2495, "answer": 36}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-6 + -33) * ((-91 + (6 + 54)) * -40)) % -86", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2496, "answer": -28}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (84 * ((-74 - (-62 * 20)) * (-72 % (93 * 18)))) // -52", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2497, "answer": -3017429}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-33 + 26) // (8 * 47)) + (-97 % 63)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2498, "answer": 28}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((57 * (-44 - -15)) - (15 + -21)) + -58", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2499, "answer": -1705}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((58 - 7) - ((23 - -78) - -9)) - -36", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2500, "answer": -23}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -56 + ((97 + -58) * (((4 + -16) + -97) - (85 + -48)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2501, "answer": -5750}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (48 % (81 + (11 * (17 + 5)))) * -82", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2502, "answer": -3936}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((16 + 29) + 26) * ((-18 - -33) + (83 + (-54 + 65)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2503, "answer": 7739}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 3 - (((86 + (89 - 11)) * 14) - -6)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2504, "answer": -2299}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-21 + -40) + ((-29 - -18) % -45)) + (77 + -11)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2505, "answer": -6}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-14 - (-49 + -36)) * 31) // -74) + -43", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2506, "answer": -73}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 24 + ((-12 - -36) - (-87 - (-41 - 9)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2507, "answer": 85}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -54 + ((95 - 22) + ((63 - 46) * (-51 * 83)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2508, "answer": -71942}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-38 // -41) - ((-17 // (3 - -87)) - (-36 + -66))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2509, "answer": -101}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -92 // (-30 + ((66 % 76) + ((1 % -21) + -81)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2510, "answer": 1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-4 - -77) + (-17 // (31 * -90))) - 25", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2511, "answer": 48}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 51 - (-36 - ((-10 - (87 // 77)) - ((96 + -82) - 58)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2512, "answer": 120}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-14 - ((-8 + 28) % -68)) + ((-40 - -55) % 32)) + 62", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2513, "answer": 111}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (5 * -37) + (11 - (91 + ((-80 + 72) + (84 * 11))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2514, "answer": -1181}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-97 - (18 * 12)) + (-19 * (-25 // -60))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2515, "answer": -313}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((71 * 67) - 8) - ((-80 * -21) * -51)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2516, "answer": 90429}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-93 - 30) + (91 + (-72 - (-79 + ((88 - -75) + -87))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2517, "answer": -101}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (25 + 32) - ((38 - ((-90 - (1 - 69)) * -70)) - -1)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2518, "answer": 1558}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (5 // ((-10 // 61) - (70 // 52))) - -2", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2519, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-2 * (-54 * 35)) // -91) - (23 % (83 * 25))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2520, "answer": -65}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 86 * (73 + (((-60 * 62) * -50) * 18))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2521, "answer": 287934278}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-95 // 20) + 33) % (87 - (37 - -43))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2522, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-73 - 65) + -34) - -11) + (56 - 41)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2523, "answer": -146}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-33 - 0) // (-32 // 45)) % (12 + -2)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2524, "answer": 3}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-82 * 44) + (96 + 26)) + -74) + (9 + (-9 // 11))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2525, "answer": -3552}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-46 * -22) - -36) + (29 * (61 * 68))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2526, "answer": 121340}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-95 // 85) % (-65 + ((10 + -15) - (-38 - 98)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2527, "answer": 64}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-95 - 74) // (-74 + -3)) * (77 - 43)) - 24", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2528, "answer": 44}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-72 // -4) - ((73 + -60) + -96)) + -73", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2529, "answer": 28}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-64 - (-25 * -13)) * ((69 + -85) + -12)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2530, "answer": 10892}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (30 + ((71 - (46 // 27)) - 3)) + (-39 - 34)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2531, "answer": 24}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-20 // ((1 - -45) - -96)) // (98 - ((35 - -43) * 98))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2532, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -92 // (49 + (-25 + ((-59 - 58) + ((-95 + 26) // 78))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2533, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (13 // (-19 + -30)) - (((32 - 59) - (78 + -50)) + -8)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2534, "answer": 62}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-62 + ((16 * -16) - 62)) - 4) // -85", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2535, "answer": 4}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-36 * -90) + (-42 // ((-4 * -2) + 91))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2536, "answer": 3239}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-52 // ((69 + -5) // 33)) + (-32 + (33 - 62))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2537, "answer": -113}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-13 * (6 + ((-88 - 82) // 39))) + -70", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2538, "answer": -83}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (25 * 35) * (((25 // 63) - 58) - -91)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2539, "answer": 28875}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((7 - (-16 * (22 - 1))) + 57) // ((-22 // -22) + -60)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2540, "answer": -7}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-33 + 78) + ((-35 + (-51 * 86)) + -81)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2541, "answer": -4457}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (19 // (-23 - (-89 * -42))) * (-71 + 37)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2542, "answer": 34}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (74 * -2) - ((-32 - (55 + 96)) - -36)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2543, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-1 + (-93 * (17 + -76))) * 29) - (-73 - (88 // -19))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2544, "answer": 159162}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((86 + 25) - ((-25 // -83) + -88)) % -43) - -32", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2545, "answer": 16}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-49 - (33 * -73)) + (44 * (-20 + -97))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2546, "answer": -2788}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 79 - ((-19 * 63) - (14 + (-20 // (16 + -90))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2547, "answer": 1290}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((47 - 91) - -29) - (-1 - ((-24 - 70) - (35 + -45)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2548, "answer": -98}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -49 - (-32 + ((-30 + -19) - (-67 % 96)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2549, "answer": 61}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((54 // -31) * (17 + 86)) + (-93 - -43)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2550, "answer": -256}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((59 * 61) + (-99 - 55)) - (-36 * 56)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2551, "answer": 5461}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (92 // 58) + ((-52 - 62) // (-23 * -81))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2552, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-42 + (10 - (-10 * -40))) + (80 - 66)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2553, "answer": -418}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -10 - (((-77 * 76) % (-79 - -93)) + ((-24 + 5) - -75))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2554, "answer": -66}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (2 * (0 * -26)) + (-84 // (13 * -25))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2555, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((44 - -3) - (31 * -35)) - ((20 - (67 + -36)) - 4)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2556, "answer": 1147}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -86 // (((93 * -81) + (25 - 96)) + -43)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2557, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((53 % -49) - (-90 * 14)) * ((-71 - (14 // -72)) // 47)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2558, "answer": -2430}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-90 + ((-56 - -76) - -31)) // ((-77 + -8) * -14)) * 52", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2559, "answer": -52}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-40 - -40) + (70 + 45)) - ((-4 - -58) - -41)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2560, "answer": 20}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 23 * ((-45 - ((-37 + -99) // (-20 - (-1 % 61)))) + 4)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2561, "answer": -966}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (84 * -71) // ((((-73 - 17) - -44) + 46) - -22)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2562, "answer": -272}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((30 + 27) - ((-49 // (35 + -3)) + -15)) - 70", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2563, "answer": 4}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((69 - 0) + ((-33 - 80) + -79)) * -38", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2564, "answer": 4674}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((96 * 24) + ((-91 * 11) - -98)) * (-6 + 44)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2565, "answer": 53238}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 23 // ((19 - 56) * ((84 + -68) - ((-13 + -93) + 1)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2566, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((93 // -32) - ((3 // -46) // 52)) * (-96 + -73)) + -24", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2567, "answer": 314}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-98 + -40) + 54) + (-35 + (22 - 79))) // (86 - 39)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2568, "answer": -4}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-7 // (-67 - 55)) + 67) - (-15 - (60 + -55))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2569, "answer": 87}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -98 + (71 - (-71 // ((-78 * (9 - -81)) * 7)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2570, "answer": -27}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((44 + ((98 - 92) + 60)) + 61) - 32", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2571, "answer": 139}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-40 + -99) * (73 - (68 - (36 + -22)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2572, "answer": -2641}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((96 + (23 - -67)) + -49) + ((-81 // (-32 + 71)) * -32)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2573, "answer": 233}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 27 * ((((61 % (-7 - -18)) - 86) + (-82 * 56)) + -64)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2574, "answer": -127872}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 98 * ((-94 * 6) - (93 - (35 * 87)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2575, "answer": 234024}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (24 - (-83 + 64)) * ((-92 + (-51 // 6)) - -32)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2576, "answer": -2967}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((9 - (-18 % 61)) - 57) * (6 // 19)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2577, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-37 - (-42 * 48)) // ((83 - (69 + -54)) // -12)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2578, "answer": -330}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((17 + -73) % (-2 - (19 - 50))) * -33", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2579, "answer": -66}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-52 + (-52 - 58)) + (95 - -34)) * (-22 // 76)) - 34", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2580, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (97 - 81) * (((-70 + (-20 // -43)) + -43) // -88)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2581, "answer": 16}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (55 + (-17 * 44)) * ((-78 + -14) + (80 + -10))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2582, "answer": 15246}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (98 % (((24 * (57 + -86)) + -56) - -8)) - (77 + -61)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2583, "answer": -662}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((20 + -56) + -70) * ((86 - 2) - 2)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2584, "answer": -8692}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -44 * ((-17 * 31) - ((38 + (-55 - 60)) + (-11 - 69)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2585, "answer": 16280}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((85 + 17) // (55 * -8)) * 26) // ((-82 + 45) - 65)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2586, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((75 + -78) * -81) * (23 + (1 + 17))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2587, "answer": 9963}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-62 * -9) + ((11 * -73) + (-58 // -6))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2588, "answer": -236}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-47 + (-92 // -96)) - (-7 + ((-91 * 91) + (48 - -57)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2589, "answer": 8136}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (31 * (-42 // -56)) - (-89 + ((-78 - -56) + (-41 - 84)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2590, "answer": 236}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-61 + -52) + -99) - ((-98 - -83) + (-94 - 41))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2591, "answer": -62}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-35 - 73) + (12 // ((26 // (96 + -46)) + 62))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2592, "answer": -108}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-59 + (-9 // -15)) - (76 * (-95 - (-79 * -91)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2593, "answer": 553525}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 59 * (((-67 + 10) * -55) - (77 + (-96 // (8 + -97))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2594, "answer": 180363}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-38 - -17) - (-60 // ((-99 * (72 + -30)) * 75))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2595, "answer": -21}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (17 - (-47 - 48)) - (12 * (44 + -92))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2596, "answer": 688}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 7 * (((-68 * ((57 - -1) - 43)) * (87 // 74)) - -21)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2597, "answer": -6993}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-99 - -34) - ((-35 + -83) + (0 + -74))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2598, "answer": 127}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-98 * -92) - (-25 + 89)) - ((-74 // -15) // 87)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2599, "answer": 8952}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 26 + (((49 + 6) + (33 + -99)) - (-24 + (-69 + -8)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2600, "answer": 116}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (68 + (58 + 47)) - ((88 - 85) - 98)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2601, "answer": 268}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -15 // ((-4 + -59) + (79 + (-65 - 70)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2602, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -16 + (((66 % 14) - ((-10 - -30) // 90)) % (80 + 83))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2603, "answer": -6}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-12 * 92) - (53 + -6)) + (98 - (-77 - -70))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2604, "answer": -1046}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-18 - 30) + ((19 * ((3 - -89) % -43)) - -78)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2605, "answer": -673}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-39 + (-34 * -8)) + ((81 - (-69 + 40)) // 11)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2606, "answer": 243}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-54 - (-5 + 80)) - ((70 + 88) - -6)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2607, "answer": -293}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-16 - 89) + (((-17 + 14) + 27) + (-72 // (15 * 52)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2608, "answer": -82}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (82 + -21) // (((-63 - 14) * -35) * ((-77 - 0) * -99))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2609, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((94 + -72) + -10) // (-53 + -70)) + (-48 - (82 * 34))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2610, "answer": -2837}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-98 - (-30 + (11 + 75))) * (-66 + (-98 + 76))) + 27", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2611, "answer": 13579}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (90 * (92 + (88 - 47))) - ((20 - -73) // 63)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2612, "answer": 11969}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-43 - (34 // (92 // 39))) + (-62 // 32)) - -6", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2613, "answer": -56}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((((40 - (99 + -39)) * 48) * 20) + 2) + (-86 - 83)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2614, "answer": -19367}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 66 - (21 // ((51 - -27) + (((-19 + 19) // 76) + 65)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2615, "answer": 66}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-71 + -88) - 16) - (((91 % (-65 + -1)) - 64) + 98)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2616, "answer": -168}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-23 * (-9 + 46)) + (77 - ((88 // -33) // -36))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2617, "answer": -774}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((61 + 64) - (19 - (-6 - 30))) + (16 // 30)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2618, "answer": 70}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((71 + 42) + (-3 + 23)) - (-44 + -21)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2619, "answer": 198}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 26 - (((14 + 67) * ((76 * (20 + 0)) + -75)) - 76)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2620, "answer": -116943}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((69 // -93) + (26 - ((0 - (-61 + -51)) // -49))) - 84", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2621, "answer": -56}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-39 * -51) // 5) + (-66 + 42)) + ((87 + -52) + -42)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2622, "answer": 366}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-19 + -49) + (18 // (-19 + (-69 + -27)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2623, "answer": -69}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-32 // (-51 + (-67 + -37))) // ((25 * -80) + (9 * 57))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2624, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 50 // ((-19 - -5) * ((-89 + -61) * (-89 - 6)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2625, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-50 // 8) - (-32 + -7)) // (21 + 1)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2626, "answer": 1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (42 + 45) + (70 - (63 + (23 // 74)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2627, "answer": 94}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (8 - ((13 // (-73 + -60)) + (-61 - (68 + 82)))) + 62", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2628, "answer": 282}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-27 + 8) // 43) - ((72 - -98) + -34)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2629, "answer": -137}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((49 + -14) + -86) - (5 * (81 + (10 - -98)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2630, "answer": -996}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-44 * -40) + (25 % 5)) + (48 + (-32 - 74))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2631, "answer": 1702}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -92 - (((3 * 45) - ((9 * 45) - -95)) + -52)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2632, "answer": 325}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-84 * 45) - (((74 - -94) * (-73 + 18)) - (11 - 65))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2633, "answer": 5406}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 85 - (-12 // (-55 + (-85 // (50 * (-35 - -20)))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2634, "answer": 85}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 18 - ((((-70 * -2) // -53) - 87) + (42 + (76 // -39)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2635, "answer": 68}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((90 // 53) % ((67 // 57) + (-71 - (-13 - -42)))) + -93", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2636, "answer": -191}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -59 - ((-89 * -85) % ((-62 - (68 - 19)) - 14))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2637, "answer": 1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (17 + (-19 // -26)) + (((-57 - 41) * -62) // (3 * -50))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2638, "answer": -24}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-79 + -57) + ((-25 - -33) % (81 + 8))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2639, "answer": -128}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((90 + (26 - 5)) - (46 - 7)) - (66 + 10)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2640, "answer": -4}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (78 + ((-54 - -7) % 19)) * (16 % (78 - -35))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2641, "answer": 1408}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((14 % -99) % 79) - 79) - ((-18 * 23) + 20)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2642, "answer": 388}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 12 // (-63 + ((40 * ((3 * 34) - -84)) * 54))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2643, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((76 - 85) - (82 // (-34 + -69))) * 13", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2644, "answer": -104}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -12 - ((-80 - 66) - ((-14 - 0) * 87))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2645, "answer": -1084}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-48 // (77 + 65)) + 3) // ((21 // 48) - (63 - -83))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2646, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-68 - (95 + 96)) * -32) - (43 * 76)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2647, "answer": 5020}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (73 - 76) % ((3 // (-78 * 48)) - (58 * 43))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2648, "answer": -3}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (34 + (-99 - 80)) + (21 + (78 + ((-73 - -6) + -56)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2649, "answer": -169}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((86 * -85) + (-26 + -85)) + (-42 + -42)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2650, "answer": -7505}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((16 + 80) - -61) // (6 % -78)) + (-16 // -82)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2651, "answer": -3}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 47 - (-86 + (((-72 + 28) + 43) * 89))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2652, "answer": 222}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 86 - ((-4 + -87) // (-10 * ((-58 + 76) % 96)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2653, "answer": 86}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-91 // -79) - (73 * ((-6 - 60) - ((66 % 18) + 73)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2654, "answer": 11024}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((54 % (-17 // 53)) - ((-34 - 95) - -57)) - (-61 // -1)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2655, "answer": 11}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-85 - (-78 + 4)) * (-71 + -10)) + 85) * (13 - -25)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2656, "answer": 37088}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-51 + (18 + 57)) - (14 + (93 - 2))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2657, "answer": -81}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((91 % 74) // (97 * -98)) // 36) + ((28 - 97) + -77)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2658, "answer": -147}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-7 * (58 * 86)) - ((-29 + -30) - (32 - -85))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2659, "answer": -34740}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-27 // 89) - -88) * ((-34 // -32) - -15)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2660, "answer": 1392}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-53 + ((96 // -37) // -18)) + -62) - 13", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2661, "answer": -128}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-75 + (-76 % (80 - (78 - -81)))) // ((74 - 9) + 31)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2662, "answer": -2}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-57 - (-37 % -8)) * (-69 + 29)) // (-86 - (86 * 78))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2663, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (95 - (-60 % -62)) - ((-60 - -11) + 58)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2664, "answer": 146}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-14 - -15) + ((48 + 33) + (41 + -73))) - 84", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2665, "answer": -34}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (95 - -27) % ((((15 - -21) - -1) - -98) - (-55 // 50))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2666, "answer": 122}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (24 + ((-53 - -79) - -32)) // (-79 - 18)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2667, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-30 // -11) + (60 % -53)) - (15 - 10)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2668, "answer": -49}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((((-15 - -24) + -28) // -15) // 32) + ((95 - -24) + -82)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2669, "answer": 37}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-70 + (85 * 49)) - (7 * (77 // -15))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2670, "answer": 4137}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (79 // ((70 - -83) + 79)) * ((-35 % (-36 - 33)) - 55)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2671, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -60 * (((23 + 55) - -37) * (85 * 72))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2672, "answer": -42228000}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-82 % ((42 + 3) % -65)) + (80 // (-84 + 20))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2673, "answer": -4}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((33 * -92) % (-40 - -73)) - (-91 + -66)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2674, "answer": 157}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (63 - -23) * ((-86 + -45) % ((67 - 84) * (-82 + 38)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2675, "answer": 53062}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-23 // 17) + ((-51 - -83) - (-66 + 61))) % -80", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2676, "answer": -45}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (26 * ((43 // (39 + 95)) + -87)) + 2", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2677, "answer": -2260}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -18 + (((32 + 3) * -3) - (-9 * (-16 + 82)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2678, "answer": 471}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 34 + (-57 - ((-64 // -80) - (70 * (11 - 50))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2679, "answer": -2753}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((51 + 83) - 56) * ((38 - 29) - -59)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2680, "answer": 5304}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((((-15 * -60) + -88) - (-79 - 72)) + (73 + -57)) + 58", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2681, "answer": 1037}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((88 + (-46 * (-95 % -46))) + 11) * ((-24 * -67) - 14)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2682, "answer": 377778}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((10 // 39) - 80) + 70) * ((21 * -63) - (90 % -3))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2683, "answer": 13230}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-98 - 30) - ((44 - -42) // (13 * -79))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2684, "answer": -127}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 5 + ((-43 * -31) - (((-37 + -12) + 9) + (-50 - 67)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2685, "answer": 1495}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-85 * -34) - (-45 * -13)) - (81 + 50)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2686, "answer": 2174}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-67 % 99) + ((91 + (-56 + (15 - -94))) + -20)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2687, "answer": 156}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-89 * 96) - ((-12 // -13) // ((34 + 55) + (49 + 16)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2688, "answer": -8544}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-24 - (-73 - ((43 - 38) - (-7 - 50)))) - 8", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2689, "answer": 103}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-40 - 36) + 1) - ((56 + -97) - (-28 - 32))) // 72", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2690, "answer": -2}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-46 + -52) + (60 + -81)) - (-27 - 40)) * 55", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2691, "answer": -2860}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-92 + -97) - 69) * ((-38 // 74) % (-19 // 50))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2692, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((8 + (-91 // 25)) * ((63 + 43) + 53)) + (-47 // -84)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2693, "answer": 636}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-42 - -37) % ((78 // (-38 * 85)) - 30)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2694, "answer": -5}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 95 * ((40 - (-36 - (9 - 41))) + (-17 - 41))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2695, "answer": -1330}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 39 - (-70 - ((-47 * 18) - (-49 * -16)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2696, "answer": -1521}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-66 + ((-57 + 31) - 97)) + ((-18 + -2) * -6)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2697, "answer": -69}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((79 % 49) - 71) % -24) // ((-12 + 46) - (57 - 46))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2698, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-12 + (67 - -38)) - (((45 // 82) - 62) + -78)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2699, "answer": 233}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -23 * ((((44 - -42) + 60) + (-58 - 77)) - -19)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2700, "answer": -690}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-84 - (72 - 99)) + (99 + (1 + 67))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2701, "answer": 110}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -82 - (((-23 - -4) + ((82 - -24) % -18)) - -61)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2702, "answer": -122}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (71 - -65) * ((96 // 60) + (19 + -48))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2703, "answer": -3808}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-85 - -51) + ((-55 + 86) + -76)) - -56", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2704, "answer": -23}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((89 + 80) - -55) % ((-40 - -25) + (48 % (-76 - -54)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2705, "answer": -7}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 42 - (-7 // ((-65 + (-60 + -16)) + ((-97 - -77) // 42)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2706, "answer": 42}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -70 * ((90 * 87) - ((29 * 82) % ((-82 - -48) - -45)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2707, "answer": -547960}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((((19 * (40 - 7)) + -77) + -52) * 27) - -38) * -25", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2708, "answer": -337100}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 97 + (-61 - (98 - (59 - (79 + 82))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2709, "answer": -164}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-42 + (-76 + ((44 * -91) * -58))) - 59", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2710, "answer": 232055}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (43 - ((49 * (74 * 6)) * -22)) + ((-51 - -70) + 47)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2711, "answer": 478741}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (32 * (-82 // (-50 + (1 * 44)))) // 87", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2712, "answer": 4}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (14 // -61) + ((61 - 3) * ((-23 // 83) + (24 + -78)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2713, "answer": -3191}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (59 % -70) * (((-90 * -17) * -92) + -71)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2714, "answer": 1549141}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-94 + 96) + (-30 * ((11 // -92) + 27))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2715, "answer": -778}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-11 + -85) - 84) + ((-11 + 93) * 81)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2716, "answer": 6462}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-42 - -80) - -3) * (-69 - (-93 + -49))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2717, "answer": 2993}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-76 + (-19 + 98)) + 77) * ((-51 - 95) - (98 - -47))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2718, "answer": -23280}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-94 + -96) - (53 - 56)) % (4 - 53)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2719, "answer": -40}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((84 % (97 - -36)) + -44) - ((-92 + 27) + -72)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2720, "answer": 177}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-93 + (-83 + -29)) + (44 - (-49 - -36))) // (-44 + -23)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2721, "answer": 2}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 93 + (((-24 + -26) - (60 * 67)) - -56)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2722, "answer": -3921}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((48 - 27) - (-63 - 35)) + (39 + 78)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2723, "answer": 236}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-8 // -19) - -71) // (59 - (48 - 8))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2724, "answer": 3}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (33 - -57) + (10 * ((41 - 82) // 26))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2725, "answer": 70}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-62 * (37 + -95)) // -91) - (78 - -39)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2726, "answer": -157}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((33 - -20) - 6) * ((33 * 11) % (83 + -31))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2727, "answer": 2397}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (26 + (-66 + (3 - -41))) - (18 - -14)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2728, "answer": -28}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (24 - 3) - (-68 + ((32 - -22) * (32 - -73)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2729, "answer": -5581}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-5 * 13) - -54) % (81 - (83 - -45))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2730, "answer": -11}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-81 + ((-69 + -73) - -21)) % ((-49 + -3) + (-77 - 33))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2731, "answer": -40}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (92 % 92) + (-14 - (((-2 - -10) - -33) * (90 - 2)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2732, "answer": -3622}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (30 * 93) - ((28 - (-77 * -31)) - (-49 // (74 // -30)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2733, "answer": 5165}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((46 % -9) + 73) // ((-92 + -97) + -40)) + (-77 * -76)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2734, "answer": 5851}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-61 * (99 % -61)) // -43) - (((-31 + 76) - -67) * 77)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2735, "answer": -8657}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((0 * (37 - -5)) - 69) + (49 // -16)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2736, "answer": -73}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((50 - (-33 + (84 + 55))) * (5 - 75)) - (-91 - 40)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2737, "answer": 4051}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -51 - ((((-38 - -29) + 36) + 61) - -35)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2738, "answer": -174}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (91 - (19 * -91)) - (77 + ((25 * 47) % (83 * 70)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2739, "answer": 568}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-21 % (53 - -9)) + (((10 + 48) - -15) - (-64 - -78))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2740, "answer": 100}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((((-66 + 22) - -12) - -56) + (-96 + -71)) + 7) % 91", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2741, "answer": 46}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (66 - ((-30 - ((49 - 70) * -27)) - (50 // -52))) - -40", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2742, "answer": 702}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (5 - ((-58 * 9) + ((84 - -76) + 76))) - 75", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2743, "answer": 216}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -76 + ((20 - (-67 - (63 + 68))) * -13)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2744, "answer": -2910}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (89 - (-89 * (45 - -22))) - ((79 + -26) // -55)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2745, "answer": 6053}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((83 - -10) + (39 - (64 % (24 % -56)))) + (83 + -8)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2746, "answer": 207}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((69 - (-87 + -64)) // 7) - (-3 // -29)) - 64", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2747, "answer": -33}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-78 + ((87 + 87) + -83)) + (-90 * 73)) // 34", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2748, "answer": -193}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (85 + (25 - 87)) - (-70 - ((-80 + -23) // (83 * 67)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2749, "answer": 92}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 50 - ((95 + 48) - ((-22 % -55) * 88))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2750, "answer": -2029}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (88 + ((-38 - 28) - 85)) - ((44 - 73) // 87)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2751, "answer": -62}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-85 + ((62 + -62) // -12)) - (-55 + (-75 + -59))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2752, "answer": 104}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (41 + (94 * (4 - (47 - 50)))) * -84", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2753, "answer": -58716}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((87 + -95) * -62) - 39) + ((85 * -47) * (47 - 66))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2754, "answer": 76362}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (5 + ((95 // 72) + 36)) + (-72 * (-96 - -51))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2755, "answer": 3282}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((94 - (15 % (-37 // 25))) * (36 - 62)) - (83 + 81)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2756, "answer": -2634}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-90 // 28) + (47 // (53 + -60))) - (26 + 85)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2757, "answer": -122}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((58 + 5) - (-84 - 22)) * -26) * (-12 * 2)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2758, "answer": 105456}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (10 * ((-7 + 74) + -29)) + (98 - (29 - -73))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2759, "answer": 376}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((48 + -10) - -99) // (-50 // -21)) - (96 - -66)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2760, "answer": -94}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -52 * ((2 - (-85 - (-67 * 91))) // 70)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2761, "answer": 4472}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-4 + (-42 // -38)) * (57 + (19 // (99 - 95)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2762, "answer": -183}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-14 - (11 * (-62 + 66))) - (-30 + 20)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2763, "answer": -48}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-67 * -12) - (24 - 95)) - (-84 // 85)) - -8", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2764, "answer": 884}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-50 + -65) // 27) + 12) * (-44 - -33)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2765, "answer": -77}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (79 + 3) - (98 * (20 + (-43 - 28)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2766, "answer": 5080}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-13 // 93) - (((-90 // -40) - (84 * (97 - 88))) - 79)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2767, "answer": 832}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -98 - (((68 - (-35 // -91)) - (91 + 15)) + (-31 - -49))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2768, "answer": -78}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (75 - -68) // ((37 - (-6 - 3)) - 63)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2769, "answer": -9}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (66 % 25) * ((-31 + (-43 - 13)) % -74)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2770, "answer": -208}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((23 + (47 - 69)) + (39 + -95)) - ((-5 + 81) // -8)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2771, "answer": -45}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-75 * (26 * 71)) - ((19 // (12 * -25)) % -92)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2772, "answer": -138449}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (62 % 16) // ((34 * 36) * ((-32 + 86) * -66))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2773, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-43 - 55) + ((74 - 73) + 33)) * (74 - (-79 + 78))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2774, "answer": -4800}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -39 + ((53 + 31) - ((-11 - -7) + (75 + 76)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2775, "answer": -102}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -67 - ((2 + (12 - 89)) + (((4 + 66) - 18) - -42))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2776, "answer": -86}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-76 // -23) + (-36 * -63)) + ((88 - -99) * -40)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2777, "answer": -5209}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-20 // (21 // -2)) * ((-73 // -16) - ((-38 * 74) * 14))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2778, "answer": 39372}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-41 * 53) + (((-98 - -48) + 43) // (-17 - 91))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2779, "answer": -2173}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((70 * 68) * (-49 % -80)) + ((32 % 26) * -44)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2780, "answer": -233504}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -61 + (-95 + ((89 + (-47 * -2)) - 72))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2781, "answer": -45}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-10 - 89) + ((((85 - 81) - -52) * -56) + 87)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2782, "answer": -3148}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((45 * -45) * 54) // (10 + (-98 // -75))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2783, "answer": -9941}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -91 - ((-22 - (((85 - 87) - -94) + 92)) + (-46 + 91))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2784, "answer": 70}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((94 * 15) - (71 * 21)) - (58 - -7)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2785, "answer": -146}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (24 - (-85 % 58)) + (54 - (27 - (7 + (98 + 82))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2786, "answer": 207}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-96 * (-10 * 93)) - ((84 - -30) + 8)) // (48 // -23)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2787, "answer": -29720}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (77 - (39 + (97 + 41))) % (91 * (-66 - 29))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2788, "answer": -100}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 69 // (((-11 - -77) + 42) - (14 % ((14 // -76) + 52)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2789, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-29 + -37) - ((-88 + 56) - 4)) % (59 + -45)) * 29", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2790, "answer": 348}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (92 * ((-61 - -38) + -88)) - (-28 * 1)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2791, "answer": -10184}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-43 // -23) * (-8 + ((53 + -15) + -54))) + (-52 - -73)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2792, "answer": -3}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-39 + 30) + 16) // (-98 + ((-46 - (-20 + 8)) + 60))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2793, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-23 - 51) + (-45 * 23)) + ((13 - -29) - 18)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2794, "answer": -1085}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((69 + ((10 // (-52 + -54)) // -70)) - -13) % -88", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2795, "answer": -6}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((((42 + 5) - 82) % 29) % 83) - 80", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2796, "answer": -57}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-89 // ((-19 + 34) // (-44 + -44))) - -4", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2797, "answer": 93}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((((-74 * -42) * 32) - -19) * -19) * 92", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2798, "answer": -173882300}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -57 + (((33 - -97) + -72) - (-82 * -52))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2799, "answer": -4263}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((39 * -76) * -4) + ((-1 + (54 // -24)) - 56)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2800, "answer": 11796}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-51 * ((-90 // -8) - (-69 + 48))) % (72 - 90)) // 52", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2801, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((((29 + 11) + 70) + 27) + -80) // 24", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2802, "answer": 2}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (65 - ((53 % -47) - (93 + 43))) + 84", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2803, "answer": 326}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 26 + (54 * ((-60 - (-46 + (-80 - 96))) - -50))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2804, "answer": 11474}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-65 * (45 * 98)) - (-89 // 71)) // (-45 // 23)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2805, "answer": 143324}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 21 - (((-1 - -60) // (-34 - 39)) * (0 // (-72 * -82)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2806, "answer": 21}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (90 + -66) * (67 * ((0 + 52) + ((10 % -18) + 26)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2807, "answer": 112560}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -56 // (-69 + (((65 - (39 + (-68 + 71))) + 87) * -66))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2808, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-49 * -84) - (-16 - ((49 - 85) + -65))) // (10 - -61)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2809, "answer": 56}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -27 % (((-94 - 50) * 81) + (63 + -72))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2810, "answer": -27}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-26 - (-92 - -11)) - -58) + (-83 * (94 + -87))) - -44", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2811, "answer": -424}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 33 + (4 - ((77 // (-35 - -34)) + (-89 - 39)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2812, "answer": 242}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 78 * (((-34 - (99 + (-30 + 9))) + 45) // (-32 - -28))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2813, "answer": 1248}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (4 + (52 + 75)) - ((6 // (78 * 17)) * (-12 + 2))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2814, "answer": 131}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((47 - 68) // (25 * (-63 % 56))) - (-79 - -21)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2815, "answer": 57}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-25 + (((67 - 14) + 11) - -54)) + -19", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2816, "answer": 74}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((93 - 0) * 55) - (54 // -11)) - -50", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2817, "answer": 5170}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 1 * (((35 + 62) // 3) * (21 - -24))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2818, "answer": 1440}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((((-65 + 76) - 0) % -66) * (0 + -78)) + (95 % -64)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2819, "answer": 4257}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((97 // -51) * (53 // 34)) + -67) * ((41 - 53) + 62)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2820, "answer": -3450}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-68 // 2) - (-3 - -59)) // ((76 + -24) * (-59 * -83))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2821, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-47 * (84 * (-17 * -62))) // ((-48 - -12) - -61)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2822, "answer": -166448}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-99 + ((54 - 0) - -83)) - (-53 + -72)) + -7", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2823, "answer": 156}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-97 - (88 + -41)) - ((97 + -77) * -51)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2824, "answer": 876}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 32 + (((-95 - -15) + 57) * ((-26 - (-37 + -61)) * -67))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2825, "answer": 110984}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-98 - (-62 % (((91 - -42) + 86) % -72))) * (79 * 65)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2826, "answer": -184860}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (38 * (32 * -43)) - ((75 % 63) - 20)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2827, "answer": -52280}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-88 // 94) + (-75 * (10 * 36))) + (-41 - -76)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2828, "answer": -26966}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((29 - (68 - -96)) % -89) * (-61 - -20)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2829, "answer": 1886}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((33 - 98) - (-44 * 74)) + (-7 * 30)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2830, "answer": 2981}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-67 - 7) - (97 - 80)) % ((-49 // 92) // 94)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2831, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-20 * -24) - ((-67 * (-48 % -16)) + -70)) + -82", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2832, "answer": 468}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-15 + -88) * (-35 + (-6 + -41))) + (31 - 21)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2833, "answer": 8456}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -32 - (((12 * -2) % (82 * -88)) - 37)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2834, "answer": 29}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((81 + 79) + (-79 + 86)) - 71) % -66", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2835, "answer": -36}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-81 + 76) + (84 + 0)) - (55 * -51)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2836, "answer": 2884}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (2 + (-75 - 69)) - (24 + (83 - -78))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2837, "answer": -327}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-99 * (-96 + 0)) - (-28 - ((-63 - 52) * 53))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2838, "answer": 3437}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-20 + -30) - -47) * (-82 * ((-68 - 75) - -7))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2839, "answer": -33456}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-29 * 49) * ((60 + 11) + (-92 - -76))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2840, "answer": -78155}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 92 - ((-42 - -24) - ((-6 + 90) // 83))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2841, "answer": 111}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((88 + 36) - 35) % (22 - (-86 // 82))) - (-70 + -6)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2842, "answer": 93}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((56 * -34) - (17 + (-43 - 32))) * (26 * (50 - -88))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2843, "answer": -6623448}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-58 * -57) * (-41 - ((43 - -89) + 13))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2844, "answer": -614916}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((76 % -69) + -20) + (2 + (-20 - 18))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2845, "answer": -118}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((18 - -95) + (4 - -1)) * (96 * -9)) % 3", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2846, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 73 - (((-58 + 41) - (-69 - -53)) - 76)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2847, "answer": 150}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((49 * -45) * ((24 + 43) % -33)) - ((10 * -33) * 82)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2848, "answer": 97620}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-97 * -23) + ((46 - -57) // 70)) + 95", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2849, "answer": 2327}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-91 - -30) - (-40 + -75)) // (-48 - -35)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2850, "answer": -5}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-12 - (49 - 44)) + (-71 * (((-10 + -74) - -60) - -33))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2851, "answer": -656}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -92 * (((20 - (22 + 94)) - 82) - -95)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2852, "answer": 7636}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-35 + 61) + (-78 - (87 - -13))) - (-7 * 89)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2853, "answer": 471}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((((-81 - 60) * -36) - ((-73 + -46) // 96)) - 5) // -50", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2854, "answer": -102}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-54 * 26) * (19 - 10)) + (((25 - -6) - 46) + -46)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2855, "answer": -12697}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-46 + ((25 * -34) + 53)) * -81) + (-43 + 99)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2856, "answer": 68339}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 41 - ((((11 - (-66 - -50)) - (56 * 56)) - -96) * 74)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2857, "answer": 223003}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-6 - (-91 // (-80 - -79))) - (57 + (-14 - -21))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2858, "answer": -161}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -21 + ((92 - (6 + -35)) * ((95 * -80) + (50 - 55)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2859, "answer": -920226}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -99 + ((-1 + ((81 * 56) - -95)) // -20)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2860, "answer": -331}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-12 + ((36 % 70) + (-2 + 17))) + 57) * 47) * -2", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2861, "answer": -9024}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((16 * -53) - (50 - ((-88 + -53) - 95))) * -50", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2862, "answer": 56700}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-21 - -42) + ((-6 + 31) - ((-59 * -31) * -7))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2863, "answer": 12849}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (71 + ((75 + 14) - 59)) - (-59 - ((-98 + -69) * -70))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2864, "answer": 11850}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((20 + 74) // 28) % ((87 + 6) * (51 % (31 * -12)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2865, "answer": -29850}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-91 + ((-48 - -11) + 29)) + -3) * (52 + -24)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2866, "answer": -2856}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-29 + -30) % ((-56 * -2) - (-61 - 26))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2867, "answer": 140}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((53 + 1) * -32) * 89) - ((68 + 90) - 0)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2868, "answer": -153950}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((91 * -79) - -10) * (61 - 89)) * (-29 + 14)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2869, "answer": -3015180}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (84 // (-38 * 14)) - ((54 - 66) - (44 % 86))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2870, "answer": 55}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((((65 + 60) * (-14 % -93)) * -39) + 13) * -10", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2871, "answer": -682630}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (98 - ((-4 * -41) + (-49 * 87))) - (4 + 49)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2872, "answer": 4144}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-36 + 5) + (((90 - 35) + -89) + 79)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2873, "answer": 14}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 22 // ((-46 // -85) - ((-9 - -99) - (-44 - -54)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2874, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-19 + (-88 + 89)) + ((-7 % 33) + (37 + (62 - 49)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2875, "answer": 58}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-25 % 2) + (((-31 + 78) % (-36 - -44)) + -65)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2876, "answer": -57}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-32 - -71) - ((-86 - (-82 - -86)) // (-94 - -54))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2877, "answer": 37}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((24 * 37) + (75 // 53)) - ((1 + -23) + (52 + 19))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2878, "answer": 840}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((33 % (-39 - (10 + -77))) + -32) + (-44 - -17)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2879, "answer": -54}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((36 + 52) - -46) + ((-11 % 72) - 94)) - 97", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2880, "answer": 4}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-91 + -52) - ((86 + 4) + (-14 - 11))) - (-84 - 24)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2881, "answer": -100}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-59 * ((-38 % (-75 + -44)) - 46)) + -71", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2882, "answer": 4885}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (19 - -35) - ((73 - -73) + (-36 - 28))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2883, "answer": -28}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-14 + (26 * (95 // -88))) - 61) * (65 // -6)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2884, "answer": 1397}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 10 - ((27 // (17 + 36)) - (95 + 38))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2885, "answer": 143}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((32 // -49) // -97) // (-34 + (19 // -45))) + (-15 + 69)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2886, "answer": 54}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-25 // ((23 - (32 - -85)) - (-51 - -69))) + 16", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2887, "answer": 16}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-34 + -37) - (10 + (91 // 33))) - (92 * 60)) * 29", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2888, "answer": -162487}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((42 + 44) // 69) - (((-93 + -48) - -52) + 61)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2889, "answer": 29}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-98 * 83) // -12) * -60) // (59 - 60)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2890, "answer": 40620}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 91 // ((-47 - (-66 - 56)) - (-2 - -49))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2891, "answer": 3}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 54 // ((-8 + 3) // ((-99 - -37) * -92))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2892, "answer": -54}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-9 - ((-53 - 75) - (-46 - -58))) // (-69 // -62)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2893, "answer": 131}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-76 + (-98 // -94)) % (-67 // -48)) * (71 - (80 - -90))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2894, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-85 % (36 - -68)) - 78) - (46 * (-85 * -11))) // -23", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2895, "answer": 1872}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((33 - -8) - 14) + ((((51 + 35) - 92) * -61) // -30)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2896, "answer": 14}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((35 - -73) + -4) - (38 - (25 - (74 % (96 * 32))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2897, "answer": 17}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((51 + -9) - (30 * -12)) // (-7 - -6)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2898, "answer": -402}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-13 * -13) * 52) // -89) - (-86 + (48 - (87 % 87)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2899, "answer": -61}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((90 * 29) + 17) - ((73 * ((82 + 96) + -24)) - 32)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2900, "answer": -8583}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (83 * (89 + -92)) - ((-26 + 5) - ((-39 + -14) - -93))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2901, "answer": -188}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-9 - 54) + 79) * 99) * (-5 + (31 + 31))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2902, "answer": 90288}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 30 * ((15 * 13) // ((15 + 97) + 16))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2903, "answer": 30}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-4 + 48) + (-5 - -27)) + ((-67 + (32 - 15)) - -62)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2904, "answer": 78}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((53 - 21) + (-95 - (-84 - 82))) - -27) * -15", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2905, "answer": -1950}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((19 - -32) * 85) - (12 - 10)) % (-49 - 74)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2906, "answer": -95}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-69 + -60) + -15) - ((-12 % (-56 - 99)) - (11 % 15))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2907, "answer": -121}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-3 // ((-60 - 99) - (26 - -62))) - (2 * -7)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2908, "answer": 14}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -27 + ((78 - (-29 - -73)) - (64 - -87))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2909, "answer": -144}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-13 + 43) - -38) - ((-8 * 60) + -13)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2910, "answer": 561}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-68 % ((-47 - -4) + 69)) * ((7 // 31) + -86)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2911, "answer": -860}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-22 % (-92 - 29)) + (95 + 84)) // (-24 - -48)) + -79", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2912, "answer": -73}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -5 - (((97 * -59) + -76) // ((-42 // 1) + 43))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2913, "answer": 5794}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 58 - ((72 - 75) + ((35 % 48) - (66 % 74)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2914, "answer": 92}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -91 * (((53 - -79) - -76) + (-5 - -47))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2915, "answer": -22750}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -58 * (((-91 * 57) - (76 + 74)) - 88)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2916, "answer": 314650}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-37 + 28) * ((-52 + (71 - 72)) - -39)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2917, "answer": 126}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((68 + (44 * 37)) - 58) % -45) * ((16 + 34) // -74)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2918, "answer": 27}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-36 * 92) + (-65 + 90)) + (40 - (-23 // 32))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2919, "answer": -3246}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -52 + ((91 + (12 - -25)) * ((-61 * 87) // (-21 - -29)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2920, "answer": -85044}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((97 - 76) * 96) * (95 % (54 - 12))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2921, "answer": 22176}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (53 + 67) // ((75 + (14 // -22)) * (57 + 46))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2922, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((70 - -77) + -21) + ((57 - -44) - 46)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2923, "answer": 181}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-76 - (-15 + 12)) + ((68 // -63) + -49)) * (-97 // -60)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2924, "answer": -124}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((43 + (-31 // 97)) + 51) - ((8 - 71) - (-68 - 70))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2925, "answer": 18}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (48 + -62) - ((-31 - -1) - (((-52 - -86) - -42) * 20))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2926, "answer": 1536}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (81 + 43) // ((0 - 73) * (-47 + 32))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2927, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((27 - 29) % (-86 + -32)) - ((50 + -1) + 76)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2928, "answer": -127}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((((18 * 29) + -1) - 44) + (-86 - -9)) + -13", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2929, "answer": 387}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (64 * 92) - ((-33 - 64) + (55 + -32))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2930, "answer": 5962}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-57 - ((-5 * 6) - -72)) + (12 + -9)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2931, "answer": -96}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-89 + -84) * -25) * (-77 * (14 - -35))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2932, "answer": -16318225}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-5 * ((-36 * -16) % (62 + (47 + 36)))) // -11", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2933, "answer": 64}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-12 - (((-39 + -42) * (41 - -18)) + -87)) + (61 - -32)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2934, "answer": 4947}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (82 + 45) + (((6 + 82) + -47) - -52)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2935, "answer": 220}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-28 - (-46 - (41 // (-99 + 3)))) * -89) // 91", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2936, "answer": -17}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (89 + ((-90 + -6) - (-67 - 55))) // (36 % (-10 * 18))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2937, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((59 + 54) + -94) * ((22 % -95) + (-10 - 58))) + 59", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2938, "answer": -2620}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -71 - ((-18 // (-88 + -20)) + (61 + (23 + 88)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2939, "answer": -243}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-43 - (10 + -80)) + (53 // (-64 - -72))) + (41 * 51)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2940, "answer": 2124}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((18 * -71) - -27) + ((-60 + -88) + (-37 * -78))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2941, "answer": 1487}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-27 - -36) - (-54 - (((-10 - 2) + (-55 + -43)) + -48))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2942, "answer": -95}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 6 // (((8 + 96) + -62) * ((-16 - -15) * -13))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2943, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-86 + 73) - (4 % 62)) + (92 % -85)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2944, "answer": -95}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-98 - -98) - -8) - 92) * (41 // 25)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2945, "answer": -84}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-18 - (-80 % 98)) - -81) % (-78 + 79)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2946, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -1 + (((-53 * (-6 - -51)) - 48) + (95 // (-95 - 62)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2947, "answer": -2435}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-79 + 8) * -15) - ((14 + 49) + (-51 + -62))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2948, "answer": 1115}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-62 - -30) % (2 % (6 + 92))) + 36", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2949, "answer": 36}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((47 - (-63 * 85)) - (-22 + (99 + 68))) - -83", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2950, "answer": 5340}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-19 * (-87 + 56)) + (-51 - (1 - 99))) - -6", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2951, "answer": 642}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (7 + -48) // ((-19 - 24) * (((-50 * 20) * 80) - -86))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2952, "answer": -1}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((4 + (-40 - 16)) + (-91 * 64)) // 66", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2953, "answer": -90}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 19 // (92 - ((-84 - -71) + (-12 - 81)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2954, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-45 + 61) - ((15 - 65) // 39)) - (-2 - 36)) - -72", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2955, "answer": 128}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-90 + -9) + 55) - -75) + ((77 // 99) + 45)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2956, "answer": 76}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 96 + (-85 // (((51 - -78) * 99) + -3))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2957, "answer": 95}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((84 // 67) - (25 - (-3 - -26))) + (-92 * 33)) + 55", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2958, "answer": -2982}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-1 - -10) // 81) + (((-61 * 90) - -14) - 47)) // -48", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2959, "answer": 115}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (70 - ((-5 * -98) - 48)) - ((-53 % -96) // 21)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2960, "answer": -369}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((68 - 85) - -53) + ((49 - 70) - -59)) - (-93 - 95)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2961, "answer": 262}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-68 + (32 - -94)) * 90) + (-93 - 56)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2962, "answer": 5071}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (51 * (51 // (47 - -99))) // (68 + 20)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2963, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -49 - ((77 + 4) + (36 + (-11 % 72)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2964, "answer": -227}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((((27 - -87) * (-28 - 72)) // 51) - 19) + (79 - -1)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2965, "answer": -163}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-73 + 45) - (((-21 - 12) + -92) + ((-48 * 63) - -18))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2966, "answer": 3103}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((52 + -57) - -61) + (-9 * (-47 + ((-38 * 87) - 46)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2967, "answer": 30647}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-9 * -88) - (27 - -8)) * (9 // 20)) + (85 + 35)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2968, "answer": 120}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-7 - (42 + (88 // -71))) - (87 * 28)) * -32", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2969, "answer": 79456}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((16 * 56) * (-4 * 58)) * (((-44 - 38) - -39) - -4)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2970, "answer": 8107008}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-54 - ((98 // -90) + -79)) // 57) + (-84 - 79)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2971, "answer": -163}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-61 - -2) % 26) // (48 + (46 * (50 * 48)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2972, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-38 - 74) - (-45 + (-37 + (43 // -44)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2973, "answer": -29}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((32 + 89) * 86) // ((-40 % -39) * -15)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2974, "answer": 693}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (77 - -56) - (-65 - (((-35 * 23) // 30) * -68))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2975, "answer": 2034}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (4 * 52) - ((-25 * (-68 + 16)) % -40)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2976, "answer": 228}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-64 * 49) + ((13 * 66) - ((-14 - -97) // (46 - 67)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2977, "answer": -2274}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (((-19 // -16) // (78 * 70)) + (86 + 24)) // 45", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2978, "answer": 2}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-81 + -67) * (-45 * -22)) + (-47 * -10)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2979, "answer": -146050}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-82 - (((-9 * -91) // 51) - -63)) - 18", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2980, "answer": -179}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 59 * ((88 // (-2 + 52)) % (7 - -52))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2981, "answer": 59}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-48 * (5 + 38)) // ((99 + (-31 // -72)) - (84 // -82))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2982, "answer": -21}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (25 + (-33 - 60)) - (-10 + (50 * -61))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2983, "answer": 2992}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. -72 - (30 - (((-45 * -60) // 96) * 61))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2984, "answer": 1606}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (15 + -17) - ((29 - 63) + (-74 - (-16 % (-90 + -51))))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2985, "answer": 90}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-86 - 65) + (6 - -26)) + (-1 + (-22 % -14))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2986, "answer": -128}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((-99 + -54) - -68) - (-12 - ((60 + 82) + 79))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2987, "answer": 148}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (46 + -27) - (26 + (93 - (-36 + 71)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2988, "answer": -65}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-1 + -1) - (60 + ((21 + 76) + (85 - 70)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2989, "answer": -174}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-36 * (-86 * (48 // 99))) % (-72 // 1)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2990, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-80 - (62 * 96)) * (90 + (-99 - -56))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2991, "answer": -283504}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (25 - (3 % -82)) - ((56 * -13) - 12)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2992, "answer": 844}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (36 // (((-50 - -44) - 73) * (12 - 1))) // -7", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2993, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-64 + (((-15 // (79 + 95)) + (42 - -70)) * 13)) + 66", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2994, "answer": 1445}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. 71 // (((45 - -84) * 81) * ((89 + -22) - (-56 - -78)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2995, "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (65 + (67 * ((47 + (29 - -71)) - (-71 + -27)))) + -98", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2996, "answer": 16382}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (78 * 81) * ((49 * -69) * (-56 * 6))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2997, "answer": 7177349088}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. (-69 * -58) + (-72 + ((-89 - -61) - (59 % 30)))", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2998, "answer": 3873}
{"problem": "Evaluate this Python expression. ((59 * 29) // 32) + (((60 + -23) // (77 + 39)) // -62)", "round": "arithmetic", "category": "n/a", "problem_number": 2999, "answer": 53}
